# newdoc id = hp4diolog.csv
# sent_id = 4001
# text = Bloody kids.
1	Bloody	O	O	O
2	kids	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4002
# text = Oh no no no my Lord Voldemort. I only meant... perhaps if we were to do it without the boy..
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	no	O	O	O
3	no	O	O	O
4	no	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	Lord	B-TTL	O	O
7	Voldemort	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	I	O	O	O
10	only	O	O	O
11	meant	O	O	O
12	...	O	O	O
13	perhaps	O	O	O
14	if	O	O	O
15	we	O	O	O
16	were	O	O	O
17	to	O	O	O
18	do	O	O	O
19	it	O	O	O
20	without	O	O	O
21	the	O	O	O
22	boy	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4003
# text = NO! The boy is everything, it cannot be done without him and it WILL be done exactly as I say.
1	NO	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	The	O	O	O
4	boy	O	O	O
5	is	O	O	O
6	everything	O	O	O
7	,	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	cannot	O	O	O
10	be	O	O	O
11	done	O	O	O
12	without	O	O	O
13	him	O	O	O
14	and	O	O	O
15	it	O	O	O
16	WILL	O	O	O
17	be	O	O	O
18	done	O	O	O
19	exactly	O	O	O
20	as	O	O	O
21	I	O	O	O
22	say	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4004
# text = I will not disappoint you my lord.
1	I	O	O	O
2	will	O	O	O
3	not	O	O	O
4	disappoint	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	my	O	O	O
7	lord	B-TTL	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4005
# text = Good. First, gather our old comrades. Send them a sign.
1	Good	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	First	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	gather	O	O	O
6	our	O	O	O
7	old	O	O	O
8	comrades	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	Send	O	O	O
11	them	O	O	O
12	a	O	O	O
13	sign	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4006
# text = Nagini tells me the old caretaker is standing outside the door.
1	Nagini	B-PER	O	O
2	tells	O	O	O
3	me	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	old	O	O	O
6	caretaker	O	O	O
7	is	O	O	O
8	standing	O	O	O
9	outside	O	O	O
10	the	O	O	O
11	door	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4007
# text = Step aside so I can give our guest a proper greeting.
1	Step	O	O	O
2	aside	O	O	O
3	so	O	O	O
4	I	O	O	O
5	can	O	O	O
6	give	O	O	O
7	our	O	O	O
8	guest	O	O	O
9	a	O	O	O
10	proper	O	O	O
11	greeting	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4008
# text = Harry!
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4009
# text = Are you alright?
1	Are	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	alright	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4010
# text = Hermione. Bad dream. When did you get here?
1	Hermione	B-PER	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Bad	O	O	O
4	dream	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	When	O	O	O
7	did	O	O	O
8	you	O	O	O
9	get	O	O	O
10	here	O	O	O
11	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4011
# text = Just now. You?
1	Just	O	O	O
2	now	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	You	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4012
# text = Last night.
1	Last	O	O	O
2	night	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4013
# text = Wake up. Wake up Ronald!
1	Wake	O	O	O
2	up	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	Wake	O	O	O
5	up	O	O	O
6	Ronald	B-PER	O	O
7	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4014
# text = Bloody hell.
1	Bloody	O	O	O
2	hell	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4015
# text = Honestly. Get dressed, and don't go back to sleep. Come on Ron! Your mother says breakfast's ready.
1	Honestly	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Get	O	O	O
4	dressed	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	and	O	O	O
7	do	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	go	O	O	O
10	back	O	O	O
11	to	O	O	O
12	sleep	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	Come	O	O	O
15	on	O	O	O
16	Ron	B-PER	O	O
17	!	O	O	O
18	Your	O	O	O
19	mother	O	O	O
20	says	O	O	O
21	breakfast	O	O	O
22	's	O	O	O
23	ready	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4016
# text = Where are we actually going?
1	Where	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	we	O	O	O
4	actually	O	O	O
5	going	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4017
# text = Don't know. Hey Dad! Where are we going?
1	Do	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	know	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Hey	O	O	O
6	Dad	O	O	O
7	!	O	O	O
8	Where	O	O	O
9	are	O	O	O
10	we	O	O	O
11	going	O	O	O
12	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4018
# text = Haven't the foggiest, keep up!
1	Have	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	foggiest	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	keep	O	O	O
7	up	O	O	O
8	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4019
# text = Arthur! It's about time son.
1	Arthur	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	It	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	about	O	O	O
6	time	O	O	O
7	son	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4020
# text = Sorry Amos. Some of us had a bit of a sleepy start. This is Amos Diggory everyone, he works with me at the ministry. And this strapping young lad must be Cedric, am I right?
1	Sorry	O	O	O
2	Amos	B-PER	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	Some	O	O	O
5	of	O	O	O
6	us	O	O	O
7	had	O	O	O
8	a	O	O	O
9	bit	O	O	O
10	of	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	sleepy	O	O	O
13	start	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	This	O	O	O
16	is	O	O	O
17	Amos	B-PER	O	O
18	Diggory	I-PER	O	O
19	everyone	O	O	O
20	,	O	O	O
21	he	O	O	O
22	works	O	O	O
23	with	O	O	O
24	me	O	O	O
25	at	O	O	O
26	the	O	O	O
27	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
28	.	O	O	O
29	And	O	O	O
30	this	O	O	O
31	strapping	O	O	O
32	young	O	O	O
33	lad	O	O	O
34	must	O	O	O
35	be	O	O	O
36	Cedric	B-PER	O	O
37	,	O	O	O
38	am	O	O	O
39	I	O	O	O
40	right	O	O	O
41	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4021
# text = Yes sir.
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4022
# text = Merlin's beard, you must be Harry Potter.
1	Merlin	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	beard	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	must	O	O	O
7	be	O	O	O
8	Harry	B-PER	O	O
9	Potter	I-PER	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4023
# text = Yes sir. This way.
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	This	O	O	O
5	way	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4024
# text = Great great pleasure.
1	Great	O	O	O
2	great	O	O	O
3	pleasure	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4025
# text = Pleasure to meet you too sir.
1	Pleasure	O	O	O
2	to	O	O	O
3	meet	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	too	O	O	O
6	sir	B-TTL	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4026
# text = That's it sir, just over there.
1	That	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	it	O	O	O
4	sir	B-TTL	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	just	O	O	O
7	over	O	O	O
8	there	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4027
# text = Shall we? We don't want to be late.
1	Shall	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O
4	We	O	O	O
5	do	O	O	O
6	n't	O	O	O
7	want	O	O	O
8	to	O	O	O
9	be	O	O	O
10	late	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4028
# text = Why are they all standing around that manky old boot?
1	Why	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	they	O	O	O
4	all	O	O	O
5	standing	O	O	O
6	around	O	O	O
7	that	O	O	O
8	manky	O	O	O
9	old	O	O	O
10	boot	O	O	O
11	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4029
# text = That isn't just any old manky boot mate.
1	That	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	just	O	O	O
5	any	O	O	O
6	old	O	O	O
7	manky	O	O	O
8	boot	O	O	O
9	mate	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4030
# text = It's a portkey.
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	portkey	B-MIT	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4031
# text = Time to go. Ready?
1	Time	O	O	O
2	to	O	O	O
3	go	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Ready	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4032
# text = What's a 'portkey'?
1	What	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	'	O	O	O
5	portkey	B-MIT	O	O
6	'	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4033
# text = After 3. One... Two...
1	After	O	O	O
2	3	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	One	O	O	O
5	...	O	O	O
6	Two	O	O	O
7	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4034
# text = Harry!
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4035
# text = Three!
1	Three	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4036
# text = Let go kids!
1	Let	O	O	O
2	go	O	O	O
3	kids	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4037
# text = What??
1	What	O	O	O
2	?	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4038
# text = Let! Go!
1	Let	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	Go	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4039
# text = I bet that cleared your sinuses eh?
1	I	O	O	O
2	bet	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	cleared	O	O	O
5	your	O	O	O
6	sinuses	O	O	O
7	eh	O	O	O
8	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4040
# text = Thanks.
1	Thanks	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4041
# text = Well kids, welcome to the Quidditch World Cup!
1	Well	O	O	O
2	kids	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	welcome	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	Quidditch	B-EVN	O	O
8	World	I-EVN	O	O
9	Cup	I-EVN	O	O
10	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4042
# text = Parting of the waves I think old chap, see you at the match.
1	Parting	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	waves	O	O	O
5	I	O	O	O
6	think	O	O	O
7	old	O	O	O
8	chap	O	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	see	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	at	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	match	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4043
# text = See ya later Cedric.
1	See	O	O	O
2	ya	O	O	O
3	later	O	O	O
4	Cedric	B-PER	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4044
# text = Home sweet home.
1	Home	O	O	O
2	sweet	O	O	O
3	home	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4045
# text = Girls. Choose a bunk and unpack. Ron, get out of the kitchen we're all hungry.
1	Girls	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Choose	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	bunk	O	O	O
6	and	O	O	O
7	unpack	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Ron	B-PER	O	O
10	,	O	O	O
11	get	O	O	O
12	out	O	O	O
13	of	O	O	O
14	the	O	O	O
15	kitchen	O	O	O
16	we	O	O	O
17	're	O	O	O
18	all	O	O	O
19	hungry	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4046
# text = Yeah get out of the kitchen Ron.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	get	O	O	O
3	out	O	O	O
4	of	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	kitchen	O	O	O
7	Ron	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4047
# text = Yeah get out of the kitchen Ron.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	get	O	O	O
3	out	O	O	O
4	of	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	kitchen	O	O	O
7	Ron	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4048
# text = Feet off the table.
1	Feet	O	O	O
2	off	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	table	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4049
# text = Feet off the table.
1	Feet	O	O	O
2	off	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	table	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4050
# text = Feet off the table.
1	Feet	O	O	O
2	off	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	table	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4051
# text = I love magic.
1	I	O	O	O
2	love	O	O	O
3	magic	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4052
# text = Blimey Dad, how far up are we?
1	Blimey	O	O	O
2	Dad	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	how	O	O	O
5	far	O	O	O
6	up	O	O	O
7	are	O	O	O
8	we	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4053
# text = Well put it this way, if it rains... you'll be the first to know
1	Well	O	O	O
2	put	O	O	O
3	it	O	O	O
4	this	O	O	O
5	way	O	O	O
6	,	O	O	O
7	if	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	rains	O	O	O
10	...	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	'll	O	O	O
13	be	O	O	O
14	the	O	O	O
15	first	O	O	O
16	to	O	O	O
17	know	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4054
# text = Father and I are in the minister's box, by personal invitation of Cornelius Fudge himself.
1	Father	O	O	O
2	and	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	are	O	O	O
5	in	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	minister	B-TTL	O	O
8	's	O	O	O
9	box	O	O	O
10	,	O	O	O
11	by	O	O	O
12	personal	O	O	O
13	invitation	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	Cornelius	I-PER	O	O
16	Fudge	B-PER	O	O
17	himself	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4055
# text = Don't boast Draco. There's no need with these people. Do enjoy yourself won't you. While you can.
1	Do	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	boast	O	O	O
4	Draco	B-PER	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	There	O	O	O
7	's	O	O	O
8	no	O	O	O
9	need	O	O	O
10	with	O	O	O
11	these	O	O	O
12	people	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	Do	O	O	O
15	enjoy	O	O	O
16	yourself	O	O	O
17	wo	O	O	O
18	n't	O	O	O
19	you	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O
21	While	O	O	O
22	you	O	O	O
23	can	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4056
# text = Come on up, take your seats. I told you these seats would be worth waiting for.
1	Come	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	up	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	take	O	O	O
6	your	O	O	O
7	seats	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	I	O	O	O
10	told	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	these	O	O	O
13	seats	O	O	O
14	would	O	O	O
15	be	O	O	O
16	worth	O	O	O
17	waiting	O	O	O
18	for	O	O	O
19	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4057
# text = Come on!
1	Come	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4058
# text = It's the Irish!
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	Irish	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4059
# text = Here come the Bulgarians!
1	Here	O	O	O
2	come	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	Bulgarians	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4060
# text = Krum!!!
1	Krum	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4061
# text = Krum!!!
1	Krum	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4062
# text = Krum!!!
1	Krum	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4063
# text = Yes!
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4064
# text = Good evening! It gives me great pleasure to welcome each and every one of you to the final of the 422nd Quidditch World Cup. Let the match begin!
1	Good	O	O	O
2	evening	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	It	O	O	O
5	gives	O	O	O
6	me	O	O	O
7	great	O	O	O
8	pleasure	O	O	O
9	to	O	O	O
10	welcome	O	O	O
11	each	O	O	O
12	and	O	O	O
13	every	O	O	O
14	one	O	O	O
15	of	O	O	O
16	you	O	O	O
17	to	O	O	O
18	the	O	O	O
19	final	O	O	O
20	of	O	O	O
21	the	O	O	O
22	422nd	B-EVN	O	O
23	Quidditch	I-EVN	O	O
24	World	I-EVN	O	O
25	Cup	I-EVN	O	O
26	.	O	O	O
27	Let	O	O	O
28	the	O	O	O
29	match	O	O	O
30	begin	O	O	O
31	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4065
# text = There's no one like Krum. He's like a bird the way he rides the wind. He's more than an athlete, he's an artist.
1	There	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	no	O	O	O
4	one	O	O	O
5	like	O	O	O
6	Krum	B-PER	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	He	O	O	O
9	's	O	O	O
10	like	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	bird	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	way	O	O	O
15	he	O	O	O
16	rides	O	O	O
17	the	O	O	O
18	wind	O	O	O
19	.	O	O	O
20	He	O	O	O
21	's	O	O	O
22	more	O	O	O
23	than	O	O	O
24	an	O	O	O
25	athlete	O	O	O
26	,	O	O	O
27	he	O	O	O
28	's	O	O	O
29	an	O	O	O
30	artist	O	O	O
31	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4066
# text = Think you're in love Ron?
1	Think	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	in	O	O	O
5	love	O	O	O
6	Ron	B-PER	O	O
7	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4067
# text = Viktor I love you! Viktor I do!
1	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	love	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O
6	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
7	I	O	O	O
8	do	O	O	O
9	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4068
# text = Viktor I love you! Viktor I do!
1	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	love	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O
6	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
7	I	O	O	O
8	do	O	O	O
9	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4069
# text = When we're apart my heart beats only for youuu!
1	When	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	apart	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	heart	O	O	O
7	beats	O	O	O
8	only	O	O	O
9	for	O	O	O
10	youuu	O	O	O
11	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4070
# text = When we're apart my heart beats only for youuu!
1	When	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	apart	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	heart	O	O	O
7	beats	O	O	O
8	only	O	O	O
9	for	O	O	O
10	youuu	O	O	O
11	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4071
# text = When we're apart my heart beats only for youuu!
1	When	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	apart	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	heart	O	O	O
7	beats	O	O	O
8	only	O	O	O
9	for	O	O	O
10	youuu	O	O	O
11	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4072
# text = Sounds like the irish have got their pride on.
1	Sounds	O	O	O
2	like	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	irish	O	O	O
5	have	O	O	O
6	got	O	O	O
7	their	O	O	O
8	pride	O	O	O
9	on	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4073
# text = Stop! Stop it. It's not the irish. We've gotta get out of here. Now.
1	Stop	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	Stop	O	O	O
4	it	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	It	O	O	O
7	's	O	O	O
8	not	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	irish	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	We	O	O	O
13	've	O	O	O
14	gotta	O	O	O
15	get	O	O	O
16	out	O	O	O
17	of	O	O	O
18	here	O	O	O
19	.	O	O	O
20	Now	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4074
# text = Get back to the portkey everybody, and stick together. Fred, George... Ginny is your responsibility.
1	Get	O	O	O
2	back	O	O	O
3	to	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	portkey	B-MIT	O	O
6	everybody	O	O	O
7	,	O	O	O
8	and	O	O	O
9	stick	O	O	O
10	together	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	Fred	B-PER	O	O
13	,	O	O	O
14	George	B-PER	O	O
15	...	O	O	O
16	Ginny	B-PER	O	O
17	is	O	O	O
18	your	O	O	O
19	responsibility	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4075
# text = Been looking for you for ages. Thought we lost you.
1	Been	O	O	O
2	looking	O	O	O
3	for	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	for	O	O	O
6	ages	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Thought	O	O	O
9	we	O	O	O
10	lost	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4076
# text = What is that?
1	What	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4077
# text = Stop! That's my son.
1	Stop	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	That	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	son	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4078
# text = Ron, Harry, Hermione are you alright?
1	Ron	B-PER	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	Harry	B-PER	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	Hermione	B-PER	O	O
6	are	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	alright	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4079
# text = Which of you conjured this?
1	Which	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	conjured	O	O	O
5	this	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4080
# text = You can't possibly..
1	You	O	O	O
2	ca	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	possibly	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4081
# text = Do not lie! You have been discovered at the scene of the crime!
1	Do	O	O	O
2	not	O	O	O
3	lie	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O
5	You	O	O	O
6	have	O	O	O
7	been	O	O	O
8	discovered	O	O	O
9	at	O	O	O
10	the	O	O	O
11	scene	O	O	O
12	of	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	crime	O	O	O
15	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4082
# text = Crime?
1	Crime	O	O	O
2	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4083
# text = Barty, they're just kids.
1	Barty	B-PER	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	they	O	O	O
4	're	O	O	O
5	just	O	O	O
6	kids	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4084
# text = What crime?
1	What	O	O	O
2	crime	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4085
# text = Harry it's his mark.
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	his	O	O	O
5	mark	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4086
# text = Those people tonight, in the masks... they're his too aren't they? they're his followers.
1	Those	O	O	O
2	people	O	O	O
3	tonight	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	in	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	masks	O	O	O
8	...	O	O	O
9	they	O	O	O
10	're	O	O	O
11	his	O	O	O
12	too	O	O	O
13	are	O	O	O
14	n't	O	O	O
15	they	O	O	O
16	?	O	O	O
17	they	O	O	O
18	're	O	O	O
19	his	O	O	O
20	followers	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4087
# text = Follow me.
1	Follow	O	O	O
2	me	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4088
# text = There was a man. Before. There.
1	There	O	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	man	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Before	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	There	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4089
# text = All of you, this way.
1	All	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	this	O	O	O
6	way	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4090
# text = Harry, who?
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	who	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4091
# text = I dunno. I didn't see his face.
1	I	O	O	O
2	dunno	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	I	O	O	O
5	did	O	O	O
6	n't	O	O	O
7	see	O	O	O
8	his	O	O	O
9	face	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4092
# text = Anything from the trolley? Anything from the trolley?
1	Anything	O	O	O
2	from	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	trolley	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O
6	Anything	O	O	O
7	from	O	O	O
8	the	O	O	O
9	trolley	O	O	O
10	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4093
# text = Anything from the trolley dears?
1	Anything	O	O	O
2	from	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	trolley	O	O	O
5	dears	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4094
# text = Packet of drewbals and a liquorice wand.
1	Packet	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	drewbals	B-PER	O	O
4	and	O	O	O
5	a	O	O	O
6	liquorice	O	O	O
7	wand	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4095
# text = On second thought, just the drewbals.
1	On	O	O	O
2	second	O	O	O
3	thought	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	just	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	drewbals	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4096
# text = It's alright I'll get it.
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	alright	O	O	O
4	I	O	O	O
5	'll	O	O	O
6	get	O	O	O
7	it	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4097
# text = Just the drewbals, thanks.
1	Just	O	O	O
2	the	O	O	O
3	drewbals	B-PER	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	thanks	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4098
# text = Two pumpkin pasties please.
1	Two	O	O	O
2	pumpkin	O	O	O
3	pasties	O	O	O
4	please	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4099
# text = Thank you.
1	Thank	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4100
# text = Anything sweet for you dear?
1	Anything	O	O	O
2	sweet	O	O	O
3	for	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	dear	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4101
# text = Oh no thank you I'm not hungry.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	no	O	O	O
3	thank	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	I	O	O	O
6	'm	O	O	O
7	not	O	O	O
8	hungry	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4102
# text = This is horrible, how can the ministry not know who conjured it. Isn't there any security or?
1	This	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	horrible	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	how	O	O	O
6	can	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
9	not	O	O	O
10	know	O	O	O
11	who	O	O	O
12	conjured	O	O	O
13	it	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	Is	O	O	O
16	n't	O	O	O
17	there	O	O	O
18	any	O	O	O
19	security	O	O	O
20	or	O	O	O
21	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4103
# text = Loads according to Dad, that's what worried them so much. Happened right under their noses.
1	Loads	O	O	O
2	according	O	O	O
3	to	O	O	O
4	Dad	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	that	O	O	O
7	's	O	O	O
8	what	O	O	O
9	worried	O	O	O
10	them	O	O	O
11	so	O	O	O
12	much	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	Happened	O	O	O
15	right	O	O	O
16	under	O	O	O
17	their	O	O	O
18	noses	O	O	O
19	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4104
# text = It's hurting again isn't it, your scar.
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	hurting	O	O	O
4	again	O	O	O
5	is	O	O	O
6	n't	O	O	O
7	it	O	O	O
8	,	O	O	O
9	your	O	O	O
10	scar	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4105
# text = I'm fine.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	fine	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4106
# text = You know Sirius will want to hear about this. What you saw at the world cup, and the dream.
1	You	O	O	O
2	know	O	O	O
3	Sirius	B-PER	O	O
4	will	O	O	O
5	want	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	hear	O	O	O
8	about	O	O	O
9	this	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	What	O	O	O
12	you	O	O	O
13	saw	O	O	O
14	at	O	O	O
15	the	O	O	O
16	world	O	O	O
17	cup	O	O	O
18	,	O	O	O
19	and	O	O	O
20	the	O	O	O
21	dream	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4107
# text = Clear the runway.
1	Clear	O	O	O
2	the	O	O	O
3	runway	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4108
# text = Well there's something you don't see every day.
1	Well	O	O	O
2	there	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	something	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	do	O	O	O
7	n't	O	O	O
8	see	O	O	O
9	every	O	O	O
10	day	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4109
# text = Now we're all settled in and sorted, I'd like to make an announcement. This castle will not only be your home this year but home to some very special guests as well. You see Hogwarts has been choosen...
1	Now	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	all	O	O	O
5	settled	O	O	O
6	in	O	O	O
7	and	O	O	O
8	sorted	O	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	I	O	O	O
11	'd	O	O	O
12	like	O	O	O
13	to	O	O	O
14	make	O	O	O
15	an	O	O	O
16	announcement	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O
18	This	O	O	O
19	castle	O	O	O
20	will	O	O	O
21	not	O	O	O
22	only	O	O	O
23	be	O	O	O
24	your	O	O	O
25	home	O	O	O
26	this	O	O	O
27	year	O	O	O
28	but	O	O	O
29	home	O	O	O
30	to	O	O	O
31	some	O	O	O
32	very	O	O	O
33	special	O	O	O
34	guests	O	O	O
35	as	O	O	O
36	well	O	O	O
37	.	O	O	O
38	You	O	O	O
39	see	O	O	O
40	Hogwarts	B-ORG	O	O
41	has	O	O	O
42	been	O	O	O
43	choosen	O	O	O
44	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4110
# text = So Hogwarts has been choosen to host a legendary event. The Tri-Wizard tournament. Now for those of you who do not know, the tri-wizard tournament brings together three schools for a series of magical contests. From each school a single contestant is selected to compete. Now let me be clear, if choosen you stand alone. And trust me when I say these contests are not for the faint hearted, but more of that later. For now please join me in welcoming the lovely ladies of the Beauxbatons Academy of magic and their headmistress Madam Maxime.
1	So	O	O	O
2	Hogwarts	B-ORG	O	O
3	has	O	O	O
4	been	O	O	O
5	choosen	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	host	O	O	O
8	a	O	O	O
9	legendary	O	O	O
10	event	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	The	O	O	O
13	Tri	B-EVN	O	O
14	Wizard	I-EVN	O	O
15	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
16	.	O	O	O
17	Now	O	O	O
18	for	O	O	O
19	those	O	O	O
20	of	O	O	O
21	you	O	O	O
22	who	O	O	O
23	do	O	O	O
24	not	O	O	O
25	know	O	O	O
26	,	O	O	O
27	the	O	O	O
28	tri	B-EVN	O	O
29	wizard	I-EVN	O	O
30	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
31	brings	O	O	O
32	together	O	O	O
33	three	O	O	O
34	schools	O	O	O
35	for	O	O	O
36	a	O	O	O
37	series	O	O	O
38	of	O	O	O
39	magical	O	O	O
40	contests	O	O	O
41	.	O	O	O
42	From	O	O	O
43	each	O	O	O
44	school	O	O	O
45	a	O	O	O
46	single	O	O	O
47	contestant	O	O	O
48	is	O	O	O
49	selected	O	O	O
50	to	O	O	O
51	compete	O	O	O
52	.	O	O	O
53	Now	O	O	O
54	let	O	O	O
55	me	O	O	O
56	be	O	O	O
57	clear	O	O	O
58	,	O	O	O
59	if	O	O	O
60	choosen	O	O	O
61	you	O	O	O
62	stand	O	O	O
63	alone	O	O	O
64	.	O	O	O
65	And	O	O	O
66	trust	O	O	O
67	me	O	O	O
68	when	O	O	O
69	I	O	O	O
70	say	O	O	O
71	these	O	O	O
72	contests	O	O	O
73	are	O	O	O
74	not	O	O	O
75	for	O	O	O
76	the	O	O	O
77	faint	O	O	O
78	hearted	O	O	O
79	,	O	O	O
80	but	O	O	O
81	more	O	O	O
82	of	O	O	O
83	that	O	O	O
84	later	O	O	O
85	.	O	O	O
86	For	O	O	O
87	now	O	O	O
88	please	O	O	O
89	join	O	O	O
90	me	O	O	O
91	in	O	O	O
92	welcoming	O	O	O
93	the	O	O	O
94	lovely	O	O	O
95	ladies	O	O	O
96	of	O	O	O
97	the	O	O	O
98	Beauxbatons	B-ORG	O	O
99	Academy	I-ORG	O	O
100	of	O	O	O
101	magic	O	O	O
102	and	O	O	O
103	their	O	O	O
104	headmistress	B-TTL	O	O
105	Madam	B-TTL	O	O
106	Maxime	B-PER	O	O
107	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4111
# text = Blimey, that's one big woman.
1	Blimey	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	one	O	O	O
6	big	O	O	O
7	woman	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4112
# text = And now our friends from the north, please greet the proud sons of Durmstrang and the high master Igor Karkaroff.
1	And	O	O	O
2	now	O	O	O
3	our	O	O	O
4	friends	O	O	O
5	from	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	north	O	O	O
8	,	O	O	O
9	please	O	O	O
10	greet	O	O	O
11	the	O	O	O
12	proud	O	O	O
13	sons	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	Durmstrang	B-ORG	O	O
16	and	O	O	O
17	the	O	O	O
18	high	B-TTL	O	O
19	master	I-TTL	O	O
20	Igor	B-PER	O	O
21	Karkaroff	I-PER	O	O
22	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4113
# text = Blimey it's him, Viktor Krum!
1	Blimey	O	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	him	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
7	Krum	I-PER	O	O
8	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4114
# text = Albus!
1	Albus	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4115
# text = Igor.
1	Igor	B-PER	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4116
# text = Professor Dumbledore, my horses have travelled a long way. They will need attending to.
1	Professor	B-TTL	O	O
2	Dumbledore	B-PER	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	my	O	O	O
5	horses	O	O	O
6	have	O	O	O
7	travelled	O	O	O
8	a	O	O	O
9	long	O	O	O
10	way	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	They	O	O	O
13	will	O	O	O
14	need	O	O	O
15	attending	O	O	O
16	to	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4117
# text = Not to worry Madame Maxime, our gamekeeper Hagrid's more than capable of seeing to them.
1	Not	O	O	O
2	to	O	O	O
3	worry	O	O	O
4	Madame	B-TTL	O	O
5	Maxime	B-PER	O	O
6	,	O	O	O
7	our	O	O	O
8	gamekeeper	B-TTL	O	O
9	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
10	's	O	O	O
11	more	O	O	O
12	than	O	O	O
13	capable	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	seeing	O	O	O
16	to	O	O	O
17	them	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4118
# text = But you know Monsieur Hagrid, they drink only single malt whiskey.
1	But	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	know	O	O	O
4	Monsieur	B-TTL	O	O
5	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
6	,	O	O	O
7	they	O	O	O
8	drink	O	O	O
9	only	O	O	O
10	single	O	O	O
11	malt	O	O	O
12	whiskey	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4119
# text = You idiot!
1	You	O	O	O
2	idiot	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4120
# text = Your attention please! I would like to say a few words. Eternal glory, that is what awaits the student who wins the tri-wizard tournament. But to do this that student must survive three tasks. Three extremely dangerous tasks.
1	Your	O	O	O
2	attention	O	O	O
3	please	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O
5	I	O	O	O
6	would	O	O	O
7	like	O	O	O
8	to	O	O	O
9	say	O	O	O
10	a	O	O	O
11	few	O	O	O
12	words	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	Eternal	O	O	O
15	glory	O	O	O
16	,	O	O	O
17	that	O	O	O
18	is	O	O	O
19	what	O	O	O
20	awaits	O	O	O
21	the	O	O	O
22	student	O	O	O
23	who	O	O	O
24	wins	O	O	O
25	the	O	O	O
26	tri	B-EVN	O	O
27	wizard	I-EVN	O	O
28	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
29	.	O	O	O
30	But	O	O	O
31	to	O	O	O
32	do	O	O	O
33	this	O	O	O
34	that	O	O	O
35	student	O	O	O
36	must	O	O	O
37	survive	O	O	O
38	three	O	O	O
39	tasks	O	O	O
40	.	O	O	O
41	Three	O	O	O
42	extremely	O	O	O
43	dangerous	O	O	O
44	tasks	O	O	O
45	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4121
# text = Wicked.
1	Wicked	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4122
# text = For this reason the ministry has seen fit to impose a new rule. To explain all this we have the head of the department of international magic cooperation Mister Bartimus Crouch.
1	For	O	O	O
2	this	O	O	O
3	reason	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
6	has	O	O	O
7	seen	O	O	O
8	fit	O	O	O
9	to	O	O	O
10	impose	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	new	O	O	O
13	rule	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	To	O	O	O
16	explain	O	O	O
17	all	O	O	O
18	this	O	O	O
19	we	O	O	O
20	have	O	O	O
21	the	O	O	O
22	head	O	O	O
23	of	O	O	O
24	the	O	O	O
25	department	B-ORG	O	O
26	of	B-ORG	O	O
27	international	B-ORG	O	O
28	magic	B-ORG	O	O
29	cooperation	B-ORG	O	O
30	Mister	B-TTL	O	O
31	Bartimus	B-PER	O	O
32	Crouch	I-PER	O	O
33	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4123
# text = Bloody hell, it's Mad-Eye Moody.
1	Bloody	O	O	O
2	hell	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	it	O	O	O
5	's	O	O	O
6	Mad	B-PER	O	O
7	Eye	I-PER	O	O
8	Moody	I-PER	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4124
# text = Alastor Moody? The auror.
1	Alastor	B-PER	O	O
2	Moody	I-PER	O	O
3	?	O	O	O
4	The	O	O	O
5	auror	B-TTL	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4125
# text = He was a catcher. Half the cells in Azkaban are full thanks to him. He's supposed to be mad as a hatter though these days.
1	He	O	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	catcher	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Half	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	cells	O	O	O
9	in	O	O	O
10	Azkaban	B-LOC	O	O
11	are	O	O	O
12	full	O	O	O
13	thanks	O	O	O
14	to	O	O	O
15	him	O	O	O
16	.	O	O	O
17	He	O	O	O
18	's	O	O	O
19	supposed	O	O	O
20	to	O	O	O
21	be	O	O	O
22	mad	O	O	O
23	as	O	O	O
24	a	O	O	O
25	hatter	O	O	O
26	though	O	O	O
27	these	O	O	O
28	days	O	O	O
29	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4126
# text = My dear old friend, thanks for coming.
1	My	O	O	O
2	dear	O	O	O
3	old	O	O	O
4	friend	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	thanks	O	O	O
7	for	O	O	O
8	coming	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4127
# text = That stupid roof.
1	That	O	O	O
2	stupid	O	O	O
3	roof	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4128
# text = What's that he's drinking do you suppose?
1	What	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	he	O	O	O
5	's	O	O	O
6	drinking	O	O	O
7	do	O	O	O
8	you	O	O	O
9	suppose	O	O	O
10	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4129
# text = I don't know but I don't think it's Pumpkin Juice.
1	I	O	O	O
2	do	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	know	O	O	O
5	but	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	do	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	think	O	O	O
10	it	O	O	O
11	's	O	O	O
12	Pumpkin	O	O	O
13	Juice	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4130
# text = After much deliberation the ministry has concluded that for their own safety no student under the age of seventeen shall be allowed to put forth their name for the tri-wizard tournament. This decision is final.
1	After	O	O	O
2	much	O	O	O
3	deliberation	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
6	has	O	O	O
7	concluded	O	O	O
8	that	O	O	O
9	for	O	O	O
10	their	O	O	O
11	own	O	O	O
12	safety	O	O	O
13	no	O	O	O
14	student	O	O	O
15	under	O	O	O
16	the	O	O	O
17	age	O	O	O
18	of	O	O	O
19	seventeen	O	O	O
20	shall	O	O	O
21	be	O	O	O
22	allowed	O	O	O
23	to	O	O	O
24	put	O	O	O
25	forth	O	O	O
26	their	O	O	O
27	name	O	O	O
28	for	O	O	O
29	the	O	O	O
30	tri	B-EVN	O	O
31	wizard	I-EVN	O	O
32	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
33	.	O	O	O
34	This	O	O	O
35	decision	O	O	O
36	is	O	O	O
37	final	O	O	O
38	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4131
# text = That's rubbish! You don't know what you're doing!
1	That	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	rubbish	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O
5	You	O	O	O
6	do	O	O	O
7	n't	O	O	O
8	know	O	O	O
9	what	O	O	O
10	you	O	O	O
11	're	O	O	O
12	doing	O	O	O
13	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4132
# text = Silence!
1	Silence	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4133
# text = The goblet of fire. Anyone wishing to submit themselves for the tournament merely write their name upon a piece of parchment and throw it in the flame before this hour on Thursday night. Do not do so lightly, if choosen there's no turning back. As from this moment the tri-wizard tournament has begun.
1	The	O	O	O
2	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
3	of	I-MIT	O	O
4	fire	I-MIT	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Anyone	O	O	O
7	wishing	O	O	O
8	to	O	O	O
9	submit	O	O	O
10	themselves	O	O	O
11	for	O	O	O
12	the	O	O	O
13	tournament	B-EVN	O	O
14	merely	O	O	O
15	write	O	O	O
16	their	O	O	O
17	name	O	O	O
18	upon	O	O	O
19	a	O	O	O
20	piece	O	O	O
21	of	O	O	O
22	parchment	O	O	O
23	and	O	O	O
24	throw	O	O	O
25	it	O	O	O
26	in	O	O	O
27	the	O	O	O
28	flame	O	O	O
29	before	O	O	O
30	this	O	O	O
31	hour	O	O	O
32	on	O	O	O
33	Thursday	O	O	O
34	night	O	O	O
35	.	O	O	O
36	Do	O	O	O
37	not	O	O	O
38	do	O	O	O
39	so	O	O	O
40	lightly	O	O	O
41	,	O	O	O
42	if	O	O	O
43	choosen	O	O	O
44	there	O	O	O
45	's	O	O	O
46	no	O	O	O
47	turning	O	O	O
48	back	O	O	O
49	.	O	O	O
50	As	O	O	O
51	from	O	O	O
52	this	O	O	O
53	moment	O	O	O
54	the	O	O	O
55	tri	B-EVN	O	O
56	wizard	I-EVN	O	O
57	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
58	has	O	O	O
59	begun	O	O	O
60	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4134
# text = Alastor Moody.
1	Alastor	B-PER	O	O
2	Moody	I-PER	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4135
# text = Ministry malcontent. And your new defence against the dark arts teacher. I'm here because Dumbledore asked me, end of story, goodbye, the end. Any questions? When it comes to the dark arts, I believe in a practical approach. But first, which of you can tell me how many unforgivable curses there are?
1	Ministry	O	O	O
2	malcontent	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	And	O	O	O
5	your	O	O	O
6	new	O	O	O
7	defence	B-CRS	O	O
8	against	B-CRS	O	O
9	the	B-CRS	O	O
10	dark	B-CRS	O	O
11	arts	B-CRS	O	O
12	teacher	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	I	O	O	O
15	'm	O	O	O
16	here	O	O	O
17	because	O	O	O
18	Dumbledore	B-PER	O	O
19	asked	O	O	O
20	me	O	O	O
21	,	O	O	O
22	end	O	O	O
23	of	O	O	O
24	story	O	O	O
25	,	O	O	O
26	goodbye	O	O	O
27	,	O	O	O
28	the	O	O	O
29	end	O	O	O
30	.	O	O	O
31	Any	O	O	O
32	questions	O	O	O
33	?	O	O	O
34	When	O	O	O
35	it	O	O	O
36	comes	O	O	O
37	to	O	O	O
38	the	O	O	O
39	dark	O	O	O
40	arts	O	O	O
41	,	O	O	O
42	I	O	O	O
43	believe	O	O	O
44	in	O	O	O
45	a	O	O	O
46	practical	O	O	O
47	approach	O	O	O
48	.	O	O	O
49	But	O	O	O
50	first	O	O	O
51	,	O	O	O
52	which	O	O	O
53	of	O	O	O
54	you	O	O	O
55	can	O	O	O
56	tell	O	O	O
57	me	O	O	O
58	how	O	O	O
59	many	O	O	O
60	unforgivable	B-SPL	O	O
61	curses	I-SPL	O	O
62	there	O	O	O
63	are	O	O	O
64	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4136
# text = Three sir.
1	Three	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4137
# text = And they are so named?
1	And	O	O	O
2	they	O	O	O
3	are	O	O	O
4	so	O	O	O
5	named	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4138
# text = Because they are unforgivable. Use of any one of them will...
1	Because	O	O	O
2	they	O	O	O
3	are	O	O	O
4	unforgivable	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Use	O	O	O
7	of	O	O	O
8	any	O	O	O
9	one	O	O	O
10	of	O	O	O
11	them	O	O	O
12	will	O	O	O
13	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4139
# text = Will earn you a one way ticket to Azkaban. Correct. Now the ministry says you're too young to see what these curses do. I say different! You need to know what you're up against, you need to be prepared, you need to find somewhere else to put your chewing gum other than the underside of your desk Mr Finnigan!
1	Will	O	O	O
2	earn	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	one	O	O	O
6	way	O	O	O
7	ticket	O	O	O
8	to	O	O	O
9	Azkaban	B-LOC	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	Correct	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O
13	Now	O	O	O
14	the	O	O	O
15	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
16	says	O	O	O
17	you	O	O	O
18	're	O	O	O
19	too	O	O	O
20	young	O	O	O
21	to	O	O	O
22	see	O	O	O
23	what	O	O	O
24	these	O	O	O
25	curses	O	O	O
26	do	O	O	O
27	.	O	O	O
28	I	O	O	O
29	say	O	O	O
30	different	O	O	O
31	!	O	O	O
32	You	O	O	O
33	need	O	O	O
34	to	O	O	O
35	know	O	O	O
36	what	O	O	O
37	you	O	O	O
38	're	O	O	O
39	up	O	O	O
40	against	O	O	O
41	,	O	O	O
42	you	O	O	O
43	need	O	O	O
44	to	O	O	O
45	be	O	O	O
46	prepared	O	O	O
47	,	O	O	O
48	you	O	O	O
49	need	O	O	O
50	to	O	O	O
51	find	O	O	O
52	somewhere	O	O	O
53	else	O	O	O
54	to	O	O	O
55	put	O	O	O
56	your	O	O	O
57	chewing	O	O	O
58	gum	O	O	O
59	other	O	O	O
60	than	O	O	O
61	the	O	O	O
62	underside	O	O	O
63	of	O	O	O
64	your	O	O	O
65	desk	O	O	O
66	Mr	B-TTL	O	O
67	Finnigan	B-PER	O	O
68	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4140
# text = Aw no way, the old codger can see out the back of his head.
1	Aw	O	O	O
2	no	O	O	O
3	way	O	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	old	O	O	O
7	codger	O	O	O
8	can	O	O	O
9	see	O	O	O
10	out	O	O	O
11	the	O	O	O
12	back	O	O	O
13	of	O	O	O
14	his	O	O	O
15	head	O	O	O
16	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4141
# text = So, which curse shall we see first?
1	So	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	which	O	O	O
4	curse	O	O	O
5	shall	O	O	O
6	we	O	O	O
7	see	O	O	O
8	first	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4142
# text = Yes...
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4143
# text = Give us a curse.
1	Give	O	O	O
2	us	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	curse	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4144
# text = Well, my dad did tell me about one... The imperious curse.
1	Well	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	my	O	O	O
4	dad	O	O	O
5	did	O	O	O
6	tell	O	O	O
7	me	O	O	O
8	about	O	O	O
9	one	O	O	O
10	...	O	O	O
11	The	O	O	O
12	imperious	B-SPL	O	O
13	curse	I-SPL	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4145
# text = Ahhh yes, your father would know all about that. Gave the ministry quite a bit of grief a few years ago. Perhaps this will show you why.
1	Ahhh	O	O	O
2	yes	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	your	O	O	O
5	father	O	O	O
6	would	O	O	O
7	know	O	O	O
8	all	O	O	O
9	about	O	O	O
10	that	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	Gave	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
15	quite	O	O	O
16	a	O	O	O
17	bit	O	O	O
18	of	O	O	O
19	grief	O	O	O
20	a	O	O	O
21	few	O	O	O
22	years	O	O	O
23	ago	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O
25	Perhaps	O	O	O
26	this	O	O	O
27	will	O	O	O
28	show	O	O	O
29	you	O	O	O
30	why	O	O	O
31	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4146
# text = Hello. What a little beauty.
1	Hello	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	What	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	little	O	O	O
6	beauty	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4147
# text = Don't worry. Completely harmless.
1	Do	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	worry	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Completely	O	O	O
6	harmless	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4148
# text = But if she bites... she's lethal!
1	But	O	O	O
2	if	O	O	O
3	she	O	O	O
4	bites	O	O	O
5	...	O	O	O
6	she	O	O	O
7	's	O	O	O
8	lethal	O	O	O
9	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4149
# text = What are you laughing at?
1	What	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	laughing	O	O	O
5	at	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4150
# text = Talented isn't she? What shall I have her do next? Jump out the window? Drown herself?
1	Talented	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	she	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O
6	What	O	O	O
7	shall	O	O	O
8	I	O	O	O
9	have	O	O	O
10	her	O	O	O
11	do	O	O	O
12	next	O	O	O
13	?	O	O	O
14	Jump	O	O	O
15	out	O	O	O
16	the	O	O	O
17	window	O	O	O
18	?	O	O	O
19	Drown	O	O	O
20	herself	O	O	O
21	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4151
# text = Scores of witches and wizards have claimed that they only do did you-know-whose bidding under the influence of the imperious curse. But here's the rub, how do we sort out the liars? Another.. another.. Come on come on. Longbottom is it? Up.
1	Scores	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	witches	O	O	O
4	and	O	O	O
5	wizards	O	O	O
6	have	O	O	O
7	claimed	O	O	O
8	that	O	O	O
9	they	O	O	O
10	only	O	O	O
11	do	O	O	O
12	did	O	O	O
13	you	O	O	O
14	know	O	O	O
15	whose	O	O	O
16	bidding	O	O	O
17	under	O	O	O
18	the	O	O	O
19	influence	O	O	O
20	of	O	O	O
21	the	O	O	O
22	imperious	B-SPL	O	O
23	curse	I-SPL	O	O
24	.	O	O	O
25	But	O	O	O
26	here	O	O	O
27	's	O	O	O
28	the	O	O	O
29	rub	O	O	O
30	,	O	O	O
31	how	O	O	O
32	do	O	O	O
33	we	O	O	O
34	sort	O	O	O
35	out	O	O	O
36	the	O	O	O
37	liars	O	O	O
38	?	O	O	O
39	Another	O	O	O
40	.	O	O	O
41	.	O	O	O
42	another	O	O	O
43	.	O	O	O
44	.	O	O	O
45	Come	O	O	O
46	on	O	O	O
47	come	O	O	O
48	on	O	O	O
49	.	O	O	O
50	Longbottom	B-PER	O	O
51	is	O	O	O
52	it	O	O	O
53	?	O	O	O
54	Up	O	O	O
55	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4152
# text = Professor Sprout tells me you have an aptitude for herbology.
1	Professor	B-TTL	O	O
2	Sprout	B-PER	O	O
3	tells	O	O	O
4	me	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	have	O	O	O
7	an	O	O	O
8	aptitude	O	O	O
9	for	O	O	O
10	herbology	B-CRS	O	O
11	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4153
# text = There's the um... The cruciatus curse.
1	There	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	um	O	O	O
5	...	O	O	O
6	The	O	O	O
7	cruciatus	B-SPL	O	O
8	curse	B-SPL	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4154
# text = Correct! Correct! come come. Particularly nasty. The torture curse.
1	Correct	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	Correct	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O
5	come	O	O	O
6	come	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Particularly	O	O	O
9	nasty	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	The	O	O	O
12	torture	O	O	O
13	curse	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4155
# text = Stop it! Can't you see it's bothering him, stop it!
1	Stop	O	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	Ca	O	O	O
5	n't	O	O	O
6	you	O	O	O
7	see	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	's	O	O	O
10	bothering	O	O	O
11	him	O	O	O
12	,	O	O	O
13	stop	O	O	O
14	it	O	O	O
15	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4156
# text = Perhaps you could give us the last unforgivable curse Miss Granger.
1	Perhaps	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	could	O	O	O
4	give	O	O	O
5	us	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	last	O	O	O
8	unforgivable	B-SPL	O	O
9	curse	B-SPL	O	O
10	Miss	B-TTL	O	O
11	Granger	B-PER	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4157
# text = The killing curse. Only one person is known to have survived it. And he's sitting in this room.
1	The	O	O	O
2	killing	B-SPL	O	O
3	curse	B-SPL	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Only	O	O	O
6	one	O	O	O
7	person	O	O	O
8	is	O	O	O
9	known	O	O	O
10	to	O	O	O
11	have	O	O	O
12	survived	O	O	O
13	it	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	And	O	O	O
16	he	O	O	O
17	's	O	O	O
18	sitting	O	O	O
19	in	O	O	O
20	this	O	O	O
21	room	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4158
# text = Brilliant isn't he! Completely demented of course. Terrifying to be in the same room with, he's really BEEN there you know.
1	Brilliant	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	he	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O
6	Completely	O	O	O
7	demented	O	O	O
8	of	O	O	O
9	course	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	Terrifying	O	O	O
12	to	O	O	O
13	be	O	O	O
14	in	O	O	O
15	the	O	O	O
16	same	O	O	O
17	room	O	O	O
18	with	O	O	O
19	,	O	O	O
20	he	O	O	O
21	's	O	O	O
22	really	O	O	O
23	BEEN	O	O	O
24	there	O	O	O
25	you	O	O	O
26	know	O	O	O
27	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4159
# text = There's a reason those curses are unforgivable, and to perform them in a classroom. I mean did you see Neville's face.
1	There	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	reason	O	O	O
5	those	O	O	O
6	curses	O	O	O
7	are	O	O	O
8	unforgivable	O	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	and	O	O	O
11	to	O	O	O
12	perform	O	O	O
13	them	O	O	O
14	in	O	O	O
15	a	O	O	O
16	classroom	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O
18	I	O	O	O
19	mean	O	O	O
20	did	O	O	O
21	you	O	O	O
22	see	O	O	O
23	Neville	B-PER	O	O
24	's	O	O	O
25	face	O	O	O
26	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4160
# text = Neville?
1	Neville	B-PER	O	O
2	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4161
# text = Son. You alright?
1	Son	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	You	O	O	O
4	alright	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4162
# text = Come on, we'll have a cup of tea. I want to show you something.
1	Come	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	we	O	O	O
5	'll	O	O	O
6	have	O	O	O
7	a	O	O	O
8	cup	O	O	O
9	of	O	O	O
10	tea	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	I	O	O	O
13	want	O	O	O
14	to	O	O	O
15	show	O	O	O
16	you	O	O	O
17	something	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4163
# text = Eternal glory, be brilliant wouldn't it? In three years from now we'll be old enough to be choosen.
1	Eternal	O	O	O
2	glory	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	be	O	O	O
5	brilliant	O	O	O
6	would	O	O	O
7	n't	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O
10	In	O	O	O
11	three	O	O	O
12	years	O	O	O
13	from	O	O	O
14	now	O	O	O
15	we	O	O	O
16	'll	O	O	O
17	be	O	O	O
18	old	O	O	O
19	enough	O	O	O
20	to	O	O	O
21	be	O	O	O
22	choosen	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4164
# text = Yeah well rather you than me.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	well	O	O	O
3	rather	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	than	O	O	O
6	me	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4165
# text = Thank you thank you, well lads we've done it.
1	Thank	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	thank	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	well	O	O	O
7	lads	O	O	O
8	we	O	O	O
9	've	O	O	O
10	done	O	O	O
11	it	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4166
# text = Cooked it up just this morning.
1	Cooked	O	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	up	O	O	O
4	just	O	O	O
5	this	O	O	O
6	morning	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4167
# text = It's not going to work.
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	not	O	O	O
4	going	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	work	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4168
# text = Oh yeah? And why's that Granger.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	yeah	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O
4	And	O	O	O
5	why	O	O	O
6	's	O	O	O
7	that	O	O	O
8	Granger	B-PER	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4169
# text = You see this? This is an age line. Dumbledore drew it himself.
1	You	O	O	O
2	see	O	O	O
3	this	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O
5	This	O	O	O
6	is	O	O	O
7	an	O	O	O
8	age	O	O	O
9	line	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	Dumbledore	B-PER	O	O
12	drew	O	O	O
13	it	O	O	O
14	himself	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4170
# text = So?
1	So	O	O	O
2	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4171
# text = So a genius like Dumbledore couldn't possibly be fooled by something pathetically dimwitted such as an age potion.
1	So	O	O	O
2	a	O	O	O
3	genius	O	O	O
4	like	O	O	O
5	Dumbledore	B-PER	O	O
6	could	O	O	O
7	n't	O	O	O
8	possibly	O	O	O
9	be	O	O	O
10	fooled	O	O	O
11	by	O	O	O
12	something	O	O	O
13	pathetically	O	O	O
14	dimwitted	O	O	O
15	such	O	O	O
16	as	O	O	O
17	an	O	O	O
18	age	O	O	O
19	potion	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4172
# text = That's why it's so brilliant.
1	That	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	why	O	O	O
4	it	O	O	O
5	's	O	O	O
6	so	O	O	O
7	brilliant	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4173
# text = Ready Fred?
1	Ready	O	O	O
2	Fred	B-PER	O	O
3	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4174
# text = Ready George?
1	Ready	O	O	O
2	George	B-PER	O	O
3	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4175
# text = You said..
1	You	O	O	O
2	said	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4176
# text = Sit down please. And now the moment you've all been waiting for, the champions selection!
1	Sit	O	O	O
2	down	O	O	O
3	please	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	And	O	O	O
6	now	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	moment	O	O	O
9	you	O	O	O
10	've	O	O	O
11	all	O	O	O
12	been	O	O	O
13	waiting	O	O	O
14	for	O	O	O
15	,	O	O	O
16	the	O	O	O
17	champions	B-TTL	O	O
18	selection	O	O	O
19	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4177
# text = The Durmstrang champion is ... Viktor Krum!
1	The	O	O	O
2	Durmstrang	B-ORG	O	O
3	champion	B-TTL	O	O
4	is	O	O	O
5	...	O	O	O
6	Viktor	B-PER	O	O
7	Krum	I-PER	O	O
8	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4178
# text = The champion from Beauxbatons... Fleur Delacour
1	The	O	O	O
2	champion	B-TTL	O	O
3	from	O	O	O
4	Beauxbatons	B-ORG	O	O
5	...	O	O	O
6	Fleur	B-PER	O	O
7	Delacour	I-PER	O	O

# sent_id = 4179
# text = The Hogwarts champion... Cedric Diggory.
1	The	O	O	O
2	Hogwarts	B-ORG	O	O
3	champion	B-TTL	O	O
4	...	O	O	O
5	Cedric	B-PER	O	O
6	Diggory	I-PER	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4180
# text = Excellent! we now have our three champions! But in the end only one will go down in history. Only one will hoist this chalice of champions, this vessel of victory the tri-wizard cup!
1	Excellent	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	we	O	O	O
4	now	O	O	O
5	have	O	O	O
6	our	O	O	O
7	three	O	O	O
8	champions	B-TTL	O	O
9	!	O	O	O
10	But	O	O	O
11	in	O	O	O
12	the	O	O	O
13	end	O	O	O
14	only	O	O	O
15	one	O	O	O
16	will	O	O	O
17	go	O	O	O
18	down	O	O	O
19	in	O	O	O
20	history	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O
22	Only	O	O	O
23	one	O	O	O
24	will	O	O	O
25	hoist	O	O	O
26	this	O	O	O
27	chalice	O	O	O
28	of	O	O	O
29	champions	O	O	O
30	,	O	O	O
31	this	O	O	O
32	vessel	O	O	O
33	of	O	O	O
34	victory	O	O	O
35	the	O	O	O
36	tri	B-MIT	O	O
37	wizard	I-MIT	O	O
38	cup	I-MIT	O	O
39	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4181
# text = Harry Potter. Harry Potter?
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	Potter	I-PER	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	Harry	B-PER	O	O
5	Potter	I-PER	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4182
# text = No... No.
1	No	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O
3	No	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4183
# text = Harry Potter!
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	Potter	I-PER	O	O
3	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4184
# text = Go on Harry. Harry for goodness sake.
1	Go	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	Harry	B-PER	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Harry	B-PER	O	O
6	for	O	O	O
7	goodness	O	O	O
8	sake	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4185
# text = He's a cheat! He's not even seventeen yet.
1	He	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	cheat	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O
6	He	O	O	O
7	's	O	O	O
8	not	O	O	O
9	even	O	O	O
10	seventeen	O	O	O
11	yet	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4186
# text = Harry! Did you put your name in the goblet of fire?
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	Did	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	put	O	O	O
6	your	O	O	O
7	name	O	O	O
8	in	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
11	of	I-MIT	O	O
12	fire	I-MIT	O	O
13	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4187
# text = No sir.
1	No	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4188
# text = Did you ask one of the older students to do it for you?
1	Did	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	ask	O	O	O
4	one	O	O	O
5	of	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	older	O	O	O
8	students	O	O	O
9	to	O	O	O
10	do	O	O	O
11	it	O	O	O
12	for	O	O	O
13	you	O	O	O
14	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4189
# text = No sir.
1	No	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4190
# text = You're absolutely sure?
1	You	O	O	O
2	're	O	O	O
3	absolutely	O	O	O
4	sure	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4191
# text = Yes sir.
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	sir	B-TTL	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4192
# text = Well of course he is lying.
1	Well	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	course	O	O	O
4	he	O	O	O
5	is	O	O	O
6	lying	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4193
# text = The hell he is. The goblet of fire is an exceptionally powerful magical object, only an exceptionally powerful conjurer could have hoodwinked it. Magic way beyond the talents of a fourth year.
1	The	O	O	O
2	hell	O	O	O
3	he	O	O	O
4	is	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	The	O	O	O
7	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
8	of	I-MIT	O	O
9	fire	I-MIT	O	O
10	is	O	O	O
11	an	O	O	O
12	exceptionally	O	O	O
13	powerful	O	O	O
14	magical	O	O	O
15	object	O	O	O
16	,	O	O	O
17	only	O	O	O
18	an	O	O	O
19	exceptionally	O	O	O
20	powerful	O	O	O
21	conjurer	O	O	O
22	could	O	O	O
23	have	O	O	O
24	hoodwinked	O	O	O
25	it	O	O	O
26	.	O	O	O
27	Magic	O	O	O
28	way	O	O	O
29	beyond	O	O	O
30	the	O	O	O
31	talents	O	O	O
32	of	O	O	O
33	a	O	O	O
34	fourth	O	O	O
35	year	O	O	O
36	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4194
# text = You seem to have given this a fair bit of thought Mad-Eye.
1	You	O	O	O
2	seem	O	O	O
3	to	O	O	O
4	have	O	O	O
5	given	O	O	O
6	this	O	O	O
7	a	O	O	O
8	fair	O	O	O
9	bit	O	O	O
10	of	O	O	O
11	thought	O	O	O
12	Mad	B-PER	O	O
13	Eye	I-PER	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4195
# text = It was once my job to think as dark wizards do Karkaroff perhaps you remember?
1	It	O	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	once	O	O	O
4	my	O	O	O
5	job	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	think	O	O	O
8	as	O	O	O
9	dark	O	O	O
10	wizards	O	O	O
11	do	O	O	O
12	Karkaroff	B-PER	O	O
13	perhaps	O	O	O
14	you	O	O	O
15	remember	O	O	O
16	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4196
# text = That doesn't help Alastor. Leave this to you Barty.
1	That	O	O	O
2	does	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	help	O	O	O
5	Alastor	B-PER	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	Leave	O	O	O
8	this	O	O	O
9	to	O	O	O
10	you	O	O	O
11	Barty	B-PER	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4197
# text = The rules are absolute, the goblet of fire constitutes a binding magical contract. Mr Potter has no choice, he is as of tonight... a tri-wizards champion.
1	The	O	O	O
2	rules	O	O	O
3	are	O	O	O
4	absolute	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	the	O	O	O
7	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
8	of	I-MIT	O	O
9	fire	I-MIT	O	O
10	constitutes	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	binding	O	O	O
13	magical	O	O	O
14	contract	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O
16	Mr	B-TTL	O	O
17	Potter	B-PER	O	O
18	has	O	O	O
19	no	O	O	O
20	choice	O	O	O
21	,	O	O	O
22	he	O	O	O
23	is	O	O	O
24	as	O	O	O
25	of	O	O	O
26	tonight	O	O	O
27	...	O	O	O
28	a	O	O	O
29	tri	B-TTL	O	O
30	wizards	I-TTL	O	O
31	champion	I-TTL	O	O
32	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4198
# text = This can't go on Albus. First the dark mark, now this?
1	This	O	O	O
2	ca	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	go	O	O	O
5	on	O	O	O
6	Albus	B-PER	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	First	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	dark	B-MIT	O	O
11	mark	I-MIT	O	O
12	,	O	O	O
13	now	O	O	O
14	this	O	O	O
15	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4199
# text = What do you suggest Minerva?
1	What	O	O	O
2	do	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	suggest	O	O	O
5	Minerva	B-PER	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4200
# text = Put an end to it. Don't let Potter compete.
1	Put	O	O	O
2	an	O	O	O
3	end	O	O	O
4	to	O	O	O
5	it	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	Do	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	let	O	O	O
10	Potter	B-PER	O	O
11	compete	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4201
# text = You heard Barty the rules are clear.
1	You	O	O	O
2	heard	O	O	O
3	Barty	B-PER	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	rules	O	O	O
6	are	O	O	O
7	clear	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4202
# text = Well the devil with Barty and his rules. And since when did you accomodate them...
1	Well	O	O	O
2	the	O	O	O
3	devil	O	O	O
4	with	O	O	O
5	Barty	B-PER	O	O
6	and	O	O	O
7	his	O	O	O
8	rules	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	And	O	O	O
11	since	O	O	O
12	when	O	O	O
13	did	O	O	O
14	you	O	O	O
15	accomodate	O	O	O
16	them	O	O	O
17	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4203
# text = Master I too find it difficult to believe this mere coincidence, if we are to truly discover the meaning of these events perhaps we should for the time being let them unfold.
1	Master	B-TTL	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	too	O	O	O
4	find	O	O	O
5	it	O	O	O
6	difficult	O	O	O
7	to	O	O	O
8	believe	O	O	O
9	this	O	O	O
10	mere	O	O	O
11	coincidence	O	O	O
12	,	O	O	O
13	if	O	O	O
14	we	O	O	O
15	are	O	O	O
16	to	O	O	O
17	truly	O	O	O
18	discover	O	O	O
19	the	O	O	O
20	meaning	O	O	O
21	of	O	O	O
22	these	O	O	O
23	events	O	O	O
24	perhaps	O	O	O
25	we	O	O	O
26	should	O	O	O
27	for	O	O	O
28	the	O	O	O
29	time	O	O	O
30	being	O	O	O
31	let	O	O	O
32	them	O	O	O
33	unfold	O	O	O
34	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4204
# text = Do nothing?? Offer him up as bait? Potter is a boy not a piece of meat.
1	Do	O	O	O
2	nothing	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O
5	Offer	O	O	O
6	him	O	O	O
7	up	O	O	O
8	as	O	O	O
9	bait	O	O	O
10	?	O	O	O
11	Potter	B-PER	O	O
12	is	O	O	O
13	a	O	O	O
14	boy	O	O	O
15	not	O	O	O
16	a	O	O	O
17	piece	O	O	O
18	of	O	O	O
19	meat	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4205
# text = I agree with Severus. Alastor, keep an eye on Harry will you?
1	I	O	O	O
2	agree	O	O	O
3	with	O	O	O
4	Severus	B-PER	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Alastor	B-PER	O	O
7	,	O	O	O
8	keep	O	O	O
9	an	O	O	O
10	eye	O	O	O
11	on	O	O	O
12	Harry	B-PER	O	O
13	will	O	O	O
14	you	O	O	O
15	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4206
# text = I can do that.
1	I	O	O	O
2	can	O	O	O
3	do	O	O	O
4	that	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4207
# text = Don't let him know though, he must be anxious enough as it is... knowing what lies ahead. Then again, we all are.
1	Do	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	let	O	O	O
4	him	O	O	O
5	know	O	O	O
6	though	O	O	O
7	,	O	O	O
8	he	O	O	O
9	must	O	O	O
10	be	O	O	O
11	anxious	O	O	O
12	enough	O	O	O
13	as	O	O	O
14	it	O	O	O
15	is	O	O	O
16	...	O	O	O
17	knowing	O	O	O
18	what	O	O	O
19	lies	O	O	O
20	ahead	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O
22	Then	O	O	O
23	again	O	O	O
24	,	O	O	O
25	we	O	O	O
26	all	O	O	O
27	are	O	O	O
28	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4208
# text = How did you do it?
1	How	O	O	O
2	did	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	do	O	O	O
5	it	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4209
# text = Never mind. Doesn't matter. You could have let your best friend know though.
1	Never	O	O	O
2	mind	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	Does	O	O	O
5	n't	O	O	O
6	matter	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	You	O	O	O
9	could	O	O	O
10	have	O	O	O
11	let	O	O	O
12	your	O	O	O
13	best	O	O	O
14	friend	O	O	O
15	know	O	O	O
16	though	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4210
# text = Let you know what?
1	Let	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	know	O	O	O
4	what	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4211
# text = You know bloody well what.
1	You	O	O	O
2	know	O	O	O
3	bloody	O	O	O
4	well	O	O	O
5	what	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4212
# text = I didn't ask for this to happen Ron. Okay? You're being stupid.
1	I	O	O	O
2	did	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	ask	O	O	O
5	for	O	O	O
6	this	O	O	O
7	to	O	O	O
8	happen	O	O	O
9	Ron	B-PER	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	Okay	O	O	O
12	?	O	O	O
13	You	O	O	O
14	're	O	O	O
15	being	O	O	O
16	stupid	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4213
# text = Yeah that's me, Ron Weasley... Harry Potter's stupid friend.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	that	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	me	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	Ron	B-PER	O	O
7	Weasley	I-PER	O	O
8	...	O	O	O
9	Harry	B-PER	O	O
10	Potter	I-PER	O	O
11	's	O	O	O
12	stupid	O	O	O
13	friend	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4214
# text = I didn't put my name in that cup. I don't want eternal glory I just wanna be.. Look, I don't know what happened tonight and I don't know why, it just did ok.
1	I	O	O	O
2	did	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	put	O	O	O
5	my	O	O	O
6	name	O	O	O
7	in	O	O	O
8	that	O	O	O
9	cup	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	I	O	O	O
12	do	O	O	O
13	n't	O	O	O
14	want	O	O	O
15	eternal	O	O	O
16	glory	O	O	O
17	I	O	O	O
18	just	O	O	O
19	wanna	O	O	O
20	be	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O
23	Look	O	O	O
24	,	O	O	O
25	I	O	O	O
26	do	O	O	O
27	n't	O	O	O
28	know	O	O	O
29	what	O	O	O
30	happened	O	O	O
31	tonight	O	O	O
32	and	O	O	O
33	I	O	O	O
34	do	O	O	O
35	n't	O	O	O
36	know	O	O	O
37	why	O	O	O
38	,	O	O	O
39	it	O	O	O
40	just	O	O	O
41	did	O	O	O
42	ok	O	O	O
43	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4215
# text = Piss off.
1	Piss	O	O	O
2	off	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4216
# text = What a charismatic quartet. Hello!
1	What	O	O	O
2	a	O	O	O
3	charismatic	O	O	O
4	quartet	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Hello	O	O	O
7	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4217
# text = I'm Rita Skeeter, I write for the daily prophet. But of course you know that don't you. It's you we don't know, you're the news. What quirks lurk beneath those rosy cheeks? what mysteries do the muscles mask? does courage lie beneath those curls? In short, what makes a champion tick. Me, myself and I want to know. Not to mention my rabid readers. So, who's feeling up to sharing? Mmm? Shall we start with the youngest. Lovely.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	Rita	B-PER	O	O
4	Skeeter	I-PER	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	write	O	O	O
8	for	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	daily	B-ORG	O	O
11	prophet	I-ORG	O	O
12	.	O	O	O
13	But	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	course	O	O	O
16	you	O	O	O
17	know	O	O	O
18	that	O	O	O
19	do	O	O	O
20	n't	O	O	O
21	you	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O
23	It	O	O	O
24	's	O	O	O
25	you	O	O	O
26	we	O	O	O
27	do	O	O	O
28	n't	O	O	O
29	know	O	O	O
30	,	O	O	O
31	you	O	O	O
32	're	O	O	O
33	the	O	O	O
34	news	O	O	O
35	.	O	O	O
36	What	O	O	O
37	quirks	O	O	O
38	lurk	O	O	O
39	beneath	O	O	O
40	those	O	O	O
41	rosy	O	O	O
42	cheeks	O	O	O
43	?	O	O	O
44	what	O	O	O
45	mysteries	O	O	O
46	do	O	O	O
47	the	O	O	O
48	muscles	O	O	O
49	mask	O	O	O
50	?	O	O	O
51	does	O	O	O
52	courage	O	O	O
53	lie	O	O	O
54	beneath	O	O	O
55	those	O	O	O
56	curls	O	O	O
57	?	O	O	O
58	In	O	O	O
59	short	O	O	O
60	,	O	O	O
61	what	O	O	O
62	makes	O	O	O
63	a	O	O	O
64	champion	B-TTL	O	O
65	tick	O	O	O
66	.	O	O	O
67	Me	O	O	O
68	,	O	O	O
69	myself	O	O	O
70	and	O	O	O
71	I	O	O	O
72	want	O	O	O
73	to	O	O	O
74	know	O	O	O
75	.	O	O	O
76	Not	O	O	O
77	to	O	O	O
78	mention	O	O	O
79	my	O	O	O
80	rabid	O	O	O
81	readers	O	O	O
82	.	O	O	O
83	So	O	O	O
84	,	O	O	O
85	who	O	O	O
86	's	O	O	O
87	feeling	O	O	O
88	up	O	O	O
89	to	O	O	O
90	sharing	O	O	O
91	?	O	O	O
92	Mmm	O	O	O
93	?	O	O	O
94	Shall	O	O	O
95	we	O	O	O
96	start	O	O	O
97	with	O	O	O
98	the	O	O	O
99	youngest	O	O	O
100	.	O	O	O
101	Lovely	O	O	O
102	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4218
# text = This is cosy.
1	This	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	cosy	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4219
# text = It's a broomcupboard.
1	It	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	broomcupboard	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4220
# text = You should feel right at home then. Don't mind if I use the quill do you?
1	You	O	O	O
2	should	O	O	O
3	feel	O	O	O
4	right	O	O	O
5	at	O	O	O
6	home	O	O	O
7	then	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Do	O	O	O
10	n't	O	O	O
11	mind	O	O	O
12	if	O	O	O
13	I	O	O	O
14	use	O	O	O
15	the	O	O	O
16	quill	O	O	O
17	do	O	O	O
18	you	O	O	O
19	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4221
# text = Oh, no.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	no	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4222
# text = So Harry, here you sit, a mere boy of twelve..
1	So	O	O	O
2	Harry	B-PER	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	here	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	sit	O	O	O
7	,	O	O	O
8	a	O	O	O
9	mere	O	O	O
10	boy	O	O	O
11	of	O	O	O
12	twelve	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4223
# text = I'm fourteen.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	fourteen	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4224
# text = ...about to compete against three students. Not only vastly more emotionally mature than yourself but have mastered spells that you wouldn't attempt in your dizziest daydreams. Concerned?
1	...	O	O	O
2	about	O	O	O
3	to	O	O	O
4	compete	O	O	O
5	against	O	O	O
6	three	O	O	O
7	students	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Not	O	O	O
10	only	O	O	O
11	vastly	O	O	O
12	more	O	O	O
13	emotionally	O	O	O
14	mature	O	O	O
15	than	O	O	O
16	yourself	O	O	O
17	but	O	O	O
18	have	O	O	O
19	mastered	O	O	O
20	spells	O	O	O
21	that	O	O	O
22	you	O	O	O
23	would	O	O	O
24	n't	O	O	O
25	attempt	O	O	O
26	in	O	O	O
27	your	O	O	O
28	dizziest	O	O	O
29	daydreams	O	O	O
30	.	O	O	O
31	Concerned	O	O	O
32	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4225
# text = I dunno I haven't really thought about it.
1	I	O	O	O
2	dunno	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	have	O	O	O
5	n't	O	O	O
6	really	O	O	O
7	thought	O	O	O
8	about	O	O	O
9	it	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4226
# text = Course you're not just any ordinary boy of twelve are you...
1	Course	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	not	O	O	O
5	just	O	O	O
6	any	O	O	O
7	ordinary	O	O	O
8	boy	O	O	O
9	of	O	O	O
10	twelve	O	O	O
11	are	O	O	O
12	you	O	O	O
13	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4227
# text = Fourteen.
1	Fourteen	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4228
# text = The story's legend. Do you think it was the trauma of your past that made you so keen to enter such a dangerous tournament.
1	The	O	O	O
2	story	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	legend	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Do	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	think	O	O	O
9	it	O	O	O
10	was	O	O	O
11	the	O	O	O
12	trauma	O	O	O
13	of	O	O	O
14	your	O	O	O
15	past	O	O	O
16	that	O	O	O
17	made	O	O	O
18	you	O	O	O
19	so	O	O	O
20	keen	O	O	O
21	to	O	O	O
22	enter	O	O	O
23	such	O	O	O
24	a	O	O	O
25	dangerous	O	O	O
26	tournament	O	O	O
27	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4229
# text = No I didn't enter.
1	No	O	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	did	O	O	O
4	n't	O	O	O
5	enter	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4230
# text = Course you didn't. Everyone loves a rebel Harry.  Scratch that last. Speaking of your parents, were they alive, how do you think they'd feel? proud? or concerned that your attitude shows at best a pathological need for attention, at worst a psychotic deathwish.
1	Course	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	did	O	O	O
4	n't	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Everyone	O	O	O
7	loves	O	O	O
8	a	O	O	O
9	rebel	O	O	O
10	Harry	B-PER	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	Scratch	O	O	O
13	that	O	O	O
14	last	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O
16	Speaking	O	O	O
17	of	O	O	O
18	your	O	O	O
19	parents	O	O	O
20	,	O	O	O
21	were	O	O	O
22	they	O	O	O
23	alive	O	O	O
24	,	O	O	O
25	how	O	O	O
26	do	O	O	O
27	you	O	O	O
28	think	O	O	O
29	they	O	O	O
30	'd	O	O	O
31	feel	O	O	O
32	?	O	O	O
33	proud	O	O	O
34	?	O	O	O
35	or	O	O	O
36	concerned	O	O	O
37	that	O	O	O
38	your	O	O	O
39	attitude	O	O	O
40	shows	O	O	O
41	at	O	O	O
42	best	O	O	O
43	a	O	O	O
44	pathological	O	O	O
45	need	O	O	O
46	for	O	O	O
47	attention	O	O	O
48	,	O	O	O
49	at	O	O	O
50	worst	O	O	O
51	a	O	O	O
52	psychotic	O	O	O
53	deathwish	O	O	O
54	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4231
# text = Hey, my eyes aren't glistening with the ghosts of my past.
1	Hey	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	my	O	O	O
4	eyes	O	O	O
5	are	O	O	O
6	n't	O	O	O
7	glistening	O	O	O
8	with	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	ghosts	O	O	O
11	of	O	O	O
12	my	O	O	O
13	past	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4232
# text = Harry. I couldn't risk sending Edward. It was since the world cup and the ministry's been intercepting more and more owls and she's too easily recognised. We need to talk Harry. Face to face. Meet me in the Griffindore common room at one o clock this Saturday night and make sure you're alone. P.S....
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	could	O	O	O
5	n't	O	O	O
6	risk	O	O	O
7	sending	O	O	O
8	Edward	B-PER	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	It	O	O	O
11	was	O	O	O
12	since	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	world	O	O	O
15	cup	O	O	O
16	and	O	O	O
17	the	O	O	O
18	ministry	B-ORG	O	O
19	's	O	O	O
20	been	O	O	O
21	intercepting	O	O	O
22	more	O	O	O
23	and	O	O	O
24	more	O	O	O
25	owls	O	O	O
26	and	O	O	O
27	she	O	O	O
28	's	O	O	O
29	too	O	O	O
30	easily	O	O	O
31	recognised	O	O	O
32	.	O	O	O
33	We	O	O	O
34	need	O	O	O
35	to	O	O	O
36	talk	O	O	O
37	Harry	B-PER	O	O
38	.	O	O	O
39	Face	O	O	O
40	to	O	O	O
41	face	O	O	O
42	.	O	O	O
43	Meet	O	O	O
44	me	O	O	O
45	in	O	O	O
46	the	O	O	O
47	Griffindore	B-HOUSE	O	O
48	common	O	O	O
49	room	O	O	O
50	at	O	O	O
51	one	O	O	O
52	o	O	O	O
53	clock	O	O	O
54	this	O	O	O
55	Saturday	O	O	O
56	night	O	O	O
57	and	O	O	O
58	make	O	O	O
59	sure	O	O	O
60	you	O	O	O
61	're	O	O	O
62	alone	O	O	O
63	.	O	O	O
64	P	O	O	O
65	.	O	O	O
66	S	O	O	O
67	...	O	O	O
68	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4233
# text = The bird bites.
1	The	O	O	O
2	bird	O	O	O
3	bites	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4234
# text = Sirius?
1	Sirius	B-PER	O	O
2	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4235
# text = Harry Potter aged 12, suspect entrant in the tri-wizard tournament. His eyes swimming with the ghosts of his...
1	Harry	B-PER	O	O
2	Potter	I-PER	O	O
3	aged	O	O	O
4	12	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	suspect	O	O	O
7	entrant	O	O	O
8	in	O	O	O
9	the	O	O	O
10	tri	B-EVN	O	O
11	wizard	I-EVN	O	O
12	tournament	I-EVN	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	His	O	O	O
15	eyes	O	O	O
16	swimming	O	O	O
17	with	O	O	O
18	the	O	O	O
19	ghosts	O	O	O
20	of	O	O	O
21	his	O	O	O
22	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4236
# text = Sirius?! How...
1	Sirius	B-PER	O	O
2	?	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	How	O	O	O
5	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4237
# text = I don't have much time Harry so let me get straight to it. Did you or did you not put your name into the goblet of fire?
1	I	O	O	O
2	do	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	have	O	O	O
5	much	O	O	O
6	time	O	O	O
7	Harry	B-PER	O	O
8	so	O	O	O
9	let	O	O	O
10	me	O	O	O
11	get	O	O	O
12	straight	O	O	O
13	to	O	O	O
14	it	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O
16	Did	O	O	O
17	you	O	O	O
18	or	O	O	O
19	did	O	O	O
20	you	O	O	O
21	not	O	O	O
22	put	O	O	O
23	your	O	O	O
24	name	O	O	O
25	into	O	O	O
26	the	O	O	O
27	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
28	of	I-MIT	O	O
29	fire	I-MIT	O	O
30	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4238
# text = No!
1	No	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4239
# text = Shh... I had to ask. Now, tell me about this dream of yours. You mentioned Wormtail and Voldemort, but who was the third man in the room?
1	Shh	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	had	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	ask	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Now	O	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	tell	O	O	O
11	me	O	O	O
12	about	O	O	O
13	this	O	O	O
14	dream	O	O	O
15	of	O	O	O
16	yours	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O
18	You	O	O	O
19	mentioned	O	O	O
20	Wormtail	B-PER	O	O
21	and	O	O	O
22	Voldemort	B-PER	O	O
23	,	O	O	O
24	but	O	O	O
25	who	O	O	O
26	was	O	O	O
27	the	O	O	O
28	third	O	O	O
29	man	O	O	O
30	in	O	O	O
31	the	O	O	O
32	room	O	O	O
33	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4240
# text = I dunno.
1	I	O	O	O
2	dunno	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4241
# text = You didn't hear a name?
1	You	O	O	O
2	did	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	hear	O	O	O
5	a	O	O	O
6	name	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4242
# text = No. Umm.. Voldemort was giving him a job to do. Something important.
1	No	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Umm	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Voldemort	B-PER	O	O
7	was	O	O	O
8	giving	O	O	O
9	him	O	O	O
10	a	O	O	O
11	job	O	O	O
12	to	O	O	O
13	do	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	Something	O	O	O
16	important	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4243
# text = What was that?
1	What	O	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4244
# text = He wanted... me. I dunno why, but he was gonna use this man to get to me. I mean it was only a dream right?
1	He	O	O	O
2	wanted	O	O	O
3	...	O	O	O
4	me	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	dunno	O	O	O
8	why	O	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	but	O	O	O
11	he	O	O	O
12	was	O	O	O
13	gonna	O	O	O
14	use	O	O	O
15	this	O	O	O
16	man	O	O	O
17	to	O	O	O
18	get	O	O	O
19	to	O	O	O
20	me	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O
22	I	O	O	O
23	mean	O	O	O
24	it	O	O	O
25	was	O	O	O
26	only	O	O	O
27	a	O	O	O
28	dream	O	O	O
29	right	O	O	O
30	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4245
# text = Yes. It's just a dream. Look Harry, the deatheaters at the world cup, your name rising from that goblet these are not just coincidences. Hogwarts isn't safe any more.
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	It	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	just	O	O	O
6	a	O	O	O
7	dream	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Look	O	O	O
10	Harry	B-PER	O	O
11	,	O	O	O
12	the	O	O	O
13	deatheaters	B-ORG	O	O
14	at	O	O	O
15	the	O	O	O
16	world	O	O	O
17	cup	O	O	O
18	,	O	O	O
19	your	O	O	O
20	name	O	O	O
21	rising	O	O	O
22	from	O	O	O
23	that	O	O	O
24	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
25	these	O	O	O
26	are	O	O	O
27	not	O	O	O
28	just	O	O	O
29	coincidences	O	O	O
30	.	O	O	O
31	Hogwarts	B-ORG	O	O
32	is	O	O	O
33	n't	O	O	O
34	safe	O	O	O
35	any	O	O	O
36	more	O	O	O
37	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4246
# text = What are you saying?
1	What	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	saying	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4247
# text = I'm saying the devils are inside the walls. Igor Karkaroff, he was a deatheater. And no one, no one stops being a deatheater. Then there's Barty Crouch, heart of stone, sent his OWN son to Azkaban.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	saying	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	devils	O	O	O
6	are	O	O	O
7	inside	O	O	O
8	the	O	O	O
9	walls	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	Igor	B-PER	O	O
12	Karkaroff	I-PER	O	O
13	,	O	O	O
14	he	O	O	O
15	was	O	O	O
16	a	O	O	O
17	deatheater	B-ORG	O	O
18	.	O	O	O
19	And	O	O	O
20	no	O	O	O
21	one	O	O	O
22	,	O	O	O
23	no	O	O	O
24	one	O	O	O
25	stops	O	O	O
26	being	O	O	O
27	a	O	O	O
28	deatheater	B-ORG	O	O
29	.	O	O	O
30	Then	O	O	O
31	there	O	O	O
32	's	O	O	O
33	Barty	B-PER	O	O
34	Crouch	I-PER	O	O
35	,	O	O	O
36	heart	O	O	O
37	of	O	O	O
38	stone	O	O	O
39	,	O	O	O
40	sent	O	O	O
41	his	O	O	O
42	OWN	O	O	O
43	son	O	O	O
44	to	O	O	O
45	Azkaban	B-LOC	O	O
46	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4248
# text = Do you think one of them put my name in the goblet?
1	Do	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	think	O	O	O
4	one	O	O	O
5	of	O	O	O
6	them	O	O	O
7	put	O	O	O
8	my	O	O	O
9	name	O	O	O
10	in	O	O	O
11	the	O	O	O
12	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
13	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4249
# text = I haven't a clue who put your name in that goblet Harry but whoever did it is no friend to you. People die in this tournament.
1	I	O	O	O
2	have	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	clue	O	O	O
6	who	O	O	O
7	put	O	O	O
8	your	O	O	O
9	name	O	O	O
10	in	O	O	O
11	that	O	O	O
12	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
13	Harry	B-PER	O	O
14	but	O	O	O
15	whoever	O	O	O
16	did	O	O	O
17	it	O	O	O
18	is	O	O	O
19	no	O	O	O
20	friend	O	O	O
21	to	O	O	O
22	you	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O
24	People	O	O	O
25	die	O	O	O
26	in	O	O	O
27	this	O	O	O
28	tournament	O	O	O
29	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4250
# text = I'm not ready for this Sirius.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	not	O	O	O
4	ready	O	O	O
5	for	O	O	O
6	this	O	O	O
7	Sirius	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4251
# text = You don't have a choice.
1	You	O	O	O
2	do	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	have	O	O	O
5	a	O	O	O
6	choice	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4252
# text = Someone's coming!
1	Someone	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	coming	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4253
# text = Keep your friends close Harry.
1	Keep	O	O	O
2	your	O	O	O
3	friends	O	O	O
4	close	O	O	O
5	Harry	B-PER	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4254
# text = Who you talking to?
1	Who	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	talking	O	O	O
4	to	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4255
# text = Who says I was talking to anyone.
1	Who	O	O	O
2	says	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	was	O	O	O
5	talking	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	anyone	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4256
# text = I heard voices.
1	I	O	O	O
2	heard	O	O	O
3	voices	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4257
# text = Maybe you're imagining things, wouldn't be the first time.
1	Maybe	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	're	O	O	O
4	imagining	O	O	O
5	things	O	O	O
6	,	O	O	O
7	would	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	be	O	O	O
10	the	O	O	O
11	first	O	O	O
12	time	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4258
# text = You're probably just practicing for your next interview I expect.
1	You	O	O	O
2	're	O	O	O
3	probably	O	O	O
4	just	O	O	O
5	practicing	O	O	O
6	for	O	O	O
7	your	O	O	O
8	next	O	O	O
9	interview	O	O	O
10	I	O	O	O
11	expect	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4259
# text = Amazing. Amazing.
1	Amazing	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Amazing	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4260
# text = Neville! You're doing it again!
1	Neville	B-PER	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	You	O	O	O
4	're	O	O	O
5	doing	O	O	O
6	it	O	O	O
7	again	O	O	O
8	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4261
# text = Oh, right sorry.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	right	O	O	O
4	sorry	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4262
# text = Magical water plants of the highland Lochs?
1	Magical	O	O	O
2	water	O	O	O
3	plants	O	O	O
4	of	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	highland	O	O	O
7	Lochs	O	O	O
8	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4263
# text = Moody gave it to me. That day we had tea.
1	Moody	B-PER	O	O
2	gave	O	O	O
3	it	O	O	O
4	to	O	O	O
5	me	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	That	O	O	O
8	day	O	O	O
9	we	O	O	O
10	had	O	O	O
11	tea	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4264
# text = We've already been through enough people why don't you just go and do it yourself? Ughh. What do you want me to say again?
1	We	O	O	O
2	've	O	O	O
3	already	O	O	O
4	been	O	O	O
5	through	O	O	O
6	enough	O	O	O
7	people	O	O	O
8	why	O	O	O
9	do	O	O	O
10	n't	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	just	O	O	O
13	go	O	O	O
14	and	O	O	O
15	do	O	O	O
16	it	O	O	O
17	yourself	O	O	O
18	?	O	O	O
19	Ughh	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O
21	What	O	O	O
22	do	O	O	O
23	you	O	O	O
24	want	O	O	O
25	me	O	O	O
26	to	O	O	O
27	say	O	O	O
28	again	O	O	O
29	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4265
# text = Ronald would like me to tell you that Seamus told him that Dean was told by Parvati that Hagrid was looking for you.
1	Ronald	B-PER	O	O
2	would	O	O	O
3	like	O	O	O
4	me	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	tell	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	that	O	O	O
9	Seamus	B-PER	O	O
10	told	O	O	O
11	him	O	O	O
12	that	O	O	O
13	Dean	B-PER	O	O
14	was	O	O	O
15	told	O	O	O
16	by	O	O	O
17	Parvati	B-PER	O	O
18	that	O	O	O
19	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
20	was	O	O	O
21	looking	O	O	O
22	for	O	O	O
23	you	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4266
# text = Is that right? Well.... what?
1	Is	O	O	O
2	that	O	O	O
3	right	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O
5	Well	O	O	O
6	...	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	what	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4267
# text = Uhhh...
1	Uhhh	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4268
# text = Dean was told by Parvati that... Please don't ask me say it again. Hagrid's looking for you.
1	Dean	B-PER	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	told	O	O	O
4	by	O	O	O
5	Parvati	B-PER	O	O
6	that	O	O	O
7	...	O	O	O
8	Please	O	O	O
9	do	O	O	O
10	n't	O	O	O
11	ask	O	O	O
12	me	O	O	O
13	say	O	O	O
14	it	O	O	O
15	again	O	O	O
16	.	O	O	O
17	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
18	's	O	O	O
19	looking	O	O	O
20	for	O	O	O
21	you	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4269
# text = Well you can tell Ronald...
1	Well	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	can	O	O	O
4	tell	O	O	O
5	Ronald	B-PER	O	O
6	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4270
# text = I'm NOT an owl!
1	I	O	O	O
2	'm	O	O	O
3	NOT	O	O	O
4	an	O	O	O
5	owl	O	O	O
6	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4271
# text = Did you bring your father's cloak like I asked you?
1	Did	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	bring	O	O	O
4	your	O	O	O
5	father	O	O	O
6	's	O	O	O
7	cloak	O	O	O
8	like	O	O	O
9	I	O	O	O
10	asked	O	O	O
11	you	O	O	O
12	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4272
# text = Yeah I brought the cloak. Hagrid where are we going?
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	brought	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	cloak	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
8	where	O	O	O
9	are	O	O	O
10	we	O	O	O
11	going	O	O	O
12	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4273
# text = You'll see soon enough. Pay attention this is important.
1	You	O	O	O
2	'll	O	O	O
3	see	O	O	O
4	soon	O	O	O
5	enough	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	Pay	O	O	O
8	attention	O	O	O
9	this	O	O	O
10	is	O	O	O
11	important	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4274
# text = What's with the flower? Hagrid have you combed your hair?
1	What	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	with	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	flower	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O
7	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
8	have	O	O	O
9	you	O	O	O
10	combed	O	O	O
11	your	O	O	O
12	hair	O	O	O
13	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4275
# text = As a matter of fact I have. You might like to try the same thing now and again.
1	As	O	O	O
2	a	O	O	O
3	matter	O	O	O
4	of	O	O	O
5	fact	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	have	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	You	O	O	O
10	might	O	O	O
11	like	O	O	O
12	to	O	O	O
13	try	O	O	O
14	the	O	O	O
15	same	O	O	O
16	thing	O	O	O
17	now	O	O	O
18	and	O	O	O
19	again	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4276
# text = Hagrid?
1	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
2	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4277
# text = Oh, the cloak. Put the cloak on.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	the	O	O	O
4	cloak	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Put	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	cloak	O	O	O
9	on	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4278
# text = Bonsoir Olympe.
1	Bonsoir	O	O	O
2	Olympe	B-PER	O	O
3	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4279
# text = Oh Hagrid. I thought you weren't coming, I thought perhaps... you had... forgotten me.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	I	O	O	O
5	thought	O	O	O
6	you	O	O	O
7	were	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	coming	O	O	O
10	,	O	O	O
11	I	O	O	O
12	thought	O	O	O
13	perhaps	O	O	O
14	...	O	O	O
15	you	O	O	O
16	had	O	O	O
17	...	O	O	O
18	forgotten	O	O	O
19	me	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4280
# text = Couldn't forget you Olympe.
1	Could	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	forget	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	Olympe	B-PER	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4281
# text = What is it you want to show me? When we spoke earlier you sounded so exhilirated.
1	What	O	O	O
2	is	O	O	O
3	it	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	want	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	show	O	O	O
8	me	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O
10	When	O	O	O
11	we	O	O	O
12	spoke	O	O	O
13	earlier	O	O	O
14	you	O	O	O
15	sounded	O	O	O
16	so	O	O	O
17	exhilirated	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4282
# text = You'll be glad you came. Trust me.
1	You	O	O	O
2	'll	O	O	O
3	be	O	O	O
4	glad	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	came	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Trust	O	O	O
9	me	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4283
# text = Ahh, c'est magnifique!
1	Ahh	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	c	O	O	O
4	'	O	O	O
5	est	O	O	O
6	magnifique	O	O	O
7	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4284
# text = Can we get closer?
1	Can	O	O	O
2	we	O	O	O
3	get	O	O	O
4	closer	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4285
# text = Dragons? That's the first task? You're joking.
1	Dragons	B-CRT	O	O
2	?	O	O	O
3	That	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	first	O	O	O
7	task	O	O	O
8	?	O	O	O
9	You	O	O	O
10	're	O	O	O
11	joking	O	O	O
12	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4286
# text = Come on Harry. They're seriously misunderstood creatures.
1	Come	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	Harry	B-PER	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	They	O	O	O
6	're	O	O	O
7	seriously	O	O	O
8	misunderstood	O	O	O
9	creatures	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4287
# text = Although, I have to admit that horntail is a right nasty piece of work. Poor Ron nearly fainted just seeing him you know.
1	Although	O	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	have	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	admit	O	O	O
7	that	O	O	O
8	horntail	B-CRT	O	O
9	is	O	O	O
10	a	O	O	O
11	right	O	O	O
12	nasty	O	O	O
13	piece	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	work	O	O	O
16	.	O	O	O
17	Poor	O	O	O
18	Ron	B-PER	O	O
19	nearly	O	O	O
20	fainted	O	O	O
21	just	O	O	O
22	seeing	O	O	O
23	him	O	O	O
24	you	O	O	O
25	know	O	O	O
26	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4288
# text = Ron was here?
1	Ron	B-PER	O	O
2	was	O	O	O
3	here	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4289
# text = Oh sure. His brother Charlie helped bring him over from Romania. Didn't Ron tell you that?
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	sure	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	His	O	O	O
5	brother	O	O	O
6	Charlie	B-PER	O	O
7	helped	O	O	O
8	bring	O	O	O
9	him	O	O	O
10	over	O	O	O
11	from	O	O	O
12	Romania	B-LOC	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	Did	O	O	O
15	n't	O	O	O
16	Ron	B-PER	O	O
17	tell	O	O	O
18	you	O	O	O
19	that	O	O	O
20	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4290
# text = No he didn't. He didn't tell me a thing.
1	No	O	O	O
2	he	O	O	O
3	did	O	O	O
4	n't	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	He	O	O	O
7	did	O	O	O
8	n't	O	O	O
9	tell	O	O	O
10	me	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	thing	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4291
# text = Cedric rules!
1	Cedric	B-PER	O	O
2	rules	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4292
# text = Thanks.
1	Thanks	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4293
# text = Like the badge?
1	Like	O	O	O
2	the	O	O	O
3	badge	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4294
# text = Excuse me..
1	Excuse	O	O	O
2	me	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4295
# text = Can I have a word?
1	Can	O	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	have	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	word	O	O	O
6	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4296
# text = Alright.
1	Alright	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4297
# text = Dragons. That's the first task. They've got one for each of us.
1	Dragons	B-CRT	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	That	O	O	O
4	's	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	first	O	O	O
7	task	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	They	O	O	O
10	've	O	O	O
11	got	O	O	O
12	one	O	O	O
13	for	O	O	O
14	each	O	O	O
15	of	O	O	O
16	us	O	O	O
17	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4298
# text = Are you serious? And Fleur and Krum, do they...?
1	Are	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	serious	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O
5	And	O	O	O
6	Fleur	B-PER	O	O
7	and	O	O	O
8	Krum	B-PER	O	O
9	,	O	O	O
10	do	O	O	O
11	they	O	O	O
12	...	O	O	O
13	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4299
# text = Yes.
1	Yes	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4300
# text = Right. Hey listen, about the badges. I've asked them not to wear them.
1	Right	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Hey	O	O	O
4	listen	O	O	O
5	,	O	O	O
6	about	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	badges	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	I	O	O	O
11	've	O	O	O
12	asked	O	O	O
13	them	O	O	O
14	not	O	O	O
15	to	O	O	O
16	wear	O	O	O
17	them	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4301
# text = Don't worry about it.
1	Do	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	worry	O	O	O
4	about	O	O	O
5	it	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4302
# text = You're a right foul git you know that?
1	You	O	O	O
2	're	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	right	O	O	O
5	foul	O	O	O
6	git	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	know	O	O	O
9	that	O	O	O
10	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4303
# text = You think so?
1	You	O	O	O
2	think	O	O	O
3	so	O	O	O
4	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4304
# text = I know so.
1	I	O	O	O
2	know	O	O	O
3	so	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4305
# text = Anything else?
1	Anything	O	O	O
2	else	O	O	O
3	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4306
# text = Yeah. Stay away from me.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Stay	O	O	O
4	away	O	O	O
5	from	O	O	O
6	me	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4307
# text = Fine.
1	Fine	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4308
# text = Why so tense Potter? My father and I have a bet you see. I don't think you're gonna last ten minutes in this tournament. He disagrees. He thinks you won't last
1	Why	O	O	O
2	so	O	O	O
3	tense	O	O	O
4	Potter	B-PER	O	O
5	?	O	O	O
6	My	O	O	O
7	father	O	O	O
8	and	O	O	O
9	I	O	O	O
10	have	O	O	O
11	a	O	O	O
12	bet	O	O	O
13	you	O	O	O
14	see	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O
16	I	O	O	O
17	do	O	O	O
18	n't	O	O	O
19	think	O	O	O
20	you	O	O	O
21	're	O	O	O
22	gonna	O	O	O
23	last	O	O	O
24	ten	O	O	O
25	minutes	O	O	O
26	in	O	O	O
27	this	O	O	O
28	tournament	O	O	O
29	.	O	O	O
30	He	O	O	O
31	disagrees	O	O	O
32	.	O	O	O
33	He	O	O	O
34	thinks	O	O	O
35	you	O	O	O
36	wo	O	O	O
37	n't	O	O	O
38	last	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4309
# text = I don't give a damn what you or your father thinks Malfoy. He's vile and cruel, and you're just pathetic.
1	I	O	O	O
2	do	O	O	O
3	n't	O	O	O
4	give	O	O	O
5	a	O	O	O
6	damn	O	O	O
7	what	O	O	O
8	you	O	O	O
9	or	O	O	O
10	your	O	O	O
11	father	O	O	O
12	thinks	O	O	O
13	Malfoy	B-PER	O	O
14	.	O	O	O
15	He	O	O	O
16	's	O	O	O
17	vile	O	O	O
18	and	O	O	O
19	cruel	O	O	O
20	,	O	O	O
21	and	O	O	O
22	you	O	O	O
23	're	O	O	O
24	just	O	O	O
25	pathetic	O	O	O
26	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4310
# text = I'll teach you to cast when someone's back is turned.
1	I	O	O	O
2	'll	O	O	O
3	teach	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	to	O	O	O
6	cast	O	O	O
7	when	O	O	O
8	someone	O	O	O
9	's	O	O	O
10	back	O	O	O
11	is	O	O	O
12	turned	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4311
# text = Professor Moody what are you doing?
1	Professor	B-TTL	O	O
2	Moody	B-PER	O	O
3	what	O	O	O
4	are	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	doing	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4312
# text = Teaching.
1	Teaching	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4313
# text = Is that a student?
1	Is	O	O	O
2	that	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	student	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4314
# text = Technically it's a ferret.
1	Technically	O	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	's	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	ferret	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4315
# text = My father will hear about this!
1	My	O	O	O
2	father	O	O	O
3	will	O	O	O
4	hear	O	O	O
5	about	O	O	O
6	this	O	O	O
7	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4316
# text = Is that a threat!
1	Is	O	O	O
2	that	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	threat	O	O	O
5	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4317
# text = I could tell you stories about your father that would curl even your greasy hair boy! It doesn't end here!
1	I	O	O	O
2	could	O	O	O
3	tell	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	stories	O	O	O
6	about	O	O	O
7	your	O	O	O
8	father	O	O	O
9	that	O	O	O
10	would	O	O	O
11	curl	O	O	O
12	even	O	O	O
13	your	O	O	O
14	greasy	O	O	O
15	hair	O	O	O
16	boy	O	O	O
17	!	O	O	O
18	It	O	O	O
19	does	O	O	O
20	n't	O	O	O
21	end	O	O	O
22	here	O	O	O
23	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4318
# text = We never use transfigration as a punishment, surely Dumbledore told you that.
1	We	O	O	O
2	never	O	O	O
3	use	O	O	O
4	transfigration	B-SPL	O	O
5	as	O	O	O
6	a	O	O	O
7	punishment	O	O	O
8	,	O	O	O
9	surely	O	O	O
10	Dumbledore	B-PER	O	O
11	told	O	O	O
12	you	O	O	O
13	that	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4319
# text = He might've mentioned it.
1	He	O	O	O
2	might	O	O	O
3	've	O	O	O
4	mentioned	O	O	O
5	it	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4320
# text = Well you will do well to remember it.
1	Well	O	O	O
2	you	O	O	O
3	will	O	O	O
4	do	O	O	O
5	well	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	remember	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4321
# text = come with me.
1	come	O	O	O
2	with	O	O	O
3	me	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4322
# text = That's a foe glass. Lets me keep an eye on my enemies. If I can see the whites of their eyes they're standing right behind me.
1	That	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	a	O	O	O
4	foe	B-MIT	O	O
5	glass	I-MIT	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	Lets	O	O	O
8	me	O	O	O
9	keep	O	O	O
10	an	O	O	O
11	eye	O	O	O
12	on	O	O	O
13	my	O	O	O
14	enemies	O	O	O
15	.	O	O	O
16	If	O	O	O
17	I	O	O	O
18	can	O	O	O
19	see	O	O	O
20	the	O	O	O
21	whites	O	O	O
22	of	O	O	O
23	their	O	O	O
24	eyes	O	O	O
25	they	O	O	O
26	're	O	O	O
27	standing	O	O	O
28	right	O	O	O
29	behind	O	O	O
30	me	O	O	O
31	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4323
# text = Wouldn't even bother telling you what's in ther. You wouldn't believe it if I did. Now... what are you going to do about your dragon?
1	Would	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	even	O	O	O
4	bother	O	O	O
5	telling	O	O	O
6	you	O	O	O
7	what	O	O	O
8	's	O	O	O
9	in	O	O	O
10	ther	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	You	O	O	O
13	would	O	O	O
14	n't	O	O	O
15	believe	O	O	O
16	it	O	O	O
17	if	O	O	O
18	I	O	O	O
19	did	O	O	O
20	.	O	O	O
21	Now	O	O	O
22	...	O	O	O
23	what	O	O	O
24	are	O	O	O
25	you	O	O	O
26	going	O	O	O
27	to	O	O	O
28	do	O	O	O
29	about	O	O	O
30	your	O	O	O
31	dragon	B-CRT	O	O
32	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4324
# text = Oh... um... You know I just thought I'd...
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O
3	um	O	O	O
4	...	O	O	O
5	You	O	O	O
6	know	O	O	O
7	I	O	O	O
8	just	O	O	O
9	thought	O	O	O
10	I	O	O	O
11	'd	O	O	O
12	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4325
# text = Sit. Listen to me Potter. Your pal Diggory, by your age he could take a whistle into a watch and have it sing you the time. Miss Delacour, she's as much a fairy princess as I am. As for Krum, his head may be filled with sawdust but Karkaroff's is NOT. They'll have a strategy, and you can bet that it'll play to Krum's strengths. Hmm? Come on Potter. What are your strengths?
1	Sit	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	Listen	O	O	O
4	to	O	O	O
5	me	O	O	O
6	Potter	B-PER	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Your	O	O	O
9	pal	O	O	O
10	Diggory	B-PER	O	O
11	,	O	O	O
12	by	O	O	O
13	your	O	O	O
14	age	O	O	O
15	he	O	O	O
16	could	O	O	O
17	take	O	O	O
18	a	O	O	O
19	whistle	O	O	O
20	into	O	O	O
21	a	O	O	O
22	watch	O	O	O
23	and	O	O	O
24	have	O	O	O
25	it	O	O	O
26	sing	O	O	O
27	you	O	O	O
28	the	O	O	O
29	time	O	O	O
30	.	O	O	O
31	Miss	B-TTL	O	O
32	Delacour	B-PER	O	O
33	,	O	O	O
34	she	O	O	O
35	's	O	O	O
36	as	O	O	O
37	much	O	O	O
38	a	O	O	O
39	fairy	O	O	O
40	princess	O	O	O
41	as	O	O	O
42	I	O	O	O
43	am	O	O	O
44	.	O	O	O
45	As	O	O	O
46	for	O	O	O
47	Krum	B-PER	O	O
48	,	O	O	O
49	his	O	O	O
50	head	O	O	O
51	may	O	O	O
52	be	O	O	O
53	filled	O	O	O
54	with	O	O	O
55	sawdust	O	O	O
56	but	O	O	O
57	Karkaroff	B-PER	O	O
58	's	O	O	O
59	is	O	O	O
60	NOT	O	O	O
61	.	O	O	O
62	They	O	O	O
63	'll	O	O	O
64	have	O	O	O
65	a	O	O	O
66	strategy	O	O	O
67	,	O	O	O
68	and	O	O	O
69	you	O	O	O
70	can	O	O	O
71	bet	O	O	O
72	that	O	O	O
73	it	O	O	O
74	'll	O	O	O
75	play	O	O	O
76	to	O	O	O
77	Krum	B-PER	O	O
78	's	O	O	O
79	strengths	O	O	O
80	.	O	O	O
81	Hmm	O	O	O
82	?	O	O	O
83	Come	O	O	O
84	on	O	O	O
85	Potter	B-PER	O	O
86	.	O	O	O
87	What	O	O	O
88	are	O	O	O
89	your	O	O	O
90	strengths	O	O	O
91	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4326
# text = Um... I dunno.. I can fly. I mean I'm a fair flyer.
1	Um	O	O	O
2	...	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	dunno	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	I	O	O	O
8	can	O	O	O
9	fly	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O
11	I	O	O	O
12	mean	O	O	O
13	I	O	O	O
14	'm	O	O	O
15	a	O	O	O
16	fair	O	O	O
17	flyer	O	O	O
18	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4327
# text = Better than fair the way I heard it.
1	Better	O	O	O
2	than	O	O	O
3	fair	O	O	O
4	the	O	O	O
5	way	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	heard	O	O	O
8	it	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4328
# text = But I'm not allowed a broom.
1	But	O	O	O
2	I	O	O	O
3	'm	O	O	O
4	not	O	O	O
5	allowed	O	O	O
6	a	O	O	O
7	broom	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4329
# text = You're allowed a wand.
1	You	O	O	O
2	're	O	O	O
3	allowed	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	wand	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4330
# text = Pssst! Harry? Is that you?
1	Pssst	O	O	O
2	!	O	O	O
3	Harry	B-PER	O	O
4	?	O	O	O
5	Is	O	O	O
6	that	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4331
# text = Yeah.
1	Yeah	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4332
# text = How are you feeling? OK? The key is to concentrate. After that you just have to...
1	How	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	feeling	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O
6	OK	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O
8	The	O	O	O
9	key	O	O	O
10	is	O	O	O
11	to	O	O	O
12	concentrate	O	O	O
13	.	O	O	O
14	After	O	O	O
15	that	O	O	O
16	you	O	O	O
17	just	O	O	O
18	have	O	O	O
19	to	O	O	O
20	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4333
# text = Battle a dragon.
1	Battle	O	O	O
2	a	O	O	O
3	dragon	B-CRT	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4334
# text = Young love! Ohh how.. stirring. If everything goes unfortunately today you might make the front page.
1	Young	O	O	O
2	love	O	O	O
3	!	O	O	O
4	Ohh	O	O	O
5	how	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	stirring	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	If	O	O	O
11	everything	O	O	O
12	goes	O	O	O
13	unfortunately	O	O	O
14	today	O	O	O
15	you	O	O	O
16	might	O	O	O
17	make	O	O	O
18	the	O	O	O
19	front	O	O	O
20	page	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4335
# text = You have no business here. This tent is for champions and friends.
1	You	O	O	O
2	have	O	O	O
3	no	O	O	O
4	business	O	O	O
5	here	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O
7	This	O	O	O
8	tent	O	O	O
9	is	O	O	O
10	for	O	O	O
11	champions	B-TTL	O	O
12	and	O	O	O
13	friends	O	O	O
14	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4336
# text = No matter. We've got what we wanted.
1	No	O	O	O
2	matter	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	We	O	O	O
5	've	O	O	O
6	got	O	O	O
7	what	O	O	O
8	we	O	O	O
9	wanted	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4337
# text = Good day champions. Gather round please. Now you've waited, you've wondered and at last the moment has arrived. The moment only four of you can fully appreciate.
1	Good	O	O	O
2	day	O	O	O
3	champions	B-TTL	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Gather	O	O	O
6	round	O	O	O
7	please	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Now	O	O	O
10	you	O	O	O
11	've	O	O	O
12	waited	O	O	O
13	,	O	O	O
14	you	O	O	O
15	've	O	O	O
16	wondered	O	O	O
17	and	O	O	O
18	at	O	O	O
19	last	O	O	O
20	the	O	O	O
21	moment	O	O	O
22	has	O	O	O
23	arrived	O	O	O
24	.	O	O	O
25	The	O	O	O
26	moment	O	O	O
27	only	O	O	O
28	four	O	O	O
29	of	O	O	O
30	you	O	O	O
31	can	O	O	O
32	fully	O	O	O
33	appreciate	O	O	O
34	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4338
# text = What are you doing here Miss Granger?
1	What	O	O	O
2	are	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	doing	O	O	O
5	here	O	O	O
6	Miss	B-TTL	O	O
7	Granger	B-PER	O	O
8	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4339
# text = Oh um.. Sorry I'll just go.
1	Oh	O	O	O
2	um	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Sorry	O	O	O
6	I	O	O	O
7	'll	O	O	O
8	just	O	O	O
9	go	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4340
# text = Barty. The bag.
1	Barty	B-PER	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	The	O	O	O
4	bag	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4341
# text = Champions, in a circle around me. Miss Delacour over here, Mr Krum, and Potter over here. Right. Miss Delacour, if you will...
1	Champions	B-TTL	O	O
2	,	O	O	O
3	in	O	O	O
4	a	O	O	O
5	circle	O	O	O
6	around	O	O	O
7	me	O	O	O
8	.	O	O	O
9	Miss	B-TTL	O	O
10	Delacour	B-PER	O	O
11	over	O	O	O
12	here	O	O	O
13	,	O	O	O
14	Mr	B-TTL	O	O
15	Krum	B-PER	O	O
16	,	O	O	O
17	and	O	O	O
18	Potter	B-PER	O	O
19	over	O	O	O
20	here	O	O	O
21	.	O	O	O
22	Right	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O
24	Miss	B-TTL	O	O
25	Delacour	B-PER	O	O
26	,	O	O	O
27	if	O	O	O
28	you	O	O	O
29	will	O	O	O
30	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4342
# text = The welsh green. Mr Krum...
1	The	O	O	O
2	welsh	B-CRT	O	O
3	green	I-CRT	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Mr	B-TTL	O	O
6	Krum	B-PER	O	O
7	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4343
# text = The chinese fireball. Oooooh.
1	The	O	O	O
2	chinese	B-CRT	O	O
3	fireball	I-CRT	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	Oooooh	O	O	O
6	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4344
# text = The swedish short-snout. Which leaves...
1	The	O	O	O
2	swedish	B-CRT	O	O
3	short	I-CRT	O	O
4	snout	I-CRT	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Which	O	O	O
7	leaves	O	O	O
8	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4345
# text = The horntail...
1	The	O	O	O
2	horntail	B-CRT	O	O
3	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4346
# text = What's that boy?
1	What	O	O	O
2	's	O	O	O
3	that	O	O	O
4	boy	O	O	O
5	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4347
# text = Nothing.
1	Nothing	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4348
# text = The hungarian horntail. These represent very real dragons, each of which has been given a golden egg to protect. Your objective is simple, collect the egg. This you must do, for each egg contains a clue without which you cannot hope to proceed to the next task. Any questions?
1	The	O	O	O
2	hungarian	B-CRT	O	O
3	horntail	I-CRT	O	O
4	.	O	O	O
5	These	O	O	O
6	represent	O	O	O
7	very	O	O	O
8	real	O	O	O
9	dragons	O	O	O
10	,	O	O	O
11	each	O	O	O
12	of	O	O	O
13	which	O	O	O
14	has	O	O	O
15	been	O	O	O
16	given	O	O	O
17	a	O	O	O
18	golden	O	O	O
19	egg	O	O	O
20	to	O	O	O
21	protect	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O
23	Your	O	O	O
24	objective	O	O	O
25	is	O	O	O
26	simple	O	O	O
27	,	O	O	O
28	collect	O	O	O
29	the	O	O	O
30	egg	O	O	O
31	.	O	O	O
32	This	O	O	O
33	you	O	O	O
34	must	O	O	O
35	do	O	O	O
36	,	O	O	O
37	for	O	O	O
38	each	O	O	O
39	egg	O	O	O
40	contains	O	O	O
41	a	O	O	O
42	clue	O	O	O
43	without	O	O	O
44	which	O	O	O
45	you	O	O	O
46	cannot	O	O	O
47	hope	O	O	O
48	to	O	O	O
49	proceed	O	O	O
50	to	O	O	O
51	the	O	O	O
52	next	O	O	O
53	task	O	O	O
54	.	O	O	O
55	Any	O	O	O
56	questions	O	O	O
57	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4349
# text = Very well. Good luck champions. Mr Diggory the sound of the cannon...
1	Very	O	O	O
2	well	O	O	O
3	.	O	O	O
4	Good	O	O	O
5	luck	O	O	O
6	champions	B-TTL	O	O
7	.	O	O	O
8	Mr	B-TTL	O	O
9	Diggory	B-PER	O	O
10	the	O	O	O
11	sound	O	O	O
12	of	O	O	O
13	the	O	O	O
14	cannon	O	O	O
15	...	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4350
# text = Three of our champions have now faced their dragons and so each one of them will proceed to the next task. And now our fourth and final contestant.
1	Three	O	O	O
2	of	O	O	O
3	our	O	O	O
4	champions	B-TTL	O	O
5	have	O	O	O
6	now	O	O	O
7	faced	O	O	O
8	their	O	O	O
9	dragons	B-CRT	O	O
10	and	O	O	O
11	so	O	O	O
12	each	O	O	O
13	one	O	O	O
14	of	O	O	O
15	them	O	O	O
16	will	O	O	O
17	proceed	O	O	O
18	to	O	O	O
19	the	O	O	O
20	next	O	O	O
21	task	O	O	O
22	.	O	O	O
23	And	O	O	O
24	now	O	O	O
25	our	O	O	O
26	fourth	O	O	O
27	and	O	O	O
28	final	O	O	O
29	contestant	O	O	O
30	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4351
# text = Your wand harry! Your wand!
1	Your	O	O	O
2	wand	O	O	O
3	harry	O	O	O
4	!	O	O	O
5	Your	O	O	O
6	wand	O	O	O
7	!	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4352
# text = We knew you wouldn't die Harry.
1	We	O	O	O
2	knew	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	would	O	O	O
5	n't	O	O	O
6	die	O	O	O
7	Harry	B-PER	O	O
8	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4353
# text = Lose a leg.
1	Lose	O	O	O
2	a	O	O	O
3	leg	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4354
# text = Or an arm.
1	Or	O	O	O
2	an	O	O	O
3	arm	O	O	O
4	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4355
# text = Pack it in altogether.
1	Pack	O	O	O
2	it	O	O	O
3	in	O	O	O
4	altogether	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4356
# text = Go on Harry, what's the clue?
1	Go	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	Harry	B-PER	O	O
4	,	O	O	O
5	what	O	O	O
6	's	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	clue	O	O	O
9	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4357
# text = Who wants me to open it? You want me to open it?
1	Who	O	O	O
2	wants	O	O	O
3	me	O	O	O
4	to	O	O	O
5	open	O	O	O
6	it	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O
8	You	O	O	O
9	want	O	O	O
10	me	O	O	O
11	to	O	O	O
12	open	O	O	O
13	it	O	O	O
14	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4358
# text = What the bloody hell was that?
1	What	O	O	O
2	the	O	O	O
3	bloody	O	O	O
4	hell	O	O	O
5	was	O	O	O
6	that	O	O	O
7	?	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4359
# text = Alright everyone, go back to your knitting. This is gonna be uncomfortable enough without all you nosey sods listening in.
1	Alright	O	O	O
2	everyone	O	O	O
3	,	O	O	O
4	go	O	O	O
5	back	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	your	O	O	O
8	knitting	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O
10	This	O	O	O
11	is	O	O	O
12	gonna	O	O	O
13	be	O	O	O
14	uncomfortable	O	O	O
15	enough	O	O	O
16	without	O	O	O
17	all	O	O	O
18	you	O	O	O
19	nosey	O	O	O
20	sods	O	O	O
21	listening	O	O	O
22	in	O	O	O
23	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4360
# text = I reckon you'd have to be barking mad to put your own name in the goblet of fire.
1	I	O	O	O
2	reckon	O	O	O
3	you	O	O	O
4	'd	O	O	O
5	have	O	O	O
6	to	O	O	O
7	be	O	O	O
8	barking	O	O	O
9	mad	O	O	O
10	to	O	O	O
11	put	O	O	O
12	your	O	O	O
13	own	O	O	O
14	name	O	O	O
15	in	O	O	O
16	the	O	O	O
17	goblet	B-MIT	O	O
18	of	I-MIT	O	O
19	fire	I-MIT	O	O
20	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4361
# text = Caught on have you. Took you long enough.
1	Caught	O	O	O
2	on	O	O	O
3	have	O	O	O
4	you	O	O	O
5	.	O	O	O
6	Took	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	long	O	O	O
9	enough	O	O	O
10	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4362
# text = Wasn't just me who thought you'd done it. Everyone was saying it behind your back.
1	Was	O	O	O
2	n't	O	O	O
3	just	O	O	O
4	me	O	O	O
5	who	O	O	O
6	thought	O	O	O
7	you	O	O	O
8	'd	O	O	O
9	done	O	O	O
10	it	O	O	O
11	.	O	O	O
12	Everyone	O	O	O
13	was	O	O	O
14	saying	O	O	O
15	it	O	O	O
16	behind	O	O	O
17	your	O	O	O
18	back	O	O	O
19	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4363
# text = Brilliant. That makes me feel loads better.
1	Brilliant	O	O	O
2	.	O	O	O
3	That	O	O	O
4	makes	O	O	O
5	me	O	O	O
6	feel	O	O	O
7	loads	O	O	O
8	better	O	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4364
# text = At least I warned you about the dragons.
1	At	O	O	O
2	least	O	O	O
3	I	O	O	O
4	warned	O	O	O
5	you	O	O	O
6	about	O	O	O
7	the	O	O	O
8	dragons	B-CRT	O	O
9	.	O	O	O

# sent_id = 4365
# text = Hagrid warned me about the dragons.
1	Hagrid	B-PER	O	O
2	warned	O	O	O
3	me	O	O	O
4	about	O	O	O
5	the	O	O	O
6	dragons	B-CRT	O	O
7	.	O	O	O