# newdoc id = hp3diolog.csv
# sent_id = 300001
# text = Lumos Maxima. Lumos Maxima. Lumos Maxima. Lumos Maxima. Lumos Maxima!
Lumos	B-SPL
Maxima	I-SPL
.	O
Lumos	B-SPL
Maxima	I-SPL
.	O
Lumos	B-SPL
Maxima	I-SPL
.	O
Lumos	B-SPL
Maxima	I-SPL
.	O
Lumos	B-SPL
Maxima	I-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300002
# text = Harry! Harry! Harry, open the door! Marge! How lovely to see...
Harry	B-PER
!	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
open	O
the	O
door	O
!	O
Marge	O
!	O
How	O
lovely	O
to	O
see	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300003
# text = Uncle Vernon, I need you to sign this form.
Uncle	O
Vernon	B-PER
,	O
I	O
need	O
you	O
to	O
sign	O
this	O
form	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300004
# text = What is it?
What	O
is	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300005
# text = Nothing. School stuff.
Nothing	O
.	O
School	O
stuff	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300006
# text = Later perhaps, if you behave.
Later	O
perhaps	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
behave	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300007
# text = I will if she does.
I	O
will	O
if	O
she	O
does	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300008
# text = Oh, you're still here, are you?
Oh	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
still	O
here	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300009
# text = Yes.
Yes	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300010
# text = Don't say yes in that ungrateful way. Damn good of my brother to keep you. He'd have been straight to an orphanage if he'd been dumped on my doorstep. Is that my Dudders? Is that my little neffy-pooh? Give us a kiss! Come on! Up, up!
Do	O
n't	O
say	O
yes	O
in	O
that	O
ungrateful	O
way	O
.	O
Damn	O
good	O
of	O
my	O
brother	O
to	O
keep	O
you	O
.	O
He	O
'd	O
have	O
been	O
straight	O
to	O
an	O
orphanage	O
if	O
he	O
'd	O
been	O
dumped	O
on	O
my	O
doorstep	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
my	O
Dudders	B-PER
?	O
Is	O
that	O
my	O
little	O
neffy	O
pooh	O
?	O
Give	O
us	O
a	O
kiss	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
!	O
Up	O
,	O
up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300011
# text = Take Marge's suitcase upstairs!
Take	O
Marge	B-PER
's	O
suitcase	O
upstairs	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300012
# text = Okay.
Okay	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300013
# text = Finish that off for Mommy. Good boy, Rippy-pooh.
Finish	O
that	O
off	O
for	O
Mommy	O
.	O
Good	O
boy	O
,	O
Rippy	B-PER
pooh	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300014
# text = Can I tempt you, Marge?
Can	O
I	O
tempt	O
you	O
,	O
Marge	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300015
# text = Just a small one. Excellent nosh, Petunia. A bit more. Usually just a fry-up for me, what with 12 dogs. Just a bit more. That's a boy! Mm! You wanna try a little drop of brandy? A little drop of brandy-brandy windy-wandy for Rippy-pippy-pooh? What are you smirking at? Where did you send the boy, Vernon?
Just	O
a	O
small	O
one	O
.	O
Excellent	O
nosh	O
,	O
Petunia	B-PER
.	O
A	O
bit	O
more	O
.	O
Usually	O
just	O
a	O
fry	O
up	O
for	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
with	O
12	O
dogs	O
.	O
Just	O
a	O
bit	O
more	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
boy	O
!	O
Mm	O
!	O
You	O
wanna	O
try	O
a	O
little	O
drop	O
of	O
brandy	O
?	O
A	O
little	O
drop	O
of	O
brandy	O
brandy	O
windy	O
wandy	O
for	O
Rippy	B-PER
pippy	I-PER
pooh	I-PER
?	O
What	O
are	O
you	O
smirking	O
at	O
?	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
send	O
the	O
boy	O
,	O
Vernon	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300016
# text = St. Brutus'. It's a fine institution for hopeless cases.
St	B-ORG
.	O
Brutus	I-ORG
'	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
fine	O
institution	O
for	O
hopeless	O
cases	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300017
# text = Do they use a cane at St. Brutus', boy?
Do	O
they	O
use	O
a	O
cane	O
at	O
St	B-ORG
.	O
Brutus	I-ORG
'	O
,	O
boy	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300018
# text = Oh, yeah. Yeah. I've been beaten loads of times.
Oh	O
,	O
yeah	O
.	O
Yeah	O
.	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
beaten	O
loads	O
of	O
times	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300019
# text = Excellent. I won't have this namby-pamby... wishy-washy nonsense about not beating people who deserve it. You mustn't blame yourself about how this one turned out. It's all to do with blood. Bad blood will out. What is it the boy's father did, Petunia?
Excellent	O
.	O
I	O
wo	O
n't	O
have	O
this	O
namby	O
pamby	O
...	O
wishy	O
washy	O
nonsense	O
about	O
not	O
beating	O
people	O
who	O
deserve	O
it	O
.	O
You	O
must	O
n't	O
blame	O
yourself	O
about	O
how	O
this	O
one	O
turned	O
out	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
all	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
blood	O
.	O
Bad	O
blood	O
will	O
out	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
it	O
the	O
boy	O
's	O
father	O
did	O
,	O
Petunia	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300020
# text = Nothing. He didn't work. He was unemployed.
Nothing	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
n't	O
work	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
unemployed	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300021
# text = And a drunk too, no doubt?
And	O
a	O
drunk	O
too	O
,	O
no	O
doubt	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300022
# text = That's a lie!
That	O
's	O
a	O
lie	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300023
# text = What did you say?
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300024
# text = My dad wasn't a drunk!
My	O
dad	O
was	O
n't	O
a	O
drunk	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300025
# text = Oh, don't worry Don't fuss, Petunia. I have a very firm grip.
Oh	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
worry	O
Do	O
n't	O
fuss	O
,	O
Petunia	B-PER
.	O
I	O
have	O
a	O
very	O
firm	O
grip	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300026
# text = I think it's time you went to bed.
I	O
think	O
it	O
's	O
time	O
you	O
went	O
to	O
bed	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300027
# text = Quiet, Vernon. You, clean it up. Actually, it's nothing to do with the father. It's all to do with the mother. You see it all the time with dogs. If there's something wrong with the bitch, then there's something wrong with the pup.
Quiet	O
,	O
Vernon	B-PER
.	O
You	O
,	O
clean	O
it	O
up	O
.	O
Actually	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
nothing	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
father	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
all	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
the	O
mother	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
it	O
all	O
the	O
time	O
with	O
dogs	O
.	O
If	O
there	O
's	O
something	O
wrong	O
with	O
the	O
bitch	O
,	O
then	O
there	O
's	O
something	O
wrong	O
with	O
the	O
pup	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300028
# text = Shut up! Shut up!
Shut	O
up	O
!	O
Shut	O
up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300029
# text = Mm. Right! Let me tell you... y-y-- Vernon! Vernon! Vernon, do something!
Mm	O
.	O
Right	O
!	O
Let	O
me	O
tell	O
you	O
...	O
y	O
y	O
Vernon	B-PER
!	O
Vernon	B-PER
!	O
Vernon	B-PER
,	O
do	O
something	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300030
# text = Ow! Ripper! Ow! Ripper, get down, boy! Down! Ripper, stop it! Stop! I've got you, Marge! I've got you! Hold on, hold on! Get off!
Ow	O
!	O
Ripper	B-PER
!	O
Ow	O
!	O
Ripper	B-PER
,	O
get	O
down	O
,	O
boy	O
!	O
Down	O
!	O
Ripper	B-PER
,	O
stop	O
it	O
!	O
Stop	O
!	O
I	O
've	O
got	O
you	O
,	O
Marge	B-PER
!	O
I	O
've	O
got	O
you	O
!	O
Hold	O
on	O
,	O
hold	O
on	O
!	O
Get	O
off	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300031
# text = Don't you dare!
Do	O
n't	O
you	O
dare	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300032
# text = Sorry!
Sorry	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300033
# text = Oh, Vernon!
Oh	O
,	O
Vernon	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300034
# text = Oh, God! Marge! Please! Marge! Come back! You bring her back! You bring her back now and you put her right!
Oh	O
,	O
God	O
!	O
Marge	B-PER
!	O
Please	O
!	O
Marge	B-PER
!	O
Come	O
back	O
!	O
You	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
!	O
You	O
bring	O
her	O
back	O
now	O
and	O
you	O
put	O
her	O
right	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300035
# text = No! She deserved what she got! Keep away from me.
No	O
!	O
She	O
deserved	O
what	O
she	O
got	O
!	O
Keep	O
away	O
from	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300036
# text = You're not allowed to do magic outside school.
You	O
're	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
do	O
magic	O
outside	O
school	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300037
# text = Yeah? Try me.
Yeah	O
?	O
Try	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300038
# text = They won't let you back now. You've nowhere to go.
They	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
you	O
back	O
now	O
.	O
You	O
've	O
nowhere	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300039
# text = I don't care. Anywhere's better than here.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
.	O
Anywhere	O
's	O
better	O
than	O
here	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300040
# text = Welcome to the Knight Bus... emergency transport for the stranded witch or wizard. My name is Stan Shunpike, and I will be your conductor for this evening. What you doing down there?
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
Knight	B-ORG
Bus	I-ORG
...	O
emergency	O
transport	O
for	O
the	O
stranded	O
witch	O
or	O
wizard	O
.	O
My	O
name	O
is	O
Stan	B-PER
Shunpike	I-PER
,	O
and	O
I	O
will	O
be	O
your	O
conductor	O
for	O
this	O
evening	O
.	O
What	O
you	O
doing	O
down	O
there	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300041
# text = I fell over.
I	O
fell	O
over	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300042
# text = What you fall over for?
What	O
you	O
fall	O
over	O
for	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300043
# text = I didn't do it on purpose.
I	O
did	O
n't	O
do	O
it	O
on	O
purpose	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300044
# text = Well, come on, then. Let's not wait for the grass to grow. What you looking at?
Well	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
,	O
then	O
.	O
Let	O
's	O
not	O
wait	O
for	O
the	O
grass	O
to	O
grow	O
.	O
What	O
you	O
looking	O
at	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300045
# text = Nothing.
Nothing	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300046
# text = Well, come on, then. In. No, no, no. I'll get this. You get in. Come on. Come on. Move on, move on, move on.
Well	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
,	O
then	O
.	O
In	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
get	O
this	O
.	O
You	O
get	O
in	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Move	O
on	O
,	O
move	O
on	O
,	O
move	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300047
# text = Take her away, Ern.
Take	O
her	O
away	O
,	O
Ern	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300048
# text = Yeah, take it away, Ernie. It's going to be a bumpy ride.
Yeah	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
Ernie	B-PER
.	O
It	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
bumpy	O
ride	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300049
# text = What did you say your name was again?
What	O
did	O
you	O
say	O
your	O
name	O
was	O
again	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300050
# text = I didn't.
I	O
did	O
n't	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300051
# text = Whereabouts are you headed?
Whereabouts	O
are	O
you	O
headed	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300052
# text = The Leaky Cauldron. That's in London.
The	B-LOC
Leaky	I-LOC
Cauldron	I-LOC
.	O
That	O
's	O
in	O
London	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300053
# text = You heard that Ern? The Leaky Cauldron. That's in London.
You	O
heard	O
that	O
Ern	B-PER
?	O
The	B-LOC
Leaky	I-LOC
Cauldron	I-LOC
.	O
That	O
's	O
in	O
London	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300054
# text = The Leaky Cauldron. If you have pea soup... make sure you eat it before it eats you.
The	B-LOC
Leaky	I-LOC
Cauldron	I-LOC
.	O
If	O
you	O
have	O
pea	O
soup	O
...	O
make	O
sure	O
you	O
eat	O
it	O
before	O
it	O
eats	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300055
# text = But the Muggles. Can't they see us?
But	O
the	O
Muggles	B-MAG
.	O
Ca	B-LOC
n't	O
they	O
see	O
us	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300056
# text = Muggles? They don't see nothing, do they?
Muggles	B-MAG
?	O
They	O
do	O
n't	O
see	O
nothing	O
,	O
do	O
they	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300057
# text = No, but if you jab them with a fork, they feel. Ernie, little old lady at 12 o'clock! Ten, nine, eight... seven, six, five... four, three, three and a half... two, one and three quarters. Yes!
No	O
,	O
but	O
if	O
you	O
jab	O
them	O
with	O
a	O
fork	O
,	O
they	O
feel	O
.	O
Ernie	B-PER
,	O
little	O
old	O
lady	O
at	O
12	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
!	O
Ten	O
,	O
nine	O
,	O
eight	O
...	O
seven	O
,	O
six	O
,	O
five	O
...	O
four	O
,	O
three	O
,	O
three	O
and	O
a	O
half	O
...	O
two	O
,	O
one	O
and	O
three	O
quarters	O
.	O
Yes	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300058
# text = Who is that? That man.
Who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
That	O
man	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300059
# text = Who is that? Who is...? That is Sirius Black, that is. Don't tell me you've never been hearing of Sirius Black. He's a murderer. Got himself locked up in Azkaban for it.
Who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Who	O
is	O
...	O
?	O
That	O
is	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
,	O
that	O
is	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
tell	O
me	O
you	O
've	O
never	O
been	O
hearing	O
of	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
.	O
He	O
's	O
a	O
murderer	O
.	O
Got	O
himself	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
for	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300060
# text = How did he escape?
How	O
did	O
he	O
escape	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300061
# text = Well, that's the question, isn't it? He's the first one that done it. He was a big supporter of... You-Know-Who. I reckon you've heard of him.
Well	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
the	O
question	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
it	O
?	O
He	O
's	O
the	O
first	O
one	O
that	O
done	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
was	O
a	O
big	O
supporter	O
of	O
...	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
.	O
I	O
reckon	O
you	O
've	O
heard	O
of	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300062
# text = Yeah. Him I've heard of.
Yeah	O
.	O
Him	O
I	O
've	O
heard	O
of	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300063
# text = Ernie, two double-deckers at 12 o'clock. They're getting closer, Ernie. Ernie, they're right on top of us! Mind your head. Hey, guys? Guys? Why the long faces? Yeah, yeah. Nearly there. Nearly there. The Leaky Cauldron. Next stop, Knockturn Alley.
Ernie	B-PER
,	O
two	O
double	O
deckers	O
at	O
12	O
o	O
'	O
clock	O
.	O
They	O
're	O
getting	O
closer	O
,	O
Ernie	B-PER
.	O
Ernie	B-PER
,	O
they	O
're	O
right	O
on	O
top	O
of	O
us	O
!	O
Mind	O
your	O
head	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
guys	O
?	O
Guys	O
?	O
Why	O
the	O
long	O
faces	O
?	O
Yeah	O
,	O
yeah	O
.	O
Nearly	O
there	O
.	O
Nearly	O
there	O
.	O
The	B-LOC
Leaky	I-LOC
Cauldron	I-LOC
.	O
Next	O
stop	O
,	O
Knockturn	B-LOC
Alley	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300064
# text = Ah, Mr. Potter, at last.
Ah	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
,	O
at	O
last	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300065
# text = Take it away, Ern.
Take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
Ern	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300066
# text = Yeah, take it away, Ernie!
Yeah	O
,	O
take	O
it	O
away	O
,	O
Ernie	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300067
# text = : Room 11.
:	O
Room	O
11	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300068
# text = Hedwig.
Hedwig	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300069
# text = : Right smart bird you got there, Mr. Potter. He arrived here just five minutes before yourself.
:	O
Right	O
smart	O
bird	O
you	O
got	O
there	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
He	O
arrived	O
here	O
just	O
five	O
minutes	O
before	O
yourself	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300070
# text = As Minister for Magic, it is my duty to inform you, Mr. Potter... that earlier this evening your uncle's sister was located... a little south of Sheffield, circling a chimney stack. The Accidental Magic Reversal Department was dispatched immediately. She has been properly punctured and her memory modified. She will have no recollection of the incident whatsoever. So that's that... and no harm done.
As	O
Minister	O
for	O
Magic	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
my	O
duty	O
to	O
inform	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
...	O
that	O
earlier	O
this	O
evening	O
your	O
uncle	O
's	O
sister	O
was	O
located	O
...	O
a	O
little	O
south	O
of	O
Sheffield	B-LOC
,	O
circling	O
a	O
chimney	O
stack	O
.	O
The	O
Accidental	B-ORG
Magic	I-ORG
Reversal	I-ORG
Department	I-ORG
was	O
dispatched	O
immediately	O
.	O
She	O
has	O
been	O
properly	O
punctured	O
and	O
her	O
memory	O
modified	O
.	O
She	O
will	O
have	O
no	O
recollection	O
of	O
the	O
incident	O
whatsoever	O
.	O
So	O
that	O
's	O
that	O
...	O
and	O
no	O
harm	O
done	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300071
# text = : Pea soup?
:	O
Pea	B-PER
soup	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300072
# text = No, thank you. Minister?
No	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O
Minister	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300073
# text = Yes?
Yes	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300074
# text = I don't understand.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
understand	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300075
# text = Understand?
Understand	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300076
# text = I broke the law. Underage wizards can't use magic at home.
I	O
broke	O
the	O
law	O
.	O
Underage	O
wizards	O
ca	O
n't	O
use	O
magic	O
at	O
home	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300077
# text = Come now, Harry the Ministry doesn't send people to Azkaban... for blowing up their aunts. On the other hand, running away like that, given the state of things... was very, very irresponsible.
Come	O
now	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
does	O
n't	O
send	O
people	O
to	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
...	O
for	O
blowing	O
up	O
their	O
aunts	O
.	O
On	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
,	O
running	O
away	O
like	O
that	O
,	O
given	O
the	O
state	O
of	O
things	O
...	O
was	O
very	O
,	O
very	O
irresponsible	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300078
# text = The state of things, sir?
The	O
state	O
of	O
things	O
,	O
sir	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300079
# text = We have a killer on the loose.
We	O
have	O
a	O
killer	O
on	O
the	O
loose	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300080
# text = Sirius Black, you mean? But what's he got to do with me?
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
,	O
you	O
mean	O
?	O
But	O
what	O
's	O
he	O
got	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
me	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300081
# text = Nothing, of course. You're safe. And that's what matters. And tomorrow you'll be on your way back to Hogwarts. These are your new schoolbooks. I took the liberty... of having them brought here. Now Tom will show you to your room.
Nothing	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
safe	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
's	O
what	O
matters	O
.	O
And	O
tomorrow	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
on	O
your	O
way	O
back	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O
These	O
are	O
your	O
new	O
schoolbooks	O
.	O
I	O
took	O
the	O
liberty	O
...	O
of	O
having	O
them	O
brought	O
here	O
.	O
Now	O
Tom	B-PER
will	O
show	O
you	O
to	O
your	O
room	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300082
# text = Hedwig.
Hedwig	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300083
# text = Oh, by the way, Harry. Whilst you're here, it would be best if you didn't... wander.
Oh	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Whilst	O
you	O
're	O
here	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
best	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
n't	O
...	O
wander	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300084
# text = Housekeeping. I'll come back later.
Housekeeping	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
come	O
back	O
later	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300085
# text = I'm warning you, Hermione. Keep that bloody beast of yours away from Scabbers, or I'll turn it into a tea cozy.
I	O
'm	O
warning	O
you	O
,	O
Hermione	B-PER
.	O
Keep	O
that	O
bloody	O
beast	O
of	O
yours	O
away	O
from	O
Scabbers	B-PER
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
turn	O
it	O
into	O
a	O
tea	O
cozy	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300086
# text = It's a cat, Ronald. What do you expect? It's in his nature.
It	O
's	O
a	O
cat	O
,	O
Ronald	B-PER
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
expect	O
?	O
It	O
's	O
in	O
his	O
nature	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300087
# text = A cat? Is that what they told you? Looks more like a pig with hair.
A	O
cat	O
?	O
Is	O
that	O
what	O
they	O
told	O
you	O
?	O
Looks	O
more	O
like	O
a	O
pig	O
with	O
hair	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300088
# text = That's rich... coming from the owner of that smelly old shoe brush. Crookshanks, just ignore the mean little boy.
That	O
's	O
rich	O
...	O
coming	O
from	O
the	O
owner	O
of	O
that	O
smelly	O
old	O
shoe	O
brush	O
.	O
Crookshanks	B-PER
,	O
just	O
ignore	O
the	O
mean	O
little	O
boy	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300089
# text = Harry.
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300090
# text = Harry.
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300091
# text = Egypt. What's it like?
Egypt	B-LOC
.	O
What	O
's	O
it	O
like	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300092
# text = Brilliant. Loads of old stuff... like mummies, tombs, even Scabbers enjoyed himself.
Brilliant	O
.	O
Loads	O
of	O
old	O
stuff	O
...	O
like	O
mummies	O
,	O
tombs	O
,	O
even	O
Scabbers	B-PER
enjoyed	O
himself	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300093
# text = You know the Egyptians used to worship cats?
You	O
know	O
the	O
Egyptians	O
used	O
to	O
worship	O
cats	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300094
# text = Along with the dung beetle.
Along	O
with	O
the	O
dung	O
beetle	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300095
# text = Not flashing that clipping again are you Ron?
Not	O
flashing	O
that	O
clipping	O
again	O
are	O
you	O
Ron	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300096
# text = Not flashing that clipping again are you Ron?
Not	O
flashing	O
that	O
clipping	O
again	O
are	O
you	O
Ron	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300097
# text = I haven't shown anyone.
I	O
have	O
n't	O
shown	O
anyone	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300098
# text = ': No, not a soul. Not unless you count Tom. The day maid. The night maid. The Cook. The bloke who fixed the toilet. And that wizard from Belgium.
'	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
soul	O
.	O
Not	O
unless	O
you	O
count	O
Tom	B-PER
.	O
The	O
day	O
maid	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
maid	O
.	O
The	O
Cook	O
.	O
The	O
bloke	O
who	O
fixed	O
the	O
toilet	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
wizard	O
from	O
Belgium	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300099
# text = ': No, not a soul. Not unless you count Tom. The day maid. The night maid. The Cook. The bloke who fixed the toilet. And that wizard from Belgium.
'	O
:	O
No	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
soul	O
.	O
Not	O
unless	O
you	O
count	O
Tom	B-PER
.	O
The	O
day	O
maid	O
.	O
The	O
night	O
maid	O
.	O
The	O
Cook	B-PER
.	O
The	O
bloke	O
who	O
fixed	O
the	O
toilet	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
wizard	O
from	O
Belgium	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300100
# text = Harry.
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300101
# text = Mrs. Weasley.
Mrs.	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300102
# text = Good to see you, dear.
Good	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
,	O
dear	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300103
# text = Good to see you.
Good	O
to	O
see	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300104
# text = You got everything you need?
You	O
got	O
everything	O
you	O
need	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300105
# text = Yes.
Yes	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300106
# text = Yes? All of your books?
Yes	O
?	O
All	O
of	O
your	O
books	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300107
# text = Yeah, it's all upstairs.
Yeah	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
all	O
upstairs	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300108
# text = All of your clothes?
All	O
of	O
your	O
clothes	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300109
# text = Everything's there.
Everything	O
's	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300110
# text = Good boy.
Good	O
boy	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300111
# text = Thank you.
Thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300112
# text = Harry Potter.
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300113
# text = Mr. Weasley.
Mr.	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300114
# text = Harry, wonder if I might have a word?
Harry	B-PER
,	O
wonder	O
if	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
a	O
word	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300115
# text = Yeah, sure.
Yeah	O
,	O
sure	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300116
# text = Hermione.
Hermione	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300117
# text = Good morning, Mr. Weasley.
Good	O
morning	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300118
# text = Looking forward to a new term?
Looking	O
forward	O
to	O
a	O
new	O
term	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300119
# text = Yeah. It should be great.
Yeah	O
.	O
It	O
should	O
be	O
great	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300120
# text = Harry, some within the Ministry would strongly discourage me... from divulging what I'm about to reveal to you. But I think that you need to know the facts. You are in danger. Grave danger.
Harry	B-PER
,	O
some	O
within	O
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
would	O
strongly	O
discourage	O
me	O
...	O
from	O
divulging	O
what	O
I	O
'm	O
about	O
to	O
reveal	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
think	O
that	O
you	O
need	O
to	O
know	O
the	O
facts	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
in	O
danger	O
.	O
Grave	O
danger	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300121
# text = Has this anything to do with Sirius Black, sir?
Has	O
this	O
anything	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
,	O
sir	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300122
# text = What do you know about Sirius Black, Harry?
What	O
do	O
you	O
know	O
about	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
,	O
Harry	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300123
# text = Only that he's escaped from Azkaban.
Only	O
that	O
he	O
's	O
escaped	O
from	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 300124
# text = Do you know why? Thirteen years ago, when you stopped...
Do	O
you	O
know	O
why	O
?	O
Thirteen	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
you	O
stopped	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300125
# text = Voldemort.
Voldemort	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300126
# text = Don't say his name.
Do	O
n't	O
say	O
his	O
name	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300127
# text = Sorry.
Sorry	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300128
# text = When you stopped You-Know-Who... Black lost everything. But to this day, he still remains a faithful servant. And in his mind... you are the only thing that stands in the way... of You-Know-Who returning to power. And that is why... he has escaped from Azkaban. To find you.
When	O
you	O
stopped	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
...	O
Black	B-MISC
lost	O
everything	O
.	O
But	O
to	O
this	O
day	O
,	O
he	O
still	O
remains	O
a	O
faithful	O
servant	O
.	O
And	O
in	O
his	O
mind	O
...	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
that	O
stands	O
in	O
the	O
way	O
...	O
of	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
returning	O
to	O
power	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
is	O
why	O
...	O
he	O
has	O
escaped	O
from	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
.	O
To	O
find	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300129
# text = And kill me.
And	O
kill	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300130
# text = Harry, swear to me that whatever you might hear... you won't go looking for Black.
Harry	B-PER
,	O
swear	O
to	O
me	O
that	O
whatever	O
you	O
might	O
hear	O
...	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
go	O
looking	O
for	O
Black	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300131
# text = Mr. Weasley... why would I go looking for someone who wants to kill me?
Mr.	O
Weasley	B-PER
...	O
why	O
would	O
I	O
go	O
looking	O
for	O
someone	O
who	O
wants	O
to	O
kill	O
me	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300132
# text = Quick. Quick. Ron, Ron! Oh, for goodness' sake! Don't lose him!
Quick	O
.	O
Quick	O
.	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
Ron	B-PER
!	O
Oh	O
,	O
for	O
goodness	O
'	O
sake	O
!	O
Do	O
n't	O
lose	O
him	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300133
# text = I didn't mean to blow her up. I just... I lost control.
I	O
did	O
n't	O
mean	O
to	O
blow	O
her	O
up	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
...	O
I	O
lost	O
control	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300134
# text = Brilliant.
Brilliant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300135
# text = Honestly, Ron, it's not funny. Harry was lucky not to be expelled.
Honestly	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
funny	O
.	O
Harry	B-PER
was	O
lucky	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
expelled	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300136
# text = I think I was lucky not to be arrested actually.
I	O
think	O
I	O
was	O
lucky	O
not	O
to	O
be	O
arrested	O
actually	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300137
# text = I still think it was brilliant.
I	O
still	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
brilliant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300138
# text = Come on. Everywhere else is full.
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Everywhere	O
else	O
is	O
full	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300139
# text = Who do you think that is?
Who	O
do	O
you	O
think	O
that	O
is	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300140
# text = Professor R.J. Lupin.
Professor	B-PER
R	I-PER
.	O
J	I-PER
.	O
Lupin	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300141
# text = Do you know everything? How is it she knows everything?
Do	O
you	O
know	O
everything	O
?	O
How	O
is	O
it	O
she	O
knows	O
everything	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300142
# text = It's on his suitcase, Ronald.
It	O
's	O
on	O
his	O
suitcase	O
,	O
Ronald	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300143
# text = Oh.
Oh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300144
# text = Do you think he's really asleep?
Do	O
you	O
think	O
he	O
's	O
really	O
asleep	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300145
# text = Seems to be. Why?
Seems	O
to	O
be	O
.	O
Why	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300146
# text = I gotta tell you something.
I	O
gotta	O
tell	O
you	O
something	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300147
# text = Let me get this straight. Sirius Black has escaped from Azkaban to come after you?
Let	O
me	O
get	O
this	O
straight	O
.	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
has	O
escaped	O
from	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
to	O
come	O
after	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300148
# text = Yeah.
Yeah	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300149
# text = But they'll catch Black, won't they? I mean, everyone's looking for him.
But	O
they	O
'll	O
catch	O
Black	B-PER
,	O
wo	O
n't	O
they	O
?	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
everyone	O
's	O
looking	O
for	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300150
# text = Sure. Except no one's ever broken out of Azkaban before... and he's a murderous, raving lunatic.
Sure	O
.	O
Except	O
no	O
one	O
's	O
ever	O
broken	O
out	O
of	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
before	O
...	O
and	O
he	O
's	O
a	O
murderous	O
,	O
raving	O
lunatic	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300151
# text = Thanks, Ron.
Thanks	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300152
# text = Why are we stopping? We can't be there yet.
Why	O
are	O
we	O
stopping	O
?	O
We	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
there	O
yet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300153
# text = What's going on?
What	O
's	O
going	O
on	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300154
# text = I don't know. Maybe we've broken down.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O
Maybe	O
we	O
've	O
broken	O
down	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300155
# text = Ouch, Ron. That was my foot.
Ouch	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
.	O
That	O
was	O
my	O
foot	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300156
# text = There's something moving out there. I think... someone's coming aboard.
There	O
's	O
something	O
moving	O
out	O
there	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
...	O
someone	O
's	O
coming	O
aboard	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300157
# text = Bloody hell! What's happening?
Bloody	O
hell	O
!	O
What	O
's	O
happening	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300158
# text = Harry. Harry, are you all right?
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
are	O
you	O
all	O
right	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300159
# text = Thank you.
Thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300160
# text = Here, eat this. It'll help. It's all right. It's chocolate.
Here	O
,	O
eat	O
this	O
.	O
It	O
'll	O
help	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
all	O
right	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
chocolate	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300161
# text = What was that thing that came?
What	O
was	O
that	O
thing	O
that	O
came	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300162
# text = It was a dementor. One of the guards of Azkaban. It's gone now. It was searching the train for Sirius Black. If you'll excuse me, I need to have a little word with the driver. Eat. You'll feel better.
It	O
was	O
a	O
dementor	B-CRT
.	O
One	O
of	O
the	O
guards	O
of	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
.	O
It	O
's	O
gone	O
now	O
.	O
It	O
was	O
searching	O
the	O
train	O
for	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
.	O
If	O
you	O
'll	O
excuse	O
me	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
have	O
a	O
little	O
word	O
with	O
the	O
driver	O
.	O
Eat	O
.	O
You	O
'll	O
feel	O
better	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300163
# text = What happened to me?
What	O
happened	O
to	O
me	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300164
# text = Well, you sort of went rigid. We thought maybe you were having a fit or something.
Well	O
,	O
you	O
sort	O
of	O
went	O
rigid	O
.	O
We	O
thought	O
maybe	O
you	O
were	O
having	O
a	O
fit	O
or	O
something	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300165
# text = And did either of you two... you know... pass out?
And	O
did	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
two	O
...	O
you	O
know	O
...	O
pass	O
out	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300166
# text = No. I felt weird, though. Like I'd never be cheerful again.
No	O
.	O
I	O
felt	O
weird	O
,	O
though	O
.	O
Like	O
I	O
'd	O
never	O
be	O
cheerful	O
again	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300167
# text = But someone was screaming. A woman.
But	O
someone	O
was	O
screaming	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300168
# text = No one was screaming, Harry.
No	O
one	O
was	O
screaming	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300169
# text = Welcome! Welcome to another year at Hogwarts! Now, I'd like to say a few words... before we all become too befuddled by our excellent feast. First, I'm pleased to welcome Professor R.J. Lupin... who's kindly consented to fill the post... of Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher. Good luck, Professor.
Welcome	O
!	O
Welcome	O
to	O
another	O
year	O
at	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
!	O
Now	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
...	O
before	O
we	O
all	O
become	O
too	O
befuddled	O
by	O
our	O
excellent	O
feast	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
pleased	O
to	O
welcome	O
Professor	O
R	B-PER
.	O
J	I-PER
.	O
Lupin	I-PER
...	O
who	O
's	O
kindly	O
consented	O
to	O
fill	O
the	O
post	O
...	O
of	O
Defense	B-CRS
Against	I-CRS
the	I-CRS
Dark	I-CRS
Arts	I-CRS
teacher	O
.	O
Good	O
luck	O
,	O
Professor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300170
# text = Of course. That's why he knew to give you the chocolate, Harry.
Of	O
course	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
why	O
he	O
knew	O
to	O
give	O
you	O
the	O
chocolate	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300171
# text = Potter. Is it true you fainted? I mean, you actually fainted?
Potter	B-PER
.	O
Is	O
it	O
true	O
you	O
fainted	O
?	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
you	O
actually	O
fainted	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300172
# text = Shove off, Malfoy.
Shove	O
off	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300173
# text = How did he find out?
How	O
did	O
he	O
find	O
out	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300174
# text = Just forget it.
Just	O
forget	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300175
# text = Our Care of Magical Creatures teacher... has decided to retire... in order to spend more time with his remaining limbs. Fortunately, I'm delighted to announce... that his place will be taken by none other... than our own Rubeus Hagrid. Finally, on a more disquieting note... at the request of the Ministry of Magic... Hogwarts will, until further notice, play host to the dementors of Azkaban... until such a time as Sirius Black is captured. The dementors will be stationed at every entrance to the grounds. Now whilst I've been assured... that their presence will not disrupt our day-to-day activities... a word of caution. Dementors are vicious creatures. They'll not distinguish... between the one they hunt and the one who gets in their way. Therefore, I must warn each and every one of you... to give them no reason to harm you. It is not in the nature of a dementor to be forgiving. But you know, happiness can be found... even in the darkest of times... if one only remembers to turn on the light.
Our	O
Care	B-CRS
of	I-CRS
Magical	I-CRS
Creatures	I-CRS
teacher	O
...	O
has	O
decided	O
to	O
retire	O
...	O
in	O
order	O
to	O
spend	O
more	O
time	O
with	O
his	O
remaining	O
limbs	O
.	O
Fortunately	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
delighted	O
to	O
announce	O
...	O
that	O
his	O
place	O
will	O
be	O
taken	O
by	O
none	O
other	O
...	O
than	O
our	O
own	O
Rubeus	B-PER
Hagrid	I-PER
.	O
Finally	O
,	O
on	O
a	O
more	O
disquieting	O
note	O
...	O
at	O
the	O
request	O
of	O
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
of	I-ORG
Magic	I-ORG
...	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
will	O
,	O
until	O
further	O
notice	O
,	O
play	O
host	O
to	O
the	O
dementors	B-CRT
of	O
Azkaban	B-ORG
...	O
until	O
such	O
a	O
time	O
as	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
is	O
captured	O
.	O
The	O
dementors	B-CRT
will	O
be	O
stationed	O
at	O
every	O
entrance	O
to	O
the	O
grounds	O
.	O
Now	O
whilst	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
assured	O
...	O
that	O
their	O
presence	O
will	O
not	O
disrupt	O
our	O
day	O
to	O
day	O
activities	O
...	O
a	O
word	O
of	O
caution	O
.	O
Dementors	B-CRT
are	O
vicious	O
creatures	O
.	O
They	O
'll	O
not	O
distinguish	O
...	O
between	O
the	O
one	O
they	O
hunt	O
and	O
the	O
one	O
who	O
gets	O
in	O
their	O
way	O
.	O
Therefore	O
,	O
I	O
must	O
warn	O
each	O
and	O
every	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
...	O
to	O
give	O
them	O
no	O
reason	O
to	O
harm	O
you	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
not	O
in	O
the	O
nature	O
of	O
a	O
dementor	B-CRT
to	O
be	O
forgiving	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
happiness	O
can	O
be	O
found	O
...	O
even	O
in	O
the	O
darkest	O
of	O
times	O
...	O
if	O
one	O
only	O
remembers	O
to	O
turn	O
on	O
the	O
light	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300176
# text = Fortuna Major. Here, listen. She just won't let me in. Fortuna Major.
Fortuna	O
Major	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
listen	O
.	O
She	O
just	O
wo	O
n't	O
let	O
me	O
in	O
.	O
Fortuna	O
Major	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300177
# text = No, no, no. Wait, wait. Watch this. Oh, amazing! Just with my voice.
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Wait	O
,	O
wait	O
.	O
Watch	O
this	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
amazing	O
!	O
Just	O
with	O
my	O
voice	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300178
# text = Fortuna Major.
Fortuna	O
Major	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300179
# text = Yes, all right. Go in.
Yes	O
,	O
all	O
right	O
.	O
Go	O
in	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300180
# text = Thank you.
Thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300181
# text = She's still doing that after three years. She can't even sing. Exactly. Hey, man. Hey, man. Oh, God. That's awful.
She	O
's	O
still	O
doing	O
that	O
after	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
ca	O
n't	O
even	O
sing	O
.	O
Exactly	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
God	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
awful	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300182
# text = She's still doing that after three years. She can't even sing. Exactly. Hey, man. Hey, man. Oh, God. That's awful.
She	O
's	O
still	O
doing	O
that	O
after	O
three	O
years	O
.	O
She	O
ca	O
n't	O
even	O
sing	O
.	O
Exactly	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
man	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
God	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
awful	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300183
# text = . Green. That's a monkey. What is that? You call that a monkey? Do not give him one again. Hey, Neville, try an elephant.
.	O
Green	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
a	O
monkey	O
.	O
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
You	O
call	O
that	O
a	O
monkey	O
?	O
Do	O
not	O
give	O
him	O
one	O
again	O
.	O
Hey	O
,	O
Neville	B-PER
,	O
try	O
an	O
elephant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300184
# text = Ron, catch.
Ron	B-PER
,	O
catch	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300185
# text = I will.
I	O
will	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300186
# text = I think we have a winner.
I	O
think	O
we	O
have	O
a	O
winner	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300187
# text = Oh, don't try one of them. Oh, no. Look at him. His face.
Oh	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
try	O
one	O
of	O
them	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
His	O
face	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300188
# text = Welcome, my children. In this room, you shall explore the noble art of Divination. In this room, you shall discover if you possess the Sight. Hello. I am Professor Trelawney. Together we shall cast ourselves into the future. This term, we'll focus on Tasseomancy, the art of reading tea leaves. So please, take the cup of the person sitting opposite you. What do you see? The truth lies buried like a sentence deep within a book, waiting to be read. But first, you must broaden your minds. First, you must look beyond.
Welcome	O
,	O
my	O
children	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
explore	O
the	O
noble	O
art	O
of	O
Divination	O
.	O
In	O
this	O
room	O
,	O
you	O
shall	O
discover	O
if	O
you	O
possess	O
the	O
Sight	O
.	O
Hello	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Professor	O
Trelawney	B-PER
.	O
Together	O
we	O
shall	O
cast	O
ourselves	O
into	O
the	O
future	O
.	O
This	O
term	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
focus	O
on	O
Tasseomancy	B-CRS
,	O
the	O
art	O
of	O
reading	O
tea	O
leaves	O
.	O
So	O
please	O
,	O
take	O
the	O
cup	O
of	O
the	O
person	O
sitting	O
opposite	O
you	O
.	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
see	O
?	O
The	O
truth	O
lies	O
buried	O
like	O
a	O
sentence	O
deep	O
within	O
a	O
book	O
,	O
waiting	O
to	O
be	O
read	O
.	O
But	O
first	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
broaden	O
your	O
minds	O
.	O
First	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
look	O
beyond	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300189
# text = What a load of rubbish.
What	O
a	O
load	O
of	O
rubbish	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300190
# text = Where did you come from?
Where	O
did	O
you	O
come	O
from	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300191
# text = Me? I've been here all this time.
Me	O
?	O
I	O
've	O
been	O
here	O
all	O
this	O
time	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300192
# text = You, boy... Is your grandmother quite well?
You	O
,	O
boy	O
...	O
Is	O
your	O
grandmother	O
quite	O
well	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300193
# text = I think so.
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300194
# text = I wouldn't be so sure of that. Give me the cup. Pity. Broaden your minds. Your aura is pulsing, dear. Are you in the beyond? I think you are.
I	O
would	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
sure	O
of	O
that	O
.	O
Give	O
me	O
the	O
cup	O
.	O
Pity	O
.	O
Broaden	O
your	O
minds	O
.	O
Your	O
aura	O
is	O
pulsing	O
,	O
dear	O
.	O
Are	O
you	O
in	O
the	O
beyond	O
?	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
are	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300195
# text = Sure.
Sure	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300196
# text = Look at the cup. Tell me what you see.
Look	O
at	O
the	O
cup	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
what	O
you	O
see	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300197
# text = Oh, yeah. Um... Well, Harry's got sort of a wonky cross. That's trials and suffering. And that there could be the sun and that's happiness. So... you're gonna suffer, but you're gonna be... happy about it.
Oh	O
,	O
yeah	O
.	O
Um	O
...	O
Well	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
's	O
got	O
sort	O
of	O
a	O
wonky	O
cross	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
trials	O
and	O
suffering	O
.	O
And	O
that	O
there	O
could	O
be	O
the	O
sun	O
and	O
that	O
's	O
happiness	O
.	O
So	O
...	O
you	O
're	O
gonna	O
suffer	O
,	O
but	O
you	O
're	O
gonna	O
be	O
...	O
happy	O
about	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300198
# text = Give me the cup. Oh, my dear boy. My dear... you have the Grim.
Give	O
me	O
the	O
cup	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
my	O
dear	O
boy	O
.	O
My	O
dear	O
...	O
you	O
have	O
the	O
Grim	B-CRT
.	O

# sent_id = 300199
# text = The Grin? What's the Grin? Not the Grin, you idiot. The Grim. Taking form of a giant spectral dog. It's among the darkest omens in our world. It's an omen... of death.
The	O
Grin	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
Grin	O
?	O
Not	O
the	O
Grin	O
,	O
you	O
idiot	O
.	O
The	O
Grim	B-CRT
.	O
Taking	O
form	O
of	O
a	O
giant	O
spectral	O
dog	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
among	O
the	O
darkest	O
omens	O
in	O
our	O
world	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
an	O
omen	O
...	O
of	O
death	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300200
# text = You don't think that Grim thing's got anything to do with Sirius Black?
You	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
that	O
Grim	B-CRT
thing	O
's	O
got	O
anything	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300201
# text = Oh, honestly, Ron. If you ask me, Divination's a woolly discipline. Now, Ancient Runes, that's a fascinating subject.
Oh	O
,	O
honestly	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
.	O
If	O
you	O
ask	O
me	O
,	O
Divination	B-CRS
's	O
a	O
woolly	O
discipline	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Ancient	B-CRS
Runes	I-CRS
,	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
fascinating	O
subject	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300202
# text = Ancient Runes? Exactly how many classes are you taking?
Ancient	B-CRS
Runes	I-CRS
?	O
Exactly	O
how	O
many	O
classes	O
are	O
you	O
taking	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300203
# text = A fair few.
A	O
fair	O
few	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300204
# text = Hang on. That's not possible. Ancient Runes is in the same time as Divination. You have to be in two classes at once.
Hang	O
on	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
not	O
possible	O
.	O
Ancient	B-CRS
Runes	I-CRS
is	O
in	O
the	O
same	O
time	O
as	O
Divination	B-CRS
.	O
You	O
have	O
to	O
be	O
in	O
two	O
classes	O
at	O
once	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300205
# text = Don't be silly Ron. How could anyone be in two classes at once? Broaden your minds. Use your Inner Eye to see the future!.
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
silly	O
Ron	B-PER
.	O
How	O
could	O
anyone	O
be	O
in	O
two	O
classes	O
at	O
once	O
?	O
Broaden	O
your	O
minds	O
.	O
Use	O
your	O
Inner	O
Eye	O
to	O
see	O
the	O
future	O
!	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300206
# text = That's it. Come on, now. Come closer. Less talking, if you don't mind. I got a real treat for you today. A great lesson. So follow me. Right, you lot. Less chattering. Form a group over there. And open your books to page 49.
That	O
's	O
it	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
now	O
.	O
Come	O
closer	O
.	O
Less	O
talking	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
a	O
real	O
treat	O
for	O
you	O
today	O
.	O
A	O
great	O
lesson	O
.	O
So	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
Right	O
,	O
you	O
lot	O
.	O
Less	O
chattering	O
.	O
Form	O
a	O
group	O
over	O
there	O
.	O
And	O
open	O
your	O
books	O
to	O
page	O
49	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300207
# text = Exactly how do we do that?
Exactly	O
how	O
do	O
we	O
do	O
that	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300208
# text = Just stroke the spine, of course. Goodness me.
Just	O
stroke	O
the	O
spine	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
Goodness	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300209
# text = Don't be such a wimp, Longbottom.
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
such	O
a	O
wimp	O
,	O
Longbottom	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300210
# text = I'm okay. Okay.
I	O
'm	O
okay	O
.	O
Okay	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300211
# text = I think they're funny.
I	O
think	O
they	O
're	O
funny	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300212
# text = Oh, yeah. Terribly funny. Really Witty. God, this place has gone to the dogs. Wait until Father hears Dumbledore's got this oaf teaching classes.
Oh	O
,	O
yeah	O
.	O
Terribly	O
funny	O
.	O
Really	O
Witty	O
.	O
God	O
,	O
this	O
place	O
has	O
gone	O
to	O
the	O
dogs	O
.	O
Wait	O
until	O
Father	O
hears	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
's	O
got	O
this	O
oaf	O
teaching	O
classes	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300213
# text = Shut up, Malfoy.
Shut	O
up	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300214
# text = D-Dementor! Dementor!
D	O
Dementor	B-CRT
!	O
Dementor	B-CRT
!	O

# sent_id = 300215
# text = Just ignore him.
Just	O
ignore	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300216
# text = You're supposed to stroke it.
You	O
're	O
supposed	O
to	O
stroke	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300217
# text = Yeah.
Yeah	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300218
# text = Isn't he beautiful? Say hello to Buckbeak.
Is	O
n't	O
he	O
beautiful	O
?	O
Say	O
hello	O
to	O
Buckbeak	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300219
# text = Hagrid, exactly what is that?
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
exactly	O
what	O
is	O
that	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300220
# text = That, Ron, is a hippogriff. First thing you wanna know about hippogriffs is that they're very proud creatures. Very easily offended. You do not want to insult a hippogriff. It may just be the last thing you ever do. Now, who'd like to come and say hello? Well done, Harry. Well done. Come on now. Now... you have to let him make the first move. It's only polite. So... step up. Give him a nice bow. Then you wait and see if he bows back. If he does, you can go and touch him. If not... Well, we'll get to that later. Just make your bow. Nice and low. Back off, Harry. Back off. Keep still. Keep still. Well done, Harry. Well done. Here, you big brute, you. Right. I think you can go and pat him now. Go on. Don't be shy. Nice and slow, now. Nice and slow. Slow. Not so fast, Harry. Slow down, Harry. That's it... Nice and slow. Now let him come to you. Slowly, now, slowly, slowly... That's it... Yes! Well done! Well done, Harry, well done! I think he may let you ride him now.
That	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
is	O
a	O
hippogriff	B-CRS
.	O
First	O
thing	O
you	O
wanna	O
know	O
about	O
hippogriffs	B-CRS
is	O
that	O
they	O
're	O
very	O
proud	O
creatures	O
.	O
Very	O
easily	O
offended	O
.	O
You	O
do	O
not	O
want	O
to	O
insult	O
a	O
hippogriff	B-CRS
.	O
It	O
may	O
just	O
be	O
the	O
last	O
thing	O
you	O
ever	O
do	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
who	O
'd	O
like	O
to	O
come	O
and	O
say	O
hello	O
?	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Well	O
done	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
now	O
.	O
Now	O
...	O
you	O
have	O
to	O
let	O
him	O
make	O
the	O
first	O
move	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
only	O
polite	O
.	O
So	O
...	O
step	O
up	O
.	O
Give	O
him	O
a	O
nice	O
bow	O
.	O
Then	O
you	O
wait	O
and	O
see	O
if	O
he	O
bows	O
back	O
.	O
If	O
he	O
does	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
and	O
touch	O
him	O
.	O
If	O
not	O
...	O
Well	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
get	O
to	O
that	O
later	O
.	O
Just	O
make	O
your	O
bow	O
.	O
Nice	O
and	O
low	O
.	O
Back	O
off	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Back	O
off	O
.	O
Keep	O
still	O
.	O
Keep	O
still	O
.	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Well	O
done	O
.	O
Here	O
,	O
you	O
big	O
brute	O
,	O
you	O
.	O
Right	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
and	O
pat	O
him	O
now	O
.	O
Go	O
on	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
be	O
shy	O
.	O
Nice	O
and	O
slow	O
,	O
now	O
.	O
Nice	O
and	O
slow	O
.	O
Slow	O
.	O
Not	O
so	O
fast	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Slow	O
down	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
That	O
's	O
it	O
...	O
Nice	O
and	O
slow	O
.	O
Now	O
let	O
him	O
come	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
Slowly	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
slowly	O
,	O
slowly	O
...	O
That	O
's	O
it	O
...	O
Yes	O
!	O
Well	O
done	O
!	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
well	O
done	O
!	O
I	O
think	O
he	O
may	O
let	O
you	O
ride	O
him	O
now	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300221
# text = What?
What	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300222
# text = Come on.
Come	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300223
# text = Hey, hey, hey!
Hey	O
,	O
hey	O
,	O
hey	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300224
# text = Put you over here, just behind the wing joint. Don't pull out any of his feathers, because he won't thank you for that. Well done, Harry, and well done, Buckbeak.
Put	O
you	O
over	O
here	O
,	O
just	O
behind	O
the	O
wing	O
joint	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
pull	O
out	O
any	O
of	O
his	O
feathers	O
,	O
because	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
thank	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
.	O
Well	O
done	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
and	O
well	O
done	O
,	O
Buckbeak	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300225
# text = That was wicked, Harry!
That	O
was	O
wicked	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300226
# text = Oh, please.
Oh	O
,	O
please	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300227
# text = Well done, well done. How am I doing me first day?
Well	O
done	O
,	O
well	O
done	O
.	O
How	O
am	O
I	O
doing	O
me	O
first	O
day	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300228
# text = Brilliant, professor.
Brilliant	O
,	O
professor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300229
# text = Yes you're not dangerous at all, are you, you great ugly brute!
Yes	O
you	O
're	O
not	O
dangerous	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
,	O
you	O
great	O
ugly	O
brute	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300230
# text = Malfoy, no... No! Buckbeak! Whoa, whoa, whoa... Whoa! Buckbeak! Away, you silly creature!
Malfoy	B-PER
,	O
no	O
...	O
No	O
!	O
Buckbeak	B-PER
!	O
Whoa	O
,	O
whoa	O
,	O
whoa	O
...	O
Whoa	O
!	O
Buckbeak	B-PER
!	O
Away	O
,	O
you	O
silly	O
creature	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300231
# text = It's killed me! It's killed me!
It	O
's	O
killed	O
me	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
killed	O
me	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300232
# text = Calm down! It's just a scratch!
Calm	O
down	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
just	O
a	O
scratch	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300233
# text = Hagrid! He has to be taken to the hospital.
Hagrid	B-PER
!	O
He	O
has	O
to	O
be	O
taken	O
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300234
# text = I'm the teacher. I'll do it.
I	O
'm	O
the	O
teacher	O
.	O
I	O
'll	O
do	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300235
# text = Oh You're gonna regret this.
Oh	O
You	O
're	O
gonna	O
regret	O
this	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300236
# text = Class dismissed!
Class	O
dismissed	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300237
# text = You and your bloody chicken!
You	O
and	O
your	O
bloody	O
chicken	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300238
# text = Does it hurt terribly, Draco?
Does	O
it	O
hurt	O
terribly	O
,	O
Draco	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300239
# text = It comes and it goes. Still, I consider myself lucky. Madam Pomfrey said another minute and I could've lost my arm. I couldn't do homework for weeks.
It	O
comes	O
and	O
it	O
goes	O
.	O
Still	O
,	O
I	O
consider	O
myself	O
lucky	O
.	O
Madam	O
Pomfrey	B-PER
said	O
another	O
minute	O
and	O
I	O
could	O
've	O
lost	O
my	O
arm	O
.	O
I	O
could	O
n't	O
do	O
homework	O
for	O
weeks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300240
# text = Listen to the idiot. He's really laying it on thick, isn't he?
Listen	O
to	O
the	O
idiot	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
really	O
laying	O
it	O
on	O
thick	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
he	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300241
# text = At least Hagrid didn't get fired.
At	O
least	O
Hagrid	B-PER
did	O
n't	O
get	O
fired	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300242
# text = Yeah but I heard Draco's father's furious. We haven't heard the end of this.
Yeah	O
but	O
I	O
heard	O
Draco	B-PER
's	O
father	O
's	O
furious	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
n't	O
heard	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
this	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300243
# text = He's been sighted! He's been sighted!
He	O
's	O
been	O
sighted	O
!	O
He	O
's	O
been	O
sighted	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300244
# text = Who?
Who	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300245
# text = Sirius Black!
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300246
# text = Dufftown? That's not far from here.
Dufftown	B-LOC
?	O
That	O
's	O
not	O
far	O
from	O
here	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300247
# text = You don't think he'd come to Hogwarts, do you? With dementors at every entrance?
You	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
he	O
'd	O
come	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
,	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
With	O
dementors	B-CRT
at	O
every	O
entrance	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300248
# text = Dementors? He's already slipped past them once. Who's to say he won't do it again?
Dementors	B-CRT
?	O
He	O
's	O
already	O
slipped	O
past	O
them	O
once	O
.	O
Who	O
's	O
to	O
say	O
he	O
wo	O
n't	O
do	O
it	O
again	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300249
# text = That's right. Black could be anywhere. It's like trying to catch smoke. Like trying to catch smoke with your bare hands.
That	O
's	O
right	O
.	O
Black	B-PER
could	O
be	O
anywhere	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
like	O
trying	O
to	O
catch	O
smoke	O
.	O
Like	O
trying	O
to	O
catch	O
smoke	O
with	O
your	O
bare	O
hands	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300250
# text = Intriguing, isn't it? Would anyone like to venture a guess... as to what is inside?
Intriguing	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
it	O
?	O
Would	O
anyone	O
like	O
to	O
venture	O
a	O
guess	O
...	O
as	O
to	O
what	O
is	O
inside	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300251
# text = That's a boggart, that is.
That	O
's	O
a	O
boggart	B-CRS
,	O
that	O
is	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300252
# text = Very good, Mr. Thomas. Now, can anybody tell me what a boggart looks like?
Very	O
good	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Thomas	B-PER
.	O
Now	O
,	O
can	O
anybody	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
a	O
boggart	B-CRS
looks	O
like	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300253
# text = No one knows.
No	O
one	O
knows	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300254
# text = When did she get here?
When	O
did	O
she	O
get	O
here	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300255
# text = Boggarts are shape-shifters. They take the shape of whatever a particular person fears the most. That's what makes them so...
Boggarts	B-CRS
are	O
shape	O
shifters	O
.	O
They	O
take	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
whatever	O
a	O
particular	O
person	O
fears	O
the	O
most	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
makes	O
them	O
so	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300256
# text = So terrifying, yes, yes, yes... Luckily, a very simple charm exists to repel a boggart. Let's practice it now. Without wands, please. After me. Riddikulus!
So	O
terrifying	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
yes	O
...	O
Luckily	O
,	O
a	O
very	O
simple	O
charm	O
exists	O
to	O
repel	O
a	O
boggart	B-CRS
.	O
Let	O
's	O
practice	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Without	O
wands	O
,	O
please	O
.	O
After	O
me	O
.	O
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300257
# text = Riddikulus!
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300258
# text = Very good. A little louder and very clear. Listen: Riddikulus!
Very	O
good	O
.	O
A	O
little	O
louder	O
and	O
very	O
clear	O
.	O
Listen	O
:	O
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300259
# text = Riddikulus!
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300260
# text = This class is ridiculous.
This	O
class	O
is	O
ridiculous	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300261
# text = Very good. So much for the easy part. You see, the incantation alone is not enough. What really finishes a boggart is laughter. You need to force it to assume a shape you find truly amusing. Let me explain. Uh... Neville, would you join me, please? Come on, don't be shy. Come on. Come on. Hello. Neville, what frightens you most of all?
Very	O
good	O
.	O
So	O
much	O
for	O
the	O
easy	O
part	O
.	O
You	O
see	O
,	O
the	O
incantation	O
alone	O
is	O
not	O
enough	O
.	O
What	O
really	O
finishes	O
a	O
boggart	B-CRS
is	O
laughter	O
.	O
You	O
need	O
to	O
force	O
it	O
to	O
assume	O
a	O
shape	O
you	O
find	O
truly	O
amusing	O
.	O
Let	O
me	O
explain	O
.	O
Uh	O
...	O
Neville	B-PER
,	O
would	O
you	O
join	O
me	O
,	O
please	O
?	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
shy	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Hello	O
.	O
Neville	B-PER
,	O
what	O
frightens	O
you	O
most	O
of	O
all	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300262
# text = Professor Snape.
Professor	O
Snape	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300263
# text = Sorry?
Sorry	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300264
# text = Professor Snape.
Professor	O
Snape	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300265
# text = Professor Snape. Yes, frightens all. And I believe you live with your grandmother.
Professor	O
Snape	B-PER
.	O
Yes	O
,	O
frightens	O
all	O
.	O
And	O
I	O
believe	O
you	O
live	O
with	O
your	O
grandmother	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300266
# text = Y-Yes but I don't want that boggart to turn into her, either.
Y	O
Yes	O
but	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
that	O
boggart	B-CRS
to	O
turn	O
into	O
her	O
,	O
either	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300267
# text = No... it won't. I want you to picture her clothes. Only her clothes, very clearly, in your mind.
No	O
...	O
it	O
wo	O
n't	O
.	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
picture	O
her	O
clothes	O
.	O
Only	O
her	O
clothes	O
,	O
very	O
clearly	O
,	O
in	O
your	O
mind	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300268
# text = She carries a red handbag...
She	O
carries	O
a	O
red	O
handbag	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300269
# text = We don't need to hear. As long as you see it, we'll see it. Now, when I open that wardrobe... here's what I want you to do. Excuse me. Imagine Professor Snape in your grandmother's clothes. Can you do that? Yes. Wand at the ready. One, two, three. Think, Neville, think.
We	O
do	O
n't	O
need	O
to	O
hear	O
.	O
As	O
long	O
as	O
you	O
see	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
'll	O
see	O
it	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
when	O
I	O
open	O
that	O
wardrobe	O
...	O
here	O
's	O
what	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Excuse	O
me	O
.	O
Imagine	O
Professor	O
Snape	B-PER
in	O
your	O
grandmother	O
's	O
clothes	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
do	O
that	O
?	O
Yes	O
.	O
Wand	O
at	O
the	O
ready	O
.	O
One	O
,	O
two	O
,	O
three	O
.	O
Think	O
,	O
Neville	B-PER
,	O
think	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300270
# text = Riddikulus!
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300271
# text = Wonderful, Neville, wonderful! Incredible! Okay... to the back, Neville. Everyone, form a line! Form a line! I want everyone to picture the thing they fear the very most... and turn it into something funny. Next! Ron! Concentrate. Face your fear. Be brave! Wand at the ready, Ron, wand at the ready.
Wonderful	O
,	O
Neville	B-PER
,	O
wonderful	O
!	O
Incredible	O
!	O
Okay	O
...	O
to	O
the	O
back	O
,	O
Neville	B-PER
.	O
Everyone	O
,	O
form	O
a	O
line	O
!	O
Form	O
a	O
line	O
!	O
I	O
want	O
everyone	O
to	O
picture	O
the	O
thing	O
they	O
fear	O
the	O
very	O
most	O
...	O
and	O
turn	O
it	O
into	O
something	O
funny	O
.	O
Next	O
!	O
Ron	B-PER
!	O
Concentrate	O
.	O
Face	O
your	O
fear	O
.	O
Be	O
brave	O
!	O
Wand	O
at	O
the	O
ready	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
wand	O
at	O
the	O
ready	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300272
# text = Riddikulus!
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300273
# text = Yes! You see? Very good, very good! Marvelous! Absolutely, very, very enjoyable! Parvati! Next! Show us what you see. Keep your nerve. Steady.
Yes	O
!	O
You	O
see	O
?	O
Very	O
good	O
,	O
very	O
good	O
!	O
Marvelous	O
!	O
Absolutely	O
,	O
very	O
,	O
very	O
enjoyable	O
!	O
Parvati	B-PER
!	O
Next	O
!	O
Show	O
us	O
what	O
you	O
see	O
.	O
Keep	O
your	O
nerve	O
.	O
Steady	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300274
# text = Riddikulus!
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300275
# text = And next! Step up, step up! Wonderful, wonderful! Here! Riddikulus! Right. Sorry about that. That's enough for today. Collect your books from the back. That's the end of the lesson. Thank you! Sorry! Sorry, you can have too much of a good thing.
And	O
next	O
!	O
Step	O
up	O
,	O
step	O
up	O
!	O
Wonderful	O
,	O
wonderful	O
!	O
Here	O
!	O
Riddikulus	B-SPL
!	O
Right	O
.	O
Sorry	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
enough	O
for	O
today	O
.	O
Collect	O
your	O
books	O
from	O
the	O
back	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
lesson	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
!	O
Sorry	O
!	O
Sorry	O
,	O
you	O
can	O
have	O
too	O
much	O
of	O
a	O
good	O
thing	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300276
# text = Now remember, these visits to Hogsmeade village are a privilege. Should your behavior reflect poorly on the school in anyway that privilege shall not be extended again. No permission form signed, no visiting the village. That's the rule, Potter.
Now	O
remember	O
,	O
these	O
visits	O
to	O
Hogsmeade	B-LOC
village	I-LOC
are	O
a	O
privilege	O
.	O
Should	O
your	O
behavior	O
reflect	O
poorly	O
on	O
the	O
school	O
in	O
anyway	O
that	O
privilege	O
shall	O
not	O
be	O
extended	O
again	O
.	O
No	O
permission	O
form	O
signed	O
,	O
no	O
visiting	O
the	O
village	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
rule	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300277
# text = Those with permission, follow me. Those without, stay put.
Those	O
with	O
permission	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
Those	O
without	O
,	O
stay	O
put	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300278
# text = But professor I thought if you signed it, then I could...
But	O
professor	O
I	O
thought	O
if	O
you	O
signed	O
it	O
,	O
then	O
I	O
could	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300279
# text = I can't. Only a parent or a guardian can sign. Since I am neither, it would be inappropriate. I'm sorry, Potter. That's my final word.
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
.	O
Only	O
a	O
parent	O
or	O
a	O
guardian	O
can	O
sign	O
.	O
Since	O
I	O
am	O
neither	O
,	O
it	O
would	O
be	O
inappropriate	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
That	O
's	O
my	O
final	O
word	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300280
# text = Forget about it, guys. See you later.
Forget	O
about	O
it	O
,	O
guys	O
.	O
See	O
you	O
later	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300281
# text = Professor, can I ask you something?
Professor	O
,	O
can	O
I	O
ask	O
you	O
something	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300282
# text = You want to know why I stopped you facing that boggart, yes? I would've thought it'd be obvious. I assumed it would take the shape of Lord Voldemort.
You	O
want	O
to	O
know	O
why	O
I	O
stopped	O
you	O
facing	O
that	O
boggart	B-CRS
,	O
yes	O
?	O
I	O
would	O
've	O
thought	O
it	O
'd	O
be	O
obvious	O
.	O
I	O
assumed	O
it	O
would	O
take	O
the	O
shape	O
of	O
Lord	O
Voldemort	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300283
# text = I did think of Voldemort at first. But then I remembered that night on the train... and the dementor.
I	O
did	O
think	O
of	O
Voldemort	B-PER
at	O
first	O
.	O
But	O
then	O
I	O
remembered	O
that	O
night	O
on	O
the	O
train	O
...	O
and	O
the	O
dementor	B-CRT
.	O

# sent_id = 300284
# text = I'm very impressed. That suggests what you fear the most is fear itself. This is very wise.
I	O
'm	O
very	O
impressed	O
.	O
That	O
suggests	O
what	O
you	O
fear	O
the	O
most	O
is	O
fear	O
itself	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
very	O
wise	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300285
# text = Before I fainted... I heard something. A woman... screaming.
Before	O
I	O
fainted	O
...	O
I	O
heard	O
something	O
.	O
A	O
woman	O
...	O
screaming	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300286
# text = Dementors force us to relive our very worst memories. Our pain becomes their power.
Dementors	B-CRT
force	O
us	O
to	O
relive	O
our	O
very	O
worst	O
memories	O
.	O
Our	O
pain	O
becomes	O
their	O
power	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300287
# text = I think it was my mother... the night she was murdered.
I	O
think	O
it	O
was	O
my	O
mother	O
...	O
the	O
night	O
she	O
was	O
murdered	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300288
# text = The very first time I saw you, Harry, I recognized you immediately. Not by your scar, by your eyes. They're your mother, Lily's. Yes. Oh, yes. I knew her. Your mother was there for me at a time when no one else was. Not only was she a singularly gifted witch... she was also an uncommonly kind woman. She had a way of seeing the beauty in others... even, and perhaps most especially, when that person could not see it in themselves. And your father, James, on the other hand... he... He had a certain, shall we say, talent for trouble. A talent, rumor has it, he passed on to you. You're more like them than you know, Harry. In time, you'll come to see just how much.
The	O
very	O
first	O
time	O
I	O
saw	O
you	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
I	O
recognized	O
you	O
immediately	O
.	O
Not	O
by	O
your	O
scar	O
,	O
by	O
your	O
eyes	O
.	O
They	O
're	O
your	O
mother	O
,	O
Lily	B-PER
's	O
.	O
Yes	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O
I	O
knew	O
her	O
.	O
Your	O
mother	O
was	O
there	O
for	O
me	O
at	O
a	O
time	O
when	O
no	O
one	O
else	O
was	O
.	O
Not	O
only	O
was	O
she	O
a	O
singularly	O
gifted	O
witch	O
...	O
she	O
was	O
also	O
an	O
uncommonly	O
kind	O
woman	O
.	O
She	O
had	O
a	O
way	O
of	O
seeing	O
the	O
beauty	O
in	O
others	O
...	O
even	O
,	O
and	O
perhaps	O
most	O
especially	O
,	O
when	O
that	O
person	O
could	O
not	O
see	O
it	O
in	O
themselves	O
.	O
And	O
your	O
father	O
,	O
James	B-PER
,	O
on	O
the	O
other	O
hand	O
...	O
he	O
...	O
He	O
had	O
a	O
certain	O
,	O
shall	O
we	O
say	O
,	O
talent	O
for	O
trouble	O
.	O
A	O
talent	O
,	O
rumor	O
has	O
it	O
,	O
he	O
passed	O
on	O
to	O
you	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
more	O
like	O
them	O
than	O
you	O
know	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
In	O
time	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
come	O
to	O
see	O
just	O
how	O
much	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300289
# text = Honeyduke's Sweetshop is brilliant, but nothing beats Zonko's Joke Shop. We never did got a chance to go to the Shrieking Shack though. You heard it's the most...
Honeyduke	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Sweetshop	I-ORG
is	O
brilliant	O
,	O
but	O
nothing	O
beats	O
Zonko	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
Joke	I-ORG
Shop	I-ORG
.	O
We	O
never	O
did	O
got	O
a	O
chance	O
to	O
go	O
to	O
the	O
Shrieking	B-LOC
Shack	I-LOC
though	O
.	O
You	O
heard	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
most	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300290
# text = The most haunted building in Britain. Yeah I know. What's going on?
The	O
most	O
haunted	O
building	O
in	O
Britain	B-LOC
.	O
Yeah	O
I	O
know	O
.	O
What	O
's	O
going	O
on	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300291
# text = Probably Neville forgotten the password again.
Probably	O
Neville	B-PER
forgotten	O
the	O
password	O
again	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300292
# text = Hey!.
Hey	O
!	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300293
# text = Oh, you're there.
Oh	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300294
# text = Let me through, please. Excuse me! I'm Head Boy! Get back, all of you. No one is to enter this dormitory until it's been searched.
Let	O
me	O
through	O
,	O
please	O
.	O
Excuse	O
me	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
Head	O
Boy	O
!	O
Get	O
back	O
,	O
all	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
No	O
one	O
is	O
to	O
enter	O
this	O
dormitory	O
until	O
it	O
's	O
been	O
searched	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300295
# text = The Fat Lady! She's gone!
The	O
Fat	B-PER
Lady	I-PER
!	O
She	O
's	O
gone	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300296
# text = Serves her right. She was a terrible singer.
Serves	O
her	O
right	O
.	O
She	O
was	O
a	O
terrible	O
singer	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300297
# text = It's not funny, Ron.
It	O
's	O
not	O
funny	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300298
# text = Keep calm, everyone. Break into fours. Back to your common room. Be quiet.
Keep	O
calm	O
,	O
everyone	O
.	O
Break	O
into	O
fours	O
.	O
Back	O
to	O
your	O
common	O
room	O
.	O
Be	O
quiet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300299
# text = Make way.
Make	O
way	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300300
# text = The headmaster's here.
The	O
headmaster	O
's	O
here	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300301
# text = Come on, move.
Come	O
on	O
,	O
move	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300302
# text = You heard. Move!
You	O
heard	O
.	O
Move	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300303
# text = Mr. Filch? Round up the ghosts. Tell them to search every painting in the castle to find the Fat Lady.
Mr.	O
Filch	B-PER
?	O
Round	O
up	O
the	O
ghosts	O
.	O
Tell	B-PER
them	O
to	O
search	O
every	O
painting	O
in	O
the	O
castle	O
to	O
find	O
the	O
Fat	B-PER
Lady	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300304
# text = There's no need for ghosts, professor. The Fat Lady's there.
There	O
's	O
no	O
need	O
for	O
ghosts	O
,	O
professor	O
.	O
The	O
Fat	B-PER
Lady	I-PER
's	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300305
# text = Mind where you're going! Slow down! You listen! I'm Head Boy! Come back here!
Mind	O
where	O
you	O
're	O
going	O
!	O
Slow	O
down	O
!	O
You	O
listen	O
!	O
I	O
'm	O
Head	O
Boy	O
!	O
Come	O
back	O
here	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300306
# text = Keep moving!
Keep	O
moving	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300307
# text = Dear lady, who did this to you?
Dear	O
lady	O
,	O
who	O
did	O
this	O
to	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300308
# text = Eyes like the devil, he's got, and a soul as dark as his name. It's him, headmaster. The one they all talk about. He's here, somewhere in the castle! Sirius Black!
Eyes	O
like	O
the	O
devil	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
got	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
soul	O
as	O
dark	O
as	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
him	O
,	O
headmaster	O
.	O
The	O
one	O
they	O
all	O
talk	O
about	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
here	O
,	O
somewhere	O
in	O
the	O
castle	O
!	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300309
# text = Secure the castle, Mr. Filch. The rest of you, to the Great Hall.
Secure	O
the	O
castle	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Filch	B-PER
.	O
The	O
rest	O
of	O
you	O
,	O
to	O
the	O
Great	B-LOC
Hall	I-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300310
# text = I've searched the Astronomy Tower and the Owlery, sir. But there's nothing there.
I	O
've	O
searched	O
the	O
Astronomy	B-LOC
Tower	I-LOC
and	O
the	O
Owlery	B-LOC
,	O
sir	O
.	O
But	O
there	O
's	O
nothing	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300311
# text = Ah, thank you.
Ah	O
,	O
thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300312
# text = The third floor's clear too, sir.
The	O
third	O
floor	O
's	O
clear	O
too	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300313
# text = Very good.
Very	O
good	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300314
# text = I've done the dungeons, headmaster. No sign of Black, nor anywhere else in the castle.
I	O
've	O
done	O
the	O
dungeons	O
,	O
headmaster	O
.	O
No	O
sign	O
of	O
Black	B-PER
,	O
nor	O
anywhere	O
else	O
in	O
the	O
castle	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300315
# text = I didn't really expect him to linger.
I	O
did	O
n't	O
really	O
expect	O
him	O
to	O
linger	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300316
# text = Remarkable feat, don't you think? To enter Hogwarts Castle on one's own... completely undetected?
Remarkable	O
feat	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
think	O
?	O
To	O
enter	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
Castle	I-ORG
on	O
one	O
's	O
own	O
...	O
completely	O
undetected	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300317
# text = Quite remarkable, yes.
Quite	O
remarkable	O
,	O
yes	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300318
# text = Any theories on how he managed it?
Any	O
theories	O
on	O
how	O
he	O
managed	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300319
# text = Many. Each as unlikely as the next.
Many	O
.	O
Each	O
as	O
unlikely	O
as	O
the	O
next	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300320
# text = You may recall... prior to the start of term I expressed concerns... about your appointment of Professor...
You	O
may	O
recall	O
...	O
prior	O
to	O
the	O
start	O
of	O
term	O
I	O
expressed	O
concerns	O
...	O
about	O
your	O
appointment	O
of	O
Professor	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300321
# text = Not a single professor inside this castle would help Sirius Black enter it. I'm quite convinced the castle is safe... and I'm more than willing to send the students back to their houses.
Not	O
a	O
single	O
professor	O
inside	O
this	O
castle	O
would	O
help	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
enter	O
it	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
quite	O
convinced	O
the	O
castle	O
is	O
safe	O
...	O
and	O
I	O
'm	O
more	O
than	O
willing	O
to	O
send	O
the	O
students	O
back	O
to	O
their	O
houses	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300322
# text = What about Potter? Should he be warned?
What	O
about	O
Potter	B-PER
?	O
Should	O
he	O
be	O
warned	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300323
# text = Perhaps. But for now, let him sleep. For in dreams, we enter a world that's entirely our own. Let them swim in the deepest ocean or glide over the highest cloud.
Perhaps	O
.	O
But	O
for	O
now	O
,	O
let	O
him	O
sleep	O
.	O
For	O
in	O
dreams	O
,	O
we	O
enter	O
a	O
world	O
that	O
's	O
entirely	O
our	O
own	O
.	O
Let	O
them	O
swim	O
in	O
the	O
deepest	O
ocean	O
or	O
glide	O
over	O
the	O
highest	O
cloud	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300324
# text = Turn to page 394.
Turn	O
to	O
page	O
394	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300325
# text = Excuse me, sir. Where's Professor Lupin?
Excuse	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Where	O
's	O
Professor	O
Lupin	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300326
# text = That's not really your concern, is it, Potter? Suffice it to say your professor finds himself incapable of teaching... at the present time. Turn to page 394.
That	O
's	O
not	O
really	O
your	O
concern	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
?	O
Suffice	O
it	O
to	O
say	O
your	O
professor	O
finds	O
himself	O
incapable	O
of	O
teaching	O
...	O
at	O
the	O
present	O
time	O
.	O
Turn	O
to	O
page	O
394	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300327
# text = Werewolves?
Werewolves	B-CRT
?	O

# sent_id = 300328
# text = But sir, we just learned about red caps and hinkypunks. We're not meant to start that for weeks.
But	O
sir	O
,	O
we	O
just	O
learned	O
about	O
red	B-CRT
caps	I-CRT
and	O
hinkypunks	B-CRT
.	O
We	O
're	O
not	O
meant	O
to	O
start	O
that	O
for	O
weeks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300329
# text = Quiet.
Quiet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300330
# text = When did she come in? Did you see her come in?
When	O
did	O
she	O
come	O
in	O
?	O
Did	O
you	O
see	O
her	O
come	O
in	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300331
# text = Now, which one of you can tell me the difference... between an Animagus and a werewolf? No one? How disappointing.
Now	O
,	O
which	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
can	O
tell	O
me	O
the	O
difference	O
...	O
between	O
an	O
Animagus	B-MAG
and	O
a	O
werewolf	B-CRT
?	O
No	O
one	O
?	O
How	O
disappointing	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300332
# text = Please, sir. An Animagus is a wizard who elects to turn into an animal. A werewolf has no choice. With each full moon, when he transforms, he no longer remembers who he is. He'd kill his best friend if he crossed his path. Furthermore, the werewolf only responds to the call of its own kind.
Please	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
An	O
Animagus	B-MAG
is	O
a	O
wizard	O
who	O
elects	O
to	O
turn	O
into	O
an	O
animal	O
.	O
A	O
werewolf	B-CRT
has	O
no	O
choice	O
.	O
With	O
each	O
full	O
moon	O
,	O
when	O
he	O
transforms	O
,	O
he	O
no	O
longer	O
remembers	O
who	O
he	O
is	O
.	O
He	O
'd	O
kill	O
his	O
best	O
friend	O
if	O
he	O
crossed	O
his	O
path	O
.	O
Furthermore	O
,	O
the	O
werewolf	B-CRT
only	O
responds	O
to	O
the	O
call	O
of	O
its	O
own	O
kind	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300333
# text = Thank you, Mr. Malfoy. That's the second time... you've spoken out of turn, Miss Granger. Are you incapable of restraining yourself... or do you take pride in being an insufferable know-it-all?
Thank	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Malfoy	B-PER
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
second	O
time	O
...	O
you	O
've	O
spoken	O
out	O
of	O
turn	O
,	O
Miss	O
Granger	B-PER
.	O
Are	O
you	O
incapable	O
of	O
restraining	O
yourself	O
...	O
or	O
do	O
you	O
take	O
pride	O
in	O
being	O
an	O
insufferable	O
know	O
it	O
all	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300334
# text = He's got a point, you know.
He	O
's	O
got	O
a	O
point	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300335
# text = Five points from Gryffindor. As an antidote to your ignorance, and on my desk, by Monday morning... two rolls of parchment on the werewolf, with emphasis... on recognizing it.
Five	O
points	O
from	O
Gryffindor	B-HOUSE
.	O
As	O
an	O
antidote	O
to	O
your	O
ignorance	O
,	O
and	O
on	O
my	O
desk	O
,	O
by	O
Monday	O
morning	O
...	O
two	O
rolls	O
of	O
parchment	O
on	O
the	O
werewolf	B-CRT
,	O
with	O
emphasis	O
...	O
on	O
recognizing	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300336
# text = Sir, it's Quidditch tomorrow.
Sir	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
Quidditch	B-MAG
tomorrow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300337
# text = Then I suggest you take extra care, Mr. Potter. Loss of limb will not excuse you. Page 394. The term werewolf... is a contraction of the Anglo-Saxon word were... which means man, and wolf. Werewolf, man-wolf. There are several ways to become a werewolf. They include being given the power of shape-shifting... being bitten by a werewolf...
Then	O
I	O
suggest	O
you	O
take	O
extra	O
care	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
Loss	O
of	O
limb	O
will	O
not	O
excuse	O
you	O
.	O
Page	O
394	O
.	O
The	O
term	O
werewolf	B-CRT
...	O
is	O
a	O
contraction	O
of	O
the	O
Anglo	O
Saxon	O
word	O
were	O
...	O
which	O
means	O
man	O
,	O
and	O
wolf	O
.	O
Werewolf	B-CRT
,	O
man	O
wolf	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
several	O
ways	O
to	O
become	O
a	O
werewolf	B-CRT
.	O
They	O
include	O
being	O
given	O
the	O
power	O
of	O
shape	O
shifting	O
...	O
being	O
bitten	O
by	O
a	O
werewolf	B-CRT
...	O

# sent_id = 300338
# text = Go, Harry! Go, Harry!
Go	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O
Go	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300339
# text = Arresto momentum!
Arresto	B-SPL
momentum	I-SPL
!	O

# sent_id = 300340
# text = He looks a bit peaky, doesn't he?
He	O
looks	O
a	O
bit	O
peaky	O
,	O
does	O
n't	O
he	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300341
# text = Peaky? What do you expect? He fell over 100 feet.
Peaky	O
?	O
What	O
do	O
you	O
expect	O
?	O
He	O
fell	O
over	O
100	O
feet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300342
# text = Yeah, come on Ron, let's walk you off the astronomy tower and see what you look like.
Yeah	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
let	O
's	O
walk	O
you	O
off	O
the	O
astronomy	B-LOC
tower	I-LOC
and	O
see	O
what	O
you	O
look	O
like	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300343
# text = Probably a right sight better than he normally does.
Probably	O
a	O
right	O
sight	O
better	O
than	O
he	O
normally	O
does	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300344
# text = How are you feeling?
How	O
are	O
you	O
feeling	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300345
# text = Oh, brilliant.
Oh	O
,	O
brilliant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300346
# text = You gave us a right good scare there, mate.
You	O
gave	O
us	O
a	O
right	O
good	O
scare	O
there	O
,	O
mate	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300347
# text = What happened?
What	O
happened	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300348
# text = Well, you fell off your broom.
Well	O
,	O
you	O
fell	O
off	O
your	O
broom	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300349
# text = Really? I meant the match. Who won?
Really	O
?	O
I	O
meant	O
the	O
match	O
.	O
Who	O
won	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300350
# text = Umm... no one blames you, Harry. The dementors aren't supposed to come inside the grounds. Dumbledore's furious. As soon as he saved you, he sent them off.
Umm	B-PER
...	O
no	O
one	O
blames	O
you	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
The	O
dementors	B-CRT
are	O
n't	O
supposed	O
to	O
come	O
inside	O
the	O
grounds	O
.	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
's	O
furious	O
.	O
As	O
soon	O
as	O
he	O
saved	O
you	O
,	O
he	O
sent	O
them	O
off	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300351
# text = There's something else you should know too. When you fell, your broom sort of blew into the Whomping Willow, and... Well...
There	O
's	O
something	O
else	O
you	O
should	O
know	O
too	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
fell	O
,	O
your	O
broom	O
sort	O
of	O
blew	O
into	O
the	O
Whomping	B-MAG
Willow	I-MAG
,	O
and	O
...	O
Well	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300352
# text = I'm sorry to hear about your broomstick. Is there no chance of fixing it?
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
to	O
hear	O
about	O
your	O
broomstick	O
.	O
Is	O
there	O
no	O
chance	O
of	O
fixing	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300353
# text = No. Professor, why do the dementors affect me so? I mean, more than everyone else?
No	O
.	O
Professor	O
,	O
why	O
do	O
the	O
dementors	B-CRT
affect	O
me	O
so	O
?	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
more	O
than	O
everyone	O
else	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300354
# text = Listen. Dementors are amongst the foulest creatures to walk this earth. They feed on every good feeling, every happy memory... until a person is left with absolutely nothing but his worst experiences. You are not weak, Harry. The dementors affect you most because there are true horrors in your past. Horrors your classmates can scarcely imagine. You have nothing to be ashamed of.
Listen	O
.	O
Dementors	B-CRT
are	O
amongst	O
the	O
foulest	O
creatures	O
to	O
walk	O
this	O
earth	O
.	O
They	O
feed	O
on	O
every	O
good	O
feeling	O
,	O
every	O
happy	O
memory	O
...	O
until	O
a	O
person	O
is	O
left	O
with	O
absolutely	O
nothing	O
but	O
his	O
worst	O
experiences	O
.	O
You	O
are	O
not	O
weak	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
The	O
dementors	B-CRT
affect	O
you	O
most	O
because	O
there	O
are	O
true	O
horrors	O
in	O
your	O
past	O
.	O
Horrors	O
your	O
classmates	O
can	O
scarcely	O
imagine	O
.	O
You	O
have	O
nothing	O
to	O
be	O
ashamed	O
of	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300355
# text = I'm scared, professor.
I	O
'm	O
scared	O
,	O
professor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300356
# text = Well I'd consider you a fool if you weren't.
Well	O
I	O
'd	O
consider	O
you	O
a	O
fool	O
if	O
you	O
were	O
n't	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300357
# text = I need to know how to fight them. You could teach me. You made that dementor on the train go away.
I	O
need	O
to	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
fight	O
them	O
.	O
You	O
could	O
teach	O
me	O
.	O
You	O
made	O
that	O
dementor	B-CRT
on	O
the	O
train	O
go	O
away	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300358
# text = There was only one that night.
There	O
was	O
only	O
one	O
that	O
night	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300359
# text = But you made it go away.
But	O
you	O
made	O
it	O
go	O
away	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300360
# text = I don't pretend to be an expert, Harry. But as the dementors seem to have developed a particular interest in you... perhaps I should teach you. But after the holidays. For now, I need to rest.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
pretend	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
expert	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
But	O
as	O
the	O
dementors	B-CRT
seem	O
to	O
have	O
developed	O
a	O
particular	O
interest	O
in	O
you	O
...	O
perhaps	O
I	O
should	O
teach	O
you	O
.	O
But	O
after	O
the	O
holidays	O
.	O
For	O
now	O
,	O
I	O
need	O
to	O
rest	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300361
# text = Last call for Hogsmeade! Come on, now!
Last	O
call	O
for	O
Hogsmeade	B-LOC
!	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
now	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300362
# text = Guys, let me go.
Guys	O
,	O
let	O
me	O
go	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300363
# text = Clever, Harry.
Clever	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300364
# text = But not clever enough. Besides, we've got a better way.
But	O
not	O
clever	O
enough	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
we	O
've	O
got	O
a	O
better	O
way	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300365
# text = I'm trying to get to Hogsmeade.
I	O
'm	O
trying	O
to	O
get	O
to	O
Hogsmeade	B-LOC
.	O

# sent_id = 300366
# text = We know. Don't worry. We'll get you there. We'll show you a quicker way. If you pipe down.
We	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
worry	O
.	O
We	O
'll	O
get	O
you	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
'll	O
show	O
you	O
a	O
quicker	O
way	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
pipe	O
down	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300367
# text = We know. Don't worry. We'll get you there. We'll show you a quicker way. If you pipe down.
We	O
know	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
worry	O
.	O
We	O
'll	O
get	O
you	O
there	O
.	O
We	O
'll	O
show	O
you	O
a	O
quicker	O
way	O
.	O
If	O
you	O
pipe	O
down	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300368
# text = Oh. Bless him.
Oh	O
.	O
Bless	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300369
# text = Let me go! Come on, guys. Don't...
Let	O
me	O
go	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
guys	O
.	O
Do	O
n't	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300370
# text = Now, Harry.
Now	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300371
# text = Come and join the big boys.
Come	O
and	O
join	O
the	O
big	O
boys	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300372
# text = Come and join the big boys.
Come	O
and	O
join	O
the	O
big	O
boys	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300373
# text = What are you doing?!
What	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300374
# text = What's this rubbish?
What	O
's	O
this	O
rubbish	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300375
# text = What's this rubbish? he says. That there it's the secret to our success.
What	O
's	O
this	O
rubbish	O
?	O
he	O
says	O
.	O
That	O
there	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
secret	O
to	O
our	O
success	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300376
# text = It's a wrench giving it to you believe me. But we've decided your needs are greater than ours.
It	O
's	O
a	O
wrench	O
giving	O
it	O
to	O
you	O
believe	O
me	O
.	O
But	O
we	O
've	O
decided	O
your	O
needs	O
are	O
greater	O
than	O
ours	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300377
# text = George, if you will.
George	B-PER
,	O
if	O
you	O
will	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300378
# text = I solemnly swear that I am up to no good.
I	O
solemnly	O
swear	O
that	O
I	O
am	O
up	O
to	O
no	O
good	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300379
# text = Mr's. Moony, Wormtail, Padfoot and Prongs... are proud to present the Marauder's Map.
Mr	O
's	O
.	O
Moony	B-PER
,	O
Wormtail	B-PER
,	O
Padfoot	B-PER
and	O
Prongs	B-PER
...	O
are	O
proud	O
to	O
present	O
the	O
Marauder	B-MAG
's	I-MAG
Map	I-MAG
.	O

# sent_id = 300380
# text = We owe them so much.
We	O
owe	O
them	O
so	O
much	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300381
# text = Hang on. This is Hogwarts. And that... No. Is that really...?
Hang	O
on	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O
And	O
that	O
...	O
No	O
.	O
Is	O
that	O
really	O
...	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300382
# text = Dumbledore.
Dumbledore	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300383
# text = In his study.
In	O
his	O
study	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300384
# text = Pacing.
Pacing	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300385
# text = Does that a lot.
Does	O
that	O
a	O
lot	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300386
# text = So you mean this map shows...
So	O
you	O
mean	O
this	O
map	O
shows	O
...	O

# sent_id = 300387
# text = Everyone.
Everyone	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300388
# text = Everyone?
Everyone	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300389
# text = Everyone.
Everyone	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300390
# text = Where they are.
Where	O
they	O
are	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300391
# text = What they're doing.
What	O
they	O
're	O
doing	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300392
# text = Every minute.
Every	O
minute	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300393
# text = Of every day.
Of	O
every	O
day	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300394
# text = Brilliant! Where did you get it?
Brilliant	O
!	O
Where	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300395
# text = Knicked it from Filch's office, of course. First year.
Knicked	O
it	O
from	O
Filch	B-PER
's	O
office	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
First	O
year	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300396
# text = Now listen, there are seven secret passageways... out of the castle. We'd recommend
Now	O
listen	O
,	O
there	O
are	O
seven	O
secret	O
passageways	O
...	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
castle	O
.	O
We	O
'd	O
recommend	O

# sent_id = 300397
# text = This one.
This	O
one	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300398
# text = This one.
This	O
one	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300399
# text = The One-Eyed Witch passageway.
The	O
One	B-PER
Eyed	I-PER
Witch	I-PER
passageway	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300400
# text = It'll lead you straight to Honeyduke's seller.
It	O
'll	O
lead	O
you	O
straight	O
to	O
Honeyduke	B-ORG
's	I-ORG
seller	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300401
# text = You best hurry. Filch is heading this way.
You	O
best	O
hurry	O
.	O
Filch	B-PER
is	O
heading	O
this	O
way	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300402
# text = Oh and Harry don't forget. When you're done, just give it a tap and say:
Oh	O
and	O
Harry	B-PER
do	O
n't	O
forget	O
.	O
When	O
you	O
're	O
done	O
,	O
just	O
give	O
it	O
a	O
tap	O
and	O
say	O
:	O

# sent_id = 300403
# text = Mischief managed. Otherwise, anyone can read it.
Mischief	O
managed	O
.	O
Otherwise	O
,	O
anyone	O
can	O
read	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300404
# text = Mischief managed. Otherwise, anyone can read it.
Mischief	O
managed	O
.	O
Otherwise	O
,	O
anyone	O
can	O
read	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300405
# text = Now, how much do you want? Delicious.
Now	O
,	O
how	O
much	O
do	O
you	O
want	O
?	O
Delicious	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300406
# text = It's meant to be the most haunted building in Britain. Did I mention that?
It	O
's	O
meant	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
most	O
haunted	O
building	O
in	O
Britain	B-LOC
.	O
Did	O
I	O
mention	O
that	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300407
# text = Twice.
Twice	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300408
# text = Do you want to move a bit closer?
Do	O
you	O
want	O
to	O
move	O
a	O
bit	O
closer	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300409
# text = To the Shrieking Shack?
To	O
the	O
Shrieking	B-LOC
Shack	I-LOC
?	O

# sent_id = 300410
# text = Actually, I'm fine here.
Actually	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
fine	O
here	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300411
# text = Well, well. Look who's here. You two shopping for your new dream home? Bit grand for you, isn't it, Weasle-Bee? Don't your family sleep in uh... one room?
Well	O
,	O
well	O
.	O
Look	O
who	O
's	O
here	O
.	O
You	O
two	O
shopping	O
for	O
your	O
new	O
dream	O
home	O
?	O
Bit	O
grand	O
for	O
you	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
it	O
,	O
Weasle	B-PER
Bee	I-PER
?	O
Do	O
n't	O
your	O
family	O
sleep	O
in	O
uh	O
...	O
one	O
room	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300412
# text = Shut your mouth, Malfoy.
Shut	O
your	O
mouth	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300413
# text = Uh, Not very friendly. Boys, I think it's time we teach Weasle-Bee how to respect his superiors.
Uh	O
,	O
Not	O
very	O
friendly	O
.	O
Boys	O
,	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
's	O
time	O
we	O
teach	O
Weasle	B-PER
Bee	I-PER
how	O
to	O
respect	O
his	O
superiors	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300414
# text = Hope you don't mean yourself!
Hope	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
yourself	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300415
# text = How dare you talk to me! You filthy little mudblood! Who is that? Don't stand there! Do something!
How	O
dare	O
you	O
talk	O
to	O
me	O
!	O
You	O
filthy	O
little	O
mudblood	B-MAG
!	O
Who	O
is	O
that	O
?	O
Do	O
n't	O
stand	O
there	O
!	O
Do	O
something	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300416
# text = What?
What	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300417
# text = What's up, Malfoy? Lost your skis?
What	O
's	O
up	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
?	O
Lost	O
your	O
skis	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300418
# text = Get out of the way! Move!
Get	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
!	O
Move	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300419
# text = Malfoy! Wait! Wait!
Malfoy	B-PER
!	O
Wait	O
!	O
Wait	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300420
# text = Harry!
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300421
# text = Bloody hell, Harry. That was not funny.
Bloody	O
hell	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
That	O
was	O
not	O
funny	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300422
# text = Those weasels! Never told me about any Marauder's Map.
Those	O
weasels	O
!	O
Never	O
told	O
me	O
about	O
any	O
Marauder	B-MAG
's	I-MAG
Map	I-MAG
.	O

# sent_id = 300423
# text = But Harry isn't going to keep it. He's going to turn it over to Professor McGonagall. Aren't you?
But	O
Harry	B-PER
is	O
n't	O
going	O
to	O
keep	O
it	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
turn	O
it	O
over	O
to	O
Professor	O
McGonagall	B-PER
.	O
Are	O
n't	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300424
# text = Sure. Along with his Invisibility Cloak.
Sure	O
.	O
Along	O
with	O
his	O
Invisibility	B-MAG
Cloak	I-MAG
.	O

# sent_id = 300425
# text = Oh, Look who it is. Madam Rosmerta. Ron fancies her.
Oh	O
,	O
Look	O
who	O
it	O
is	O
.	O
Madam	O
Rosmerta	B-PER
.	O
Ron	B-PER
fancies	O
her	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300426
# text = That's not true!
That	O
's	O
not	O
true	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300427
# text = Professor McGonagall!
Professor	O
McGonagall	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300428
# text = Cornelius!
Cornelius	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300429
# text = Allow me, minister.
Allow	O
me	O
,	O
minister	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300430
# text = Oh, Hagrid...
Oh	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
...	O

# sent_id = 300431
# text = Sorry about that.
Sorry	O
about	O
that	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300432
# text = Rosmerta, my dear. I hope business is good.
Rosmerta	B-PER
,	O
my	O
dear	O
.	O
I	O
hope	O
business	O
is	O
good	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300433
# text = It'd be a lot better if the Ministry wasn't sending dementors... into my pub every other night!
It	O
'd	O
be	O
a	O
lot	O
better	O
if	O
the	O
Ministry	B-ORG
was	O
n't	O
sending	O
dementors	B-CRT
...	O
into	O
my	O
pub	O
every	O
other	O
night	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300434
# text = We have... We have a killer on the loose!
We	O
have	O
...	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
killer	O
on	O
the	O
loose	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300435
# text = Sirius Black in Hogsmeade! And what would bring him here?
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
in	O
Hogsmeade	B-LOC
!	O
And	O
what	O
would	O
bring	O
him	O
here	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300436
# text = Harry Potter.
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300437
# text = Harry Potter?
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300438
# text = Come.
Come	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300439
# text = Harry!
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300440
# text = No underage wizards allowed in today! Shut the damn door!
No	O
underage	O
wizards	O
allowed	O
in	O
today	O
!	O
Shut	O
the	O
damn	O
door	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300441
# text = So rude.
So	O
rude	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300442
# text = Thick heads.
Thick	O
heads	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300443
# text = Thick heads?! How dare they! Who are they calling thick heads? Young whippersnappers!
Thick	O
heads	O
?	O
!	O
How	O
dare	O
they	O
!	O
Who	O
are	O
they	O
calling	O
thick	O
heads	O
?	O
Young	O
whippersnappers	O
!	O

# sent_id = 300444
# text = Nobody's going to come to a pub where they're gonna get scared out of their wits. Why?
Nobody	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
come	O
to	O
a	O
pub	O
where	O
they	O
're	O
gonna	O
get	O
scared	O
out	O
of	O
their	O
wits	O
.	O
Why	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300445
# text = Professor Dumbledore does not want dementors around the place, I can assure you.
Professor	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
does	O
not	O
want	O
dementors	B-CRT
around	O
the	O
place	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
assure	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300446
# text = Now, tell me what this is all about.
Now	O
,	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
this	O
is	O
all	O
about	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300447
# text = Well. Now years ago, when Harry Potter's parents realized they were marked for death... You remember? They went into hiding. Few knew where they were. One who did was Sirius Black. And he told You-Know-Who!
Well	O
.	O
Now	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
when	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
's	O
parents	O
realized	O
they	O
were	O
marked	O
for	O
death	O
...	O
You	O
remember	O
?	O
They	O
went	O
into	O
hiding	O
.	O
Few	O
knew	O
where	O
they	O
were	O
.	O
One	O
who	O
did	O
was	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
.	O
And	O
he	O
told	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300448
# text = Not only did Black lead You-Know-Who to the Potters that night, but he also killed one of their friends, Peter Pettigrew!
Not	O
only	O
did	O
Black	B-PER
lead	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
to	O
the	O
Potters	B-PER
that	O
night	O
,	O
but	O
he	O
also	O
killed	O
one	O
of	O
their	O
friends	O
,	O
Peter	B-PER
Pettigrew	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 300449
# text = Peter Pettigrew?
Peter	B-PER
Pettigrew	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 300450
# text = Yes, little lump of a boy. Always trailing after Sirius Black.
Yes	O
,	O
little	O
lump	O
of	O
a	O
boy	O
.	O
Always	O
trailing	O
after	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300451
# text = Ah, I remember him. Never let James and Sirius out of his sight. But what happened?
Ah	O
,	O
I	O
remember	O
him	O
.	O
Never	O
let	O
James	B-PER
and	O
Sirius	B-PER
out	O
of	O
his	O
sight	O
.	O
But	O
what	O
happened	O
?	O

# sent_id = 300452
# text = Well Peter Pettigrew tried to warn the Potters... and might have managed to, had he not run into an old friend, Sirius Black.
Well	O
Peter	B-PER
Pettigrew	B-PER
tried	O
to	O
warn	O
the	O
Potters	B-PER
...	O
and	O
might	O
have	O
managed	O
to	O
,	O
had	O
he	O
not	O
run	O
into	O
an	O
old	O
friend	O
,	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 300453
# text = Black was vicious. He didn't kill Pettigrew. He destroyed him! A finger. That's all that was left. A finger. Nothing else.
Black	B-PER
was	O
vicious	O
.	O
He	O
did	O
n't	O
kill	O
Pettigrew	B-PER
.	O
He	O
destroyed	O
him	O
!	O
A	O
finger	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
all	O
that	O
was	O
left	O
.	O
A	O
finger	O
.	O
Nothing	O
else	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300454
# text = Yes. Sirius Black may not have put his hands to the Potters, but he's the reason they're dead.
Yes	O
.	O
Sirius	B-PER
Black	I-PER
may	O
not	O
have	O
put	O
his	O
hands	O
to	O
the	O
Potters	B-PER
,	O
but	O
he	O
's	O
the	O
reason	O
they	O
're	O
dead	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300455
# text = And now he wants to finish what he started.
And	O
now	O
he	O
wants	O
to	O
finish	O
what	O
he	O
started	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300456
# text = Mhmm.
Mhmm	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300457
# text = I don't believe it.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300458
# text = Ah, that's not the worst of it.
Ah	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
not	O
the	O
worst	O
of	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 300459
# text = What could be worse?
What	O
could	O
be	O
worse	O
?	O