# newdoc id = hp1diolog.csv
# sent_id = 100001
# text = I should have known that you would be here...Professor McGonagall.
I	O
should	O
have	O
known	O
that	O
you	O
would	O
be	O
here	O
...	O
Professor	O
McGonagall	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100002
# text = Good evening, Professor Dumbledore. Are the rumours true, Albus?
Good	O
evening	O
,	O
Professor	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
.	O
Are	O
the	O
rumours	O
true	O
,	O
Albus	B-PER?	O

# sent_id = 100003
# text = I'm afraid so, Professor. The good, and the bad.
I	O
'm	O
afraid	O
so	O
,	O
Professor	O
.	O
The	O
good	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
bad	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100004
# text = And the boy?
And	O
the	O
boy	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100005
# text = Hagrid is bringing him.
Hagrid	B-PER
is	O
bringing	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100007
# text = Ah, Professor, I would trust Hagrid with my life.
Ah	O
,	O
Professor	O
,	O
I	O
would	O
trust	O
Hagrid	B-PER
with	O
my	O
life	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100008
# text = Professor Dumbledore, Sir. Professor McGonagall.
Professor	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
,	O
Sir	O
.	O
Professor	O
McGonagall	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100009
# text = No problems, I trust, Hagrid?
No	O
problems	O
,	O
I	O
trust	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100010
# text = No, sir. Little tyke fell asleep just as we were flying over Bristol. Heh. Try not to wake him. There you go.
No	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Little	O
tyke	O
fell	O
asleep	O
just	O
as	O
we	O
were	O
flying	O
over	O
Bristol	B-LOC
.	O
Heh	O
.	O
Try	O
not	O
to	O
wake	O
him	O
.	O
There	O
you	O
go	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100011
# text = Albus, do you really think it's safe, leaving him with these people? I've watched them all day. They're the worst sort of Muggles imaginable. They really are...
Albus	B-PER
,	O
do	O
you	O
really	O
think	O
it	O
's	O
safe	O
,	O
leaving	O
him	O
with	O
these	O
people	O
?	O
I	O
've	O
watched	O
them	O
all	O
day	O
.	O
They	O
're	O
the	O
worst	O
sort	O
of	O
Muggles	O
imaginable	O
.	O
They	O
really	O
are	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100012
# text = The only family he has.
The	O
only	O
family	O
he	O
has	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100013
# text = This boy will be famous. There won't be a child in our world who doesn't know his name.
This	O
boy	O
will	O
be	O
famous	O
.	O
There	O
wo	O
n't	O
be	O
a	O
child	O
in	O
our	O
world	O
who	O
does	O
n't	O
know	O
his	O
name	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100014
# text = Exactly. He's better off growing up away from all that. Until he is ready.
Exactly	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
better	O
off	O
growing	O
up	O
away	O
from	O
all	O
that	O
.	O
Until	O
he	O
is	O
ready	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100015
# text = There, there, Hagrid. It's not really goodbye, after all.
There	O
,	O
there	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
.	O
It	O
's	O
not	O
really	O
goodbye	O
,	O
after	O
all	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100016
# text = Good luck...Harry Potter.
Good	O
luck	O
...	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100017
# text = Up. Get up.  Now!
Up	O
.	O
Get	O
up	O
.	O
Now	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100018
# text = Wake up, cousin! We're going to the zoo!
Wake	O
up	O
,	O
cousin	O
!	O
We	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
zoo	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100019
# text = Oh, here he comes, the birthday boy!
Oh	O
,	O
here	O
he	O
comes	O
,	O
the	O
birthday	O
boy	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100020
# text = Happy birthday, son.
Happy	O
birthday	O
,	O
son	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100021
# text = Why don't you just cook the breakfast, and try not to burn anything.
Why	O
do	O
n't	O
you	O
just	O
cook	O
the	O
breakfast	O
,	O
and	O
try	O
not	O
to	O
burn	O
anything	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100022
# text = Yes, Aunt Petunia.
Yes	O
,	O
Aunt	O
Petunia	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100023
# text = I want everything to be perfect for my Dudley's special day.
I	O
want	O
everything	O
to	O
be	O
perfect	O
for	O
my	O
Dudley	B-PER
's	O
special	O
day	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100024
# text = Hurry up! Bring my coffee, boy!
Hurry	O
up	O
!	O
Bring	O
my	O
coffee	O
,	O
boy	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100025
# text = Yes, Uncle Vernon.
Yes	O
,	O
Uncle	O
Vernon	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100026
# text = Aren t they wonderful, darling?
Aren	O
t	O
they	O
wonderful	O
,	O
darling	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100027
# text = How many are there?
How	O
many	O
are	O
there	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100028
# text = Thirty-six. Counted 'em myself.
Thirty	O
six	O
.	O
Counted	O
'	O
em	O
myself	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100029
# text = Thirty-six?! But last year last year I had thirty-seven!!
Thirty	O
six	O
?	O
!	O
But	O
last	O
year	O
last	O
year	O
I	O
had	O
thirty	O
seven	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100030
# text = Err yes, well, some of them are quite a bit bigger than last year.
Err	O
yes	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
some	O
of	O
them	O
are	O
quite	O
a	O
bit	O
bigger	O
than	O
last	O
year	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100031
# text = I don't care how big they are!
I	O
do	O
n't	O
care	O
how	O
big	O
they	O
are	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100032
# text = Oh, now, now, now. This is what we're going to do, is that when we go out, we're going to buy you two new presents! How's that, pumpkin?
Oh	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
now	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
what	O
we	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
do	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
when	O
we	O
go	O
out	O
,	O
we	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
buy	O
you	O
two	O
new	O
presents	O
!	O
How	O
's	O
that	O
,	O
pumpkin	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100033
# text = This will be a lovely day at the zoo. I'm really looking forward to it.
This	O
will	O
be	O
a	O
lovely	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
zoo	O
.	O
I	O
'm	O
really	O
looking	O
forward	O
to	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100034
# text = I'm warning you now, boy. Any funny business, any at all, and you won't have any meals for a week. Get in.
I	O
'm	O
warning	O
you	O
now	O
,	O
boy	O
.	O
Any	O
funny	O
business	O
,	O
any	O
at	O
all	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
wo	O
n't	O
have	O
any	O
meals	O
for	O
a	O
week	O
.	O
Get	O
in	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100035
# text = Make it move.
Make	O
it	O
move	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100036
# text = Move!
Move	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100037
# text = MOVE!
MOVE	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100038
# text = He's asleep!
He	O
's	O
asleep	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100039
# text = He's boring.
He	O
's	O
boring	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100040
# text = Sorry about him. He doesn't understand what it's like, lying there day after day, having people press their ugly faces in on you.  Can you...hear me?  It's just...I've never talked to a snake before. Do you...I mean...do you talk to people often?  You're from Burma, aren't you? Was it nice there, do you miss your family?  I see. That's me as well. I never knew my parents, either.
Sorry	O
about	O
him	O
.	O
He	O
does	O
n't	O
understand	O
what	O
it	O
's	O
like	O
,	O
lying	O
there	O
day	O
after	O
day	O
,	O
having	O
people	O
press	O
their	O
ugly	O
faces	O
in	O
on	O
you	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
...	O
hear	O
me	O
?	O
It	O
's	O
just	O
...	O
I	O
've	O
never	O
talked	O
to	O
a	O
snake	O
before	O
.	O
Do	O
you	O
...	O
I	O
mean	O
...	O
do	O
you	O
talk	O
to	O
people	O
often	O
?	O
You	O
're	O
from	O
Burma	B-LOC
,	O
are	O
n't	O
you	O
?	O
Was	O
it	O
nice	O
there	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
miss	O
your	O
family	O
?	O
I	O
see	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
me	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
I	O
never	O
knew	O
my	O
parents	O
,	O
either	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100041
# text = Mummy, dad, come here! You won't believe what this snake is doing!
Mummy	O
,	O
dad	O
,	O
come	O
here	O
!	O
You	O
wo	O
n't	O
believe	O
what	O
this	O
snake	O
is	O
doing	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100042
# text = Whoa! Ahh! Ahh!!
Whoa	O
!	O
Ahh	O
!	O
Ahh	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100043
# text = Thanks.
Thanks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100044
# text = Anytime.
Anytime	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100045
# text = SNAKE!
SNAKE	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100046
# text = Mum, mummy!
Mum	O
,	O
mummy	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100047
# text = AHH!
AHH	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100048
# text = Mum, help! Help me!
Mum	O
,	O
help	O
!	O
Help	O
me	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100049
# text = My darling boy! How did you get in there?! How did you get in there? Dursley, oh, Dursley!
My	O
darling	O
boy	O
!	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
!	O
How	O
did	O
you	O
get	O
in	O
there	O
?	O
Dursley	B-PER
,	O
oh	O
,	O
Dursley	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100050
# text = It's all right. It's all right.
It	O
's	O
all	O
right	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
all	O
right	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100051
# text = Ow!
Ow	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100052
# text = What happened?!
What	O
happened	O
?	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100053
# text = I swear I don't know!  One minute, the glass was there and then it was gone! It was like magic!
I	O
swear	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
!	O
One	O
minute	O
,	O
the	O
glass	O
was	O
there	O
and	O
then	O
it	O
was	O
gone	O
!	O
It	O
was	O
like	O
magic	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100054
# text = There's no such thing as magic!
There	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
as	O
magic	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100055
# text = Awww, smile.  Vernon, just look at him. I can't believe it. In just a week you'll be off to Smeltings.
Awww	O
,	O
smile	O
.	O
Vernon	B-PER
,	O
just	O
look	O
at	O
him	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
believe	O
it	O
.	O
In	O
just	O
a	O
week	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
off	O
to	O
Smeltings	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100056
# text = Caveat Smeltona. Proudest moment of my life.
Caveat	O
Smeltona	O
.	O
Proudest	O
moment	O
of	O
my	O
life	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100057
# text = Will I have to wear that, too?
Will	O
I	O
have	O
to	O
wear	O
that	O
,	O
too	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100058
# text = What, you? Go to Smeltings?
What	O
,	O
you	O
?	O
Go	O
to	O
Smeltings	B-ORG
?	O

# sent_id = 100059
# text = Ha!
Ha	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100060
# text = Oh, don't be so stupid, you're going to the state school where you belong.  And this is what you're gonna be wearing when I've finished dyeing it.
Oh	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
so	O
stupid	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
state	O
school	O
where	O
you	O
belong	O
.	O
And	O
this	O
is	O
what	O
you	O
're	O
gonna	O
be	O
wearing	O
when	O
I	O
've	O
finished	O
dyeing	O
it	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100061
# text = But that's Dudley's old uniform. It'll fit me like bits of old Elephant skin.
But	O
that	O
's	O
Dudley	B-PER
's	O
old	O
uniform	O
.	O
It	O
'll	O
fit	O
me	O
like	O
bits	O
of	O
old	O
Elephant	O
skin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100062
# text = It'll fit you well enough. Go get the post.  Go!
It	O
'll	O
fit	O
you	O
well	O
enough	O
.	O
Go	O
get	O
the	O
post	O
.	O
Go	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100063
# text = Oh, Marge is ill! Ate a funny whelk.
Oh	O
,	O
Marge	B-PER
is	O
ill	O
!	O
Ate	O
a	O
funny	O
whelk	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100064
# text = Dad! Look! Harry's got a letter!
Dad	O
!	O
Look	O
!	O
Harry	B-PER
's	O
got	O
a	O
letter	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100065
# text = Hey, give it back! It's mine!
Hey	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
back	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
mine	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100066
# text = Yours? Who'd be writing to you?
Yours	O
?	O
Who	O
'd	O
be	O
writing	O
to	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100067
# text = No more mail through this letterbox.
No	O
more	O
mail	O
through	O
this	O
letterbox	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100068
# text = Have a lovely day at the office, dear.
Have	O
a	O
lovely	O
day	O
at	O
the	O
office	O
,	O
dear	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100069
# text = Shoo! Go on!
Shoo	O
!	O
Go	O
on	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100070
# text = Fine day Sunday. In my opinion, best day of the week. Why is that, Dudley?
Fine	O
day	O
Sunday	O
.	O
In	O
my	O
opinion	O
,	O
best	O
day	O
of	O
the	O
week	O
.	O
Why	O
is	O
that	O
,	O
Dudley	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100071
# text = Because there's no post on Sunday?
Because	O
there	O
's	O
no	O
post	O
on	O
Sunday	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100072
# text = Ah, right you are, Harry. No post on Sunday. Ha! No blasted letters today. No, sir. Not one single bloody letter, not one.  No, sir, not one blasted, miserable-
Ah	O
,	O
right	O
you	O
are	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
No	O
post	O
on	O
Sunday	O
.	O
Ha	O
!	O
No	O
blasted	O
letters	O
today	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Not	O
one	O
single	O
bloody	O
letter	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
sir	O
,	O
not	O
one	O
blasted	O
,	O
miserable	O

# sent_id = 100073
# text = AHH! Make it stop! Please make it stop!
AHH	O
!	O
Make	O
it	O
stop	O
!	O
Please	O
make	O
it	O
stop	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100074
# text = Go away, ahh!
Go	O
away	O
,	O
ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100075
# text = What is it? Please tell me what's happening!
What	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Please	O
tell	O
me	O
what	O
's	O
happening	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100076
# text = Give me that! Give me that letter!
Give	O
me	O
that	O
!	O
Give	O
me	O
that	O
letter	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100077
# text = Get off! Ahh!
Get	O
off	O
!	O
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100078
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100079
# text = They're my letters! Let go of me!
They	O
're	O
my	O
letters	O
!	O
Let	O
go	O
of	O
me	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100080
# text = That's it! We're going away! Far away! Where they can't find us!
That	O
's	O
it	O
!	O
We	O
're	O
going	O
away	O
!	O
Far	O
away	O
!	O
Where	O
they	O
ca	O
n't	O
find	O
us	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100081
# text = Daddy's gone mad, hasn't he?!
Daddy	O
's	O
gone	O
mad	O
,	O
has	O
n't	O
he	O
?	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100082
# text = Make a wish, Harry.
Make	O
a	O
wish	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100083
# text = Who's there? Ahh!
Who	O
's	O
there	O
?	O
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100084
# text = Sorry 'bout that.
Sorry	O
'	O
bout	O
that	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100085
# text = I demand that you leave at once, sir! You are breaking and entering!
I	O
demand	O
that	O
you	O
leave	O
at	O
once	O
,	O
sir	O
!	O
You	O
are	O
breaking	O
and	O
entering	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100086
# text = Dry up, Dursley, you great prune.  Boy, I haven't seen you since you was a baby, Harry, but you're a bit more along than I would have expected. Particularly 'round the middle!
Dry	O
up	O
,	O
Dursley	B-PER
,	O
you	O
great	O
prune	O
.	O
Boy	O
,	O
I	O
have	O
n't	O
seen	O
you	O
since	O
you	O
was	O
a	O
baby	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
but	O
you	O
're	O
a	O
bit	O
more	O
along	O
than	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
expected	O
.	O
Particularly	O
'	O
round	O
the	O
middle	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100087
# text = I-I-I'm not Harry.
I	O
I	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100088
# text = I-I am.
I	O
I	O
am	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100089
# text = Oh, well, of course you are! Got something for ya. 'Fraid I might have sat on it at some point! I imagine that it'll taste fine just the same. Ahh. Baked it myself.  Words and all. Heh.
Oh	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
you	O
are	O
!	O
Got	O
something	O
for	O
ya	O
.	O
'	O
Fraid	O
I	O
might	O
have	O
sat	O
on	O
it	O
at	O
some	O
point	O
!	O
I	O
imagine	O
that	O
it	O
'll	O
taste	O
fine	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
.	O
Ahh	O
.	O
Baked	O
it	O
myself	O
.	O
Words	O
and	O
all	O
.	O
Heh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100090
# text = Thank you!
Thank	O
you	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100091
# text = It's not every day that your young man turns eleven, now is it?
It	O
's	O
not	O
every	O
day	O
that	O
your	O
young	O
man	O
turns	O
eleven	O
,	O
now	O
is	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100092
# text = Excuse me, who are you?
Excuse	O
me	O
,	O
who	O
are	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100093
# text = Rubeus Hagrid. Keeper of keys and grounds at Hogwarts. Course, you'll know all about Hogwarts.
Rubeus	B-PER
Hagrid	I-PER
.	O
Keeper	O
of	O
keys	O
and	O
grounds	O
at	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O
Course	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
know	O
all	O
about	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100094
# text = Sorry, no.
Sorry	O
,	O
no	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100095
# text = No? Blimey, Harry, didn't you ever wonder where your mum and dad learned it all?
No	O
?	O
Blimey	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
did	O
n't	O
you	O
ever	O
wonder	O
where	O
your	O
mum	O
and	O
dad	O
learned	O
it	O
all	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100096
# text = Learned what?
Learned	O
what	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100097
# text = You're a wizard, Harry.
You	O
're	O
a	O
wizard	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100098
# text = I-I'm a what?
I	O
I	O
'm	O
a	O
what	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100099
# text = A wizard. And a thumping good one at that, I'd wager. Once you train up a little.
A	O
wizard	O
.	O
And	O
a	O
thumping	O
good	O
one	O
at	O
that	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
wager	O
.	O
Once	O
you	O
train	O
up	O
a	O
little	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100100
# text = No, you've made a mistake. I can't be...a-a wizard. I mean, I'm just... Harry. Just Harry.
No	O
,	O
you	O
've	O
made	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
be	O
...	O
a	O
a	O
wizard	O
.	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
just	O
...	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Just	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100101
# text = Well, just Harry. Did you ever make anything happen? Anything you couldn't explain when you were angry or scared?  Ah.
Well	O
,	O
just	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Did	O
you	O
ever	O
make	O
anything	O
happen	O
?	O
Anything	O
you	O
could	O
n't	O
explain	O
when	O
you	O
were	O
angry	O
or	O
scared	O
?	O
Ah	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100103
# text = He'll not be going! We swore when we took him in, we d put a stop to this rubbish!
He	O
'll	O
not	O
be	O
going	O
!	O
We	O
swore	O
when	O
we	O
took	O
him	O
in	O
,	O
we	O
d	O
put	O
a	O
stop	O
to	O
this	O
rubbish	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100104
# text = You knew? You knew all along and you never told me?
You	O
knew	O
?	O
You	O
knew	O
all	O
along	O
and	O
you	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100105
# text = Of course we knew. How could you not be? My perfect sister being who she was. Oh, my mother and father were so proud the day she got her letter. We have a witch in the family. Isn't it wonderful? I was the only one to see her for what she was. A freak! And then she met that Potter, and then she had you, and I knew you'd be just the same, just as strange, just as ... abnormal. And then, if you please, she went and got herself blown up. And we got landed with you.
Of	O
course	O
we	O
knew	O
.	O
How	O
could	O
you	O
not	O
be	O
?	O
My	O
perfect	O
sister	O
being	O
who	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
my	O
mother	O
and	O
father	O
were	O
so	O
proud	O
the	O
day	O
she	O
got	O
her	O
letter	O
.	O
We	O
have	O
a	O
witch	O
in	O
the	O
family	O
.	O
Is	O
n't	O
it	O
wonderful	O
?	O
I	O
was	O
the	O
only	O
one	O
to	O
see	O
her	O
for	O
what	O
she	O
was	O
.	O
A	O
freak	O
!	O
And	O
then	O
she	O
met	O
that	O
Potter	B-PER
,	O
and	O
then	O
she	O
had	O
you	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
knew	O
you	O
'd	O
be	O
just	O
the	O
same	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
strange	O
,	O
just	O
as	O
...	O
abnormal	O
.	O
And	O
then	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
please	O
,	O
she	O
went	O
and	O
got	O
herself	O
blown	O
up	O
.	O
And	O
we	O
got	O
landed	O
with	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100106
# text = Blown up? You told me my parents died in a car crash!
Blown	O
up	O
?	O
You	O
told	O
me	O
my	O
parents	O
died	O
in	O
a	O
car	O
crash	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100107
# text = A car crash? A car crash kill James and Lily Potter?
A	O
car	O
crash	O
?	O
A	O
car	O
crash	O
kill	O
James	B-PER
and	O
Lily	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100108
# text = We had to tell him something.
We	O
had	O
to	O
tell	O
him	O
something	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100109
# text = It's an outrage! It's a scandal!
It	O
's	O
an	O
outrage	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
scandal	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100110
# text = He'll not be going!
He	O
'll	O
not	O
be	O
going	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100111
# text = Oh, and I suppose a great Muggle like yourself's going to stop him, are you?
Oh	O
,	O
and	O
I	O
suppose	O
a	O
great	O
Muggle	O
like	O
yourself	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
stop	O
him	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100112
# text = Muggle?
Muggle	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100113
# text = Non magic folk.  This boy's had his name down ever since he was born!  He's going to the finest school of witchcraft and wizardry in the world, and he'll be under the finest headmaster that Hogwarts has ever seen: Albus Dumbledore.
Non	O
magic	O
folk	O
.	O
This	O
boy	O
's	O
had	O
his	O
name	O
down	O
ever	O
since	O
he	O
was	O
born	O
!	O
He	O
's	O
going	O
to	O
the	O
finest	O
school	O
of	O
witchcraft	O
and	O
wizardry	O
in	O
the	O
world	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
'll	O
be	O
under	O
the	O
finest	O
headmaster	O
that	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
has	O
ever	O
seen	O
:	O
Albus	B-PER
Dumbledore	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100114
# text = I will not pay for some crackpot old fool to teach him magic tricks!
I	O
will	O
not	O
pay	O
for	O
some	O
crackpot	O
old	O
fool	O
to	O
teach	O
him	O
magic	O
tricks	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100116
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100117
# text = Oh, um, I'd appreciate if you didn't tell anyone at Hogwarts about that. Strictly speaking, I'm not allowed to do magic.
Oh	O
,	O
um	O
,	O
I	O
'd	O
appreciate	O
if	O
you	O
did	O
n't	O
tell	O
anyone	O
at	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
about	O
that	O
.	O
Strictly	O
speaking	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
not	O
allowed	O
to	O
do	O
magic	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100118
# text = Okay.
Okay	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100119
# text = Ooh, we're a bit behind schedule. Best be off.  Unless you'd rather stay, of course. Hmm?
Ooh	B-PER
,	O
we	O
're	O
a	O
bit	O
behind	O
schedule	O
.	O
Best	O
be	O
off	O
.	O
Unless	O
you	O
'd	O
rather	O
stay	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
Hmm	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100120
# text = First year students will require: three sets of work robes, one wand.
First	O
year	O
students	O
will	O
require	O
:	O
three	O
sets	O
of	O
work	O
robes	O
,	O
one	O
wand	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100121
# text = Essential bit of equipment, Harry.
Essential	O
bit	O
of	O
equipment	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100122
# text = One pair of dragon-hide gloves.  Hagrid, do they mean for a real dragon?
One	O
pair	O
of	O
dragon	O
hide	O
gloves	O
.	O
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
do	O
they	O
mean	O
for	O
a	O
real	O
dragon	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100123
# text = Well, they don't mean for a penguin, do they? Heh. Crikey, but not a dragon.
Well	O
,	O
they	O
do	O
n't	O
mean	O
for	O
a	O
penguin	O
,	O
do	O
they	O
?	O
Heh	O
.	O
Crikey	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
a	O
dragon	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100124
# text = But you like a dragon?
But	O
you	O
like	O
a	O
dragon	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100125
# text = Fast and misunderstood beasts, Harry. Fast and misunderstood.
Fast	O
and	O
misunderstood	O
beasts	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Fast	O
and	O
misunderstood	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100126
# text = All students must be equipped with...one standard size two pewter cauldron and may bring if they desire either an owl, a cat or a toad. Could we find all this in London?
All	O
students	O
must	O
be	O
equipped	O
with	O
...	O
one	O
standard	O
size	O
two	O
pewter	O
cauldron	O
and	O
may	O
bring	O
if	O
they	O
desire	O
either	O
an	O
owl	O
,	O
a	O
cat	O
or	O
a	O
toad	O
.	O
Could	O
we	O
find	O
all	O
this	O
in	O
London	B-LOC
?	O

# sent_id = 100127
# text = If you know where to go.
If	O
you	O
know	O
where	O
to	O
go	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100128
# text = Ah, Hagrid! The usual, I presume?
Ah	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
!	O
The	O
usual	O
,	O
I	O
presume	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100129
# text = No thanks, Tom. I'm on official Hogwarts business today. Just helping young Harry here buy his school supplies.
No	O
thanks	O
,	O
Tom	B-PER
.	O
I	O
'm	O
on	O
official	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
business	O
today	O
.	O
Just	O
helping	O
young	O
Harry	B-PER
here	O
buy	O
his	O
school	O
supplies	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100130
# text = Bless my soul. It's Harry Potter.
Bless	O
my	O
soul	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100131
# text = Welcome back, Mr. Potter, welcome back.
Welcome	O
back	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
,	O
welcome	O
back	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100132
# text = Doris Crockford, Mr. Potter. I can't believe I'm meeting you at last.
Doris	B-PER
Crockford	I-PER
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
believe	O
I	O
'm	O
meeting	O
you	O
at	O
last	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100133
# text = Harry P-potter. C-can't tell you how pleased I am to meet you.
Harry	B-PER
P	O
potter	I-PER
.	O
C	O
ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
pleased	O
I	O
am	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100134
# text = Hello, Professor. I didn't see you there. Harry, this is Professor Quirrell. He'll be your Defense Against the Dark Arts teacher at Hogwarts.
Hello	O
,	O
Professor	O
.	O
I	O
did	O
n't	O
see	O
you	O
there	O
.	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
this	O
is	O
Professor	O
Quirrell	B-PER
.	O
He	O
'll	O
be	O
your	O
Defense	O
Against	O
the	O
Dark	O
Arts	O
teacher	O
at	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100135
# text = Oh, nice to meet you.
Oh	O
,	O
nice	O
to	O
meet	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100136
# text = F-fearfully fascinating subject. N-not that you need it, e-eh, Potter? Heheh.
F	O
fearfully	O
fascinating	O
subject	O
.	O
N	O
not	O
that	O
you	O
need	O
it	O
,	O
e	O
eh	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
?	O
Heheh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100137
# text = Yes, well, must be going now. Lots to buy. Heh.
Yes	O
,	O
well	O
,	O
must	O
be	O
going	O
now	O
.	O
Lots	O
to	O
buy	O
.	O
Heh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100138
# text = Goodbye.
Goodbye	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100139
# text = See, Harry, you're famous!
See	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
you	O
're	O
famous	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100140
# text = But why am I famous, Hagrid? All those people back there, how is it they know who I am?
But	O
why	O
am	O
I	O
famous	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
?	O
All	O
those	O
people	O
back	O
there	O
,	O
how	O
is	O
it	O
they	O
know	O
who	O
I	O
am	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100141
# text = I'm not exactly sure I'm the right person to tell you that, Harry.  Welcome, Harry, to Diagon Alley.  Here's where you'll get your quills and ink, and over there all your bits and bobs for doing your wizardry.
I	O
'm	O
not	O
exactly	O
sure	O
I	O
'm	O
the	O
right	O
person	O
to	O
tell	O
you	O
that	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Welcome	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
to	O
Diagon	B-LOC
Alley	I-LOC
.	O
Here	O
's	O
where	O
you	O
'll	O
get	O
your	O
quills	O
and	O
ink	O
,	O
and	O
over	O
there	O
all	O
your	O
bits	O
and	O
bobs	O
for	O
doing	O
your	O
wizardry	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100142
# text = It's a world class racing broom. Look at it, it s the new Nimbus 2000! It's the fastest model yet.
It	O
's	O
a	O
world	O
class	O
racing	O
broom	O
.	O
Look	O
at	O
it	O
,	O
it	O
s	O
the	O
new	O
Nimbus	O
2000	O
!	O
It	O
's	O
the	O
fastest	O
model	O
yet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100143
# text = But, Hagrid, how am I to pay for all this? I haven't any money.
But	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
how	O
am	O
I	O
to	O
pay	O
for	O
all	O
this	O
?	O
I	O
have	O
n't	O
any	O
money	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100144
# text = Well, there's your money, Harry.  Gringotts, the Wizard Bank. T'aint no place safer, 'cept perhaps Hogwarts.
Well	O
,	O
there	O
's	O
your	O
money	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Gringotts	B-ORG
,	O
the	O
Wizard	O
Bank	O
.	O
T	O
'	O
aint	O
no	O
place	O
safer	O
,	O
'	O
cept	O
perhaps	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100145
# text = Uh, Hagrid, what exactly are these things?
Uh	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
what	O
exactly	O
are	O
these	O
things	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100146
# text = They're goblins, Harry. Clever as they come goblins, but not the most friendly of beasts. Best stick close to me.  Mr. Harry Potter wishes to make a withdrawal.
They	O
're	O
goblins	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Clever	O
as	O
they	O
come	O
goblins	O
,	O
but	O
not	O
the	O
most	O
friendly	O
of	O
beasts	O
.	O
Best	O
stick	O
close	O
to	O
me	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
wishes	O
to	O
make	O
a	O
withdrawal	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100147
# text = And does Mr. Harry Potter have his key?
And	O
does	O
Mr.	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
have	O
his	O
key	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100148
# text = Oh. Wait a minute. Got it here somewhere. Hah. There's the little devil.  Oh, and there's something else as well.  Professor Dumbledore gave me this.  It's about you-know-what in vault you-know-which.
Oh	O
.	O
Wait	O
a	O
minute	O
.	O
Got	O
it	O
here	O
somewhere	O
.	O
Hah	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
the	O
little	O
devil	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
something	O
else	O
as	O
well	O
.	O
Professor	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
gave	O
me	O
this	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
about	O
you	O
know	O
what	O
in	O
vault	O
you	O
know	O
which	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100149
# text = Very well.
Very	O
well	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100150
# text = Vault 687. Lamp, please.  Key please.
Vault	O
687	O
.	O
Lamp	O
,	O
please	O
.	O
Key	O
please	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100151
# text = Didn't think your mum and dad would leave you with nothing now, did ya?
Did	O
n't	O
think	O
your	O
mum	O
and	O
dad	O
would	O
leave	O
you	O
with	O
nothing	O
now	O
,	O
did	O
ya	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100152
# text = Vault 713.
Vault	O
713	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100153
# text = What's in there, Hagrid?
What	O
's	O
in	O
there	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100154
# text = Can't tell you, Harry. It's Hogwarts business. Very secret.
Ca	O
n't	O
tell	O
you	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
It	O
's	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
business	O
.	O
Very	O
secret	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100155
# text = Stand back.
Stand	O
back	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100156
# text = Best not mention this to anyone, Harry.
Best	O
not	O
mention	O
this	O
to	O
anyone	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100157
# text = I still need...a wand.
I	O
still	O
need	O
...	O
a	O
wand	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100158
# text = A wand? Well, you'll want Ollivanders.  No place better. Run along there, but wait. I just got one more thing I got to do. Won't be long.
A	O
wand	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
you	O
'll	O
want	O
Ollivanders	B-ORG
.	O
No	O
place	O
better	O
.	O
Run	O
along	O
there	O
,	O
but	O
wait	O
.	O
I	O
just	O
got	O
one	O
more	O
thing	O
I	O
got	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
Wo	O
n't	O
be	O
long	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100159
# text = Hello? Hello?
Hello	O
?	O
Hello	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100160
# text = I wondered when I'd be seeing you, Mr. Potter. It seems only yesterday that your mother and father were in here buying their first wands.  Ah. Here we are.  Well, give it a wave.  Apparently not.  Perhaps this.  No, no, definitely not! No matter...  I wonder.  Curious, very curious.
I	O
wondered	O
when	O
I	O
'd	O
be	O
seeing	O
you	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
It	O
seems	O
only	O
yesterday	O
that	O
your	O
mother	O
and	O
father	O
were	O
in	O
here	O
buying	O
their	O
first	O
wands	O
.	O
Ah	O
.	O
Here	O
we	O
are	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
give	O
it	O
a	O
wave	O
.	O
Apparently	O
not	O
.	O
Perhaps	O
this	O
.	O
No	O
,	O
no	O
,	O
definitely	O
not	O
!	O
No	O
matter	O
...	O
I	O
wonder	O
.	O
Curious	O
,	O
very	O
curious	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100161
# text = Sorry, but what's curious?
Sorry	O
,	O
but	O
what	O
's	O
curious	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100162
# text = I remember every wand I've ever sold, Mr. Potter. It just so happens that the phoenix, whose tail feather resides in your wand gave one other feather, just one. It is curious that you should be destined for this wand when its brother gave you that scar.
I	O
remember	O
every	O
wand	O
I	O
've	O
ever	O
sold	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
It	O
just	O
so	O
happens	O
that	O
the	O
phoenix	O
,	O
whose	O
tail	O
feather	O
resides	O
in	O
your	O
wand	O
gave	O
one	O
other	O
feather	O
,	O
just	O
one	O
.	O
It	O
is	O
curious	O
that	O
you	O
should	O
be	O
destined	O
for	O
this	O
wand	O
when	O
its	O
brother	O
gave	O
you	O
that	O
scar	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100163
# text = And...who owned that wand?
And	O
...	O
who	O
owned	O
that	O
wand	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100164
# text = Oh, we do not speak his name. The wand chooses the wizard, Mr. Potter. It's not always clear why, but I think it is clear that we can expect great things from you. After all, He-Who-Must-Not-Be-Named did great things...terrible, yes, but great.
Oh	O
,	O
we	O
do	O
not	O
speak	O
his	O
name	O
.	O
The	O
wand	O
chooses	O
the	O
wizard	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
It	O
's	O
not	O
always	O
clear	O
why	O
,	O
but	O
I	O
think	O
it	O
is	O
clear	O
that	O
we	O
can	O
expect	O
great	O
things	O
from	O
you	O
.	O
After	O
all	O
,	O
He	B-PER
Who	I-PER
Must	I-PER
Not	I-PER
Be	I-PER
Named	I-PER
did	O
great	O
things	O
...	O
terrible	O
,	O
yes	O
,	O
but	O
great	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100165
# text = Harry! Harry! Happy birthday!
Harry	B-PER
!	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O
Happy	O
birthday	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100166
# text = Wow.
Wow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100167
# text = You all right, Harry? You seem very quiet.
You	O
all	O
right	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
?	O
You	O
seem	O
very	O
quiet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100168
# text = He killed my parents, didn't he? The one who gave me this. You know, Hagrid, I know you do.
He	O
killed	O
my	O
parents	O
,	O
did	O
n't	O
he	O
?	O
The	O
one	O
who	O
gave	O
me	O
this	O
.	O
You	O
know	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
I	O
know	O
you	O
do	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100169
# text = First, and understand this, Harry, 'cause it's very important. Not all wizards are good. Some of them go bad. A few years ago, there was one wizard who went as bad as you can go. And his name was V-...his name was V-...
First	O
,	O
and	O
understand	O
this	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
'	O
cause	O
it	O
's	O
very	O
important	O
.	O
Not	O
all	O
wizards	O
are	O
good	O
.	O
Some	O
of	O
them	O
go	O
bad	O
.	O
A	O
few	O
years	O
ago	O
,	O
there	O
was	O
one	O
wizard	O
who	O
went	O
as	O
bad	O
as	O
you	O
can	O
go	O
.	O
And	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
V	O
...	O
his	O
name	O
was	O
V	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100170
# text = Maybe if you wrote it down?
Maybe	O
if	O
you	O
wrote	O
it	O
down	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100171
# text = No, I can't spell it. All right.  Voldemort.
No	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
spell	O
it	O
.	O
All	O
right	O
.	O
Voldemort	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100172
# text = Voldemort?
Voldemort	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100173
# text = Shh!!
Shh	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100174
# text = It was dark times, Harry, dark times.  Voldemort started to gather some followers, brought 'em over to the dark side. Anyone that stood up to him ended up dead. Your parents fought against him, but nobody lived once he decided to kill 'em.  Nobody...not one.  Cept you.
It	O
was	O
dark	O
times	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
dark	O
times	O
.	O
Voldemort	B-PER
started	O
to	O
gather	O
some	O
followers	O
,	O
brought	O
'	O
em	O
over	O
to	O
the	O
dark	O
side	O
.	O
Anyone	O
that	O
stood	O
up	O
to	O
him	O
ended	O
up	O
dead	O
.	O
Your	O
parents	O
fought	O
against	O
him	O
,	O
but	O
nobody	O
lived	O
once	O
he	O
decided	O
to	O
kill	O
'	O
em	O
.	O
Nobody	O
...	O
not	O
one	O
.	O
Cept	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100175
# text = Me? Voldemort tried to kill...me?
Me	O
?	O
Voldemort	B-PER
tried	O
to	O
kill	O
...	O
me	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100176
# text = Yes. That ain't no ordinary cut on your forehead, Harry. A mark like that only comes from being touched by a curse...and an evil curse at that.
Yes	O
.	O
That	O
ai	O
n't	O
no	O
ordinary	O
cut	O
on	O
your	O
forehead	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
A	O
mark	O
like	O
that	O
only	O
comes	O
from	O
being	O
touched	O
by	O
a	O
curse	O
...	O
and	O
an	O
evil	O
curse	O
at	O
that	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100177
# text = What happened to...to You-Know-Who?
What	O
happened	O
to	O
...	O
to	O
You	B-PER
Know	I-PER
Who	I-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100178
# text = Well, some say he died. Codswallop in my opinion. Nope, I reckon he's out there, still, too tired to go on. But one thing's absolutely certain. Something about you stumped him that night. That's why you're famous. That's why everybody knows your name. You're the boy who lived.
Well	O
,	O
some	O
say	O
he	O
died	O
.	O
Codswallop	O
in	O
my	O
opinion	O
.	O
Nope	O
,	O
I	O
reckon	O
he	O
's	O
out	O
there	O
,	O
still	O
,	O
too	O
tired	O
to	O
go	O
on	O
.	O
But	O
one	O
thing	O
's	O
absolutely	O
certain	O
.	O
Something	O
about	O
you	O
stumped	O
him	O
that	O
night	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
why	O
you	O
're	O
famous	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
why	O
everybody	O
knows	O
your	O
name	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
the	O
boy	O
who	O
lived	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100179
# text = What're you looking at?  Blimey, is that the time? Sorry, Harry, I'm gonna have to leave you. Dumbledore'll be wanting his- well, he'll be wanting to see me. Now, uh, your train leaves in 10 minutes. Here's your ticket.  Stick to it, Harry that's very important. Stick to your ticket.
What	O
're	O
you	O
looking	O
at	O
?	O
Blimey	O
,	O
is	O
that	O
the	O
time	O
?	O
Sorry	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
I	O
'm	O
gonna	O
have	O
to	O
leave	O
you	O
.	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
'll	O
be	O
wanting	O
his	O
well	O
,	O
he	O
'll	O
be	O
wanting	O
to	O
see	O
me	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
uh	O
,	O
your	O
train	O
leaves	O
in	O
10	O
minutes	O
.	O
Here	O
's	O
your	O
ticket	O
.	O
Stick	O
to	O
it	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
that	O
's	O
very	O
important	O
.	O
Stick	O
to	O
your	O
ticket	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100180
# text = Platform 9 3/4? But, Hagrid, there must be a mistake. This says Platform 9 3/4. There's no such thing...is there?
Platform	B-LOC
9	I-LOC
3/4	I-LOC
?	O
But	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
,	O
there	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
mistake	O
.	O
This	O
says	O
Platform	B-LOC
9	I-LOC
3/4	I-LOC
.	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
such	O
thing	O
...	O
is	O
there	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100181
# text = Sorry.
Sorry	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100182
# text = Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse	O
me	O
,	O
excuse	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100183
# text = Right on your left, ma'am.
Right	O
on	O
your	O
left	O
,	O
ma	O
'	O
am	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100184
# text = Excuse me, sir. Can you tell me where I might find Platform 9 3/4?
Excuse	O
me	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
where	O
I	O
might	O
find	O
Platform	B-LOC
9	I-LOC
3/4	I-LOC
?	O

# sent_id = 100185
# text = 9 3/4? Think you're being funny, do ya?
9	B-LOC
3/4	I-LOC
?	O
Think	O
you	O
're	O
being	O
funny	O
,	O
do	O
ya	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100186
# text = It's the same year after year. Always packed with Muggles, of course.
It	O
's	O
the	O
same	O
year	O
after	O
year	O
.	O
Always	O
packed	O
with	O
Muggles	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100187
# text = Muggles?
Muggles	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100188
# text = Come on. Platform 9 3/4 this way! All right, Percy, you first.
Come	O
on	O
.	O
Platform	B-LOC
9	I-LOC
3/4	I-LOC
this	O
way	O
!	O
All	O
right	O
,	O
Percy	B-PER
,	O
you	O
first	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100189
# text = Fred, you next.
Fred	B-PER
,	O
you	O
next	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100190
# text = He's not Fred, I am!
He	O
's	O
not	O
Fred	B-PER
,	O
I	O
am	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100191
# text = Honestly, woman, you call yourself our mother.
Honestly	O
,	O
woman	O
,	O
you	O
call	O
yourself	O
our	O
mother	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100192
# text = Oh, I'm sorry, George.
Oh	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
sorry	O
,	O
George	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100193
# text = I'm only joking. I am Fred.
I	O
'm	O
only	O
joking	O
.	O
I	O
am	O
Fred	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100194
# text = Excuse me! C-could you tell me how to-
Excuse	O
me	O
!	O
C	O
could	O
you	O
tell	O
me	O
how	O
to	O

# sent_id = 100195
# text = How to get on the platform? Yes, not to worry, dear. It's Ron's first time to Hogwarts as well.  Now, all you've got to do is walk straight at the wall between platforms 9 and 10. Best do it at a bit of a run if you're nervous.
How	O
to	O
get	O
on	O
the	O
platform	O
?	O
Yes	O
,	O
not	O
to	O
worry	O
,	O
dear	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
Ron	B-PER
's	O
first	O
time	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
as	O
well	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
all	O
you	O
've	O
got	O
to	O
do	O
is	O
walk	O
straight	O
at	O
the	O
wall	O
between	O
platforms	O
9	O
and	O
10	O
.	O
Best	O
do	O
it	O
at	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
a	O
run	O
if	O
you	O
're	O
nervous	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100196
# text = Good luck.
Good	O
luck	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100197
# text = Excuse me, do you mind? Everywhere else is full.
Excuse	O
me	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
mind	O
?	O
Everywhere	O
else	O
is	O
full	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100198
# text = No, not at all.
No	O
,	O
not	O
at	O
all	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100199
# text = I'm Ron, by the way. Ron Weasley.
I	O
'm	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
.	O
Ron	B-PER
Weasley	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100200
# text = I'm Harry. Harry Potter.
I	O
'm	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100201
# text = So-so it's true? I mean, do you really have the...the...
So	O
so	O
it	O
's	O
true	O
?	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
really	O
have	O
the	O
...	O
the	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100202
# text = The what?
The	O
what	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100203
# text = Scar...?
Scar	O
...	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100204
# text = Oh
Oh	O

# sent_id = 100205
# text = Wicked.
Wicked	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100206
# text = Anything off the trolley, dears?
Anything	O
off	O
the	O
trolley	O
,	O
dears	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100207
# text = No, thanks, I'm all set.
No	O
,	O
thanks	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
all	O
set	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100208
# text = We'll take the lot!
We	O
'll	O
take	O
the	O
lot	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100209
# text = Whoa!
Whoa	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100210
# text = Bertie Bott's Every Flavour Beans?
Bertie	B-PER
Bott	I-PER
's	O
Every	O
Flavour	O
Beans	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100211
# text = They mean every flavour! There's chocolate and peppermint, and there's also spinach, liver and tripe. George sweared he got a bogey-flavoured one once!
They	O
mean	O
every	O
flavour	O
!	O
There	O
's	O
chocolate	O
and	O
peppermint	O
,	O
and	O
there	O
's	O
also	O
spinach	O
,	O
liver	O
and	O
tripe	O
.	O
George	B-PER
sweared	O
he	O
got	O
a	O
bogey	O
flavoured	O
one	O
once	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100212
# text = These aren't real chocolate frogs, are they?
These	O
are	O
n't	O
real	O
chocolate	O
frogs	O
,	O
are	O
they	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100213
# text = It's just a spell. Besides, it's the cards you want. Each pack's got a famous witch or wizard. I got about 500 meself.  Watch it!  Oh, that's rotten luck. They've only got one good jump in them to begin with.
It	O
's	O
just	O
a	O
spell	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
cards	O
you	O
want	O
.	O
Each	O
pack	O
's	O
got	O
a	O
famous	O
witch	O
or	O
wizard	O
.	O
I	O
got	O
about	O
500	O
meself	O
.	O
Watch	O
it	O
!	O
Oh	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
rotten	O
luck	O
.	O
They	O
've	O
only	O
got	O
one	O
good	O
jump	O
in	O
them	O
to	O
begin	O
with	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100214
# text = I got Dumbledore!
I	O
got	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100215
# text = I got about 6 of him.
I	O
got	O
about	O
6	O
of	O
him	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100216
# text = Hey, he's gone!
Hey	O
,	O
he	O
's	O
gone	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100217
# text = Well, you can't expect him to hang around all day, can you?  This is Scabbers, by the way, pathetic, isn't he?
Well	O
,	O
you	O
ca	O
n't	O
expect	O
him	O
to	O
hang	O
around	O
all	O
day	O
,	O
can	O
you	O
?	O
This	O
is	O
Scabbers	B-PER
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
pathetic	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
he	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100218
# text = A little.
A	O
little	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100219
# text = Fred gave me a spell as to turn him yellow. Want to see?
Fred	B-PER
gave	O
me	O
a	O
spell	O
as	O
to	O
turn	O
him	O
yellow	O
.	O
Want	O
to	O
see	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100220
# text = Yeah!
Yeah	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100221
# text = Ahem. Sun-
Ahem	O
.	O
Sun	O

# sent_id = 100222
# text = Has anyone seen a toad? A boy named Neville's lost one.
Has	O
anyone	O
seen	O
a	O
toad	O
?	O
A	O
boy	O
named	O
Neville	B-PER
's	O
lost	O
one	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100223
# text = No.
No	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100224
# text = Oh, are you doing magic? Let's see then.
Oh	O
,	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
magic	O
?	O
Let	O
's	O
see	O
then	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100225
# text = Sunshine, daises, butter mellow, turn this stupid fat rat yellow!
Sunshine	O
,	O
daises	O
,	O
butter	O
mellow	O
,	O
turn	O
this	O
stupid	O
fat	O
rat	O
yellow	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100226
# text = Are you sure that's a real spell? Well, it's not very good, is it? Of course I've only tried a few simple spells myself, and they've all worked for me. For example...  Oculus Reparo.  That's better, isn't it? Holy Cricket, you're Harry Potter. I'm Hermione Granger...and you are...?
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
that	O
's	O
a	O
real	O
spell	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
not	O
very	O
good	O
,	O
is	O
it	O
?	O
Of	O
course	O
I	O
've	O
only	O
tried	O
a	O
few	O
simple	O
spells	O
myself	O
,	O
and	O
they	O
've	O
all	O
worked	O
for	O
me	O
.	O
For	O
example	O
...	O
Oculus	O
Reparo	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
better	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
it	O
?	O
Holy	O
Cricket	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O
I	O
'm	O
Hermione	B-PER
Granger	I-PER
...	O
and	O
you	O
are	O
...	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100227
# text = I'm...Ron Weasley.
I	O
'm	O
...	O
Ron	B-PER
Weasley	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100228
# text = Pleasure. You two better change into your robes. I expect we'll be arriving soon.  You've got dirt, on your nose, by the way, did you know? Just there.
Pleasure	O
.	O
You	O
two	O
better	O
change	O
into	O
your	O
robes	O
.	O
I	O
expect	O
we	O
'll	O
be	O
arriving	O
soon	O
.	O
You	O
've	O
got	O
dirt	O
,	O
on	O
your	O
nose	O
,	O
by	O
the	O
way	O
,	O
did	O
you	O
know	O
?	O
Just	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100229
# text = Right, then! First years! This way, please! Come on, now, don't be shy! Come on now, hurry up!
Right	O
,	O
then	O
!	O
First	O
years	O
!	O
This	O
way	O
,	O
please	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
be	O
shy	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
hurry	O
up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100230
# text = Hello, Harry.
Hello	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100231
# text = Hey, Hagrid.
Hey	O
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100232
# text = Whoaa!
Whoaa	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100233
# text = Right then. This way to the boats! Come on, now, follow me.
Right	O
then	O
.	O
This	O
way	O
to	O
the	O
boats	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
now	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100234
# text = Wicked.
Wicked	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100235
# text = Welcome to Hogwarts. Now, in a few moments, you will pass through these doors and join your classmates. But before you can take your seats, you must be sorted into your houses. They are Gryffindor, Hufflepuff, Ravenclaw, and Slytherin. Now while you re here, your house will be like your family. Your triumphs will earn you house points. Any rule breaking, and you will lose points. At the end of the year, the house with the most points is awarded the house cup.
Welcome	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O
Now	O
,	O
in	O
a	O
few	O
moments	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
pass	O
through	O
these	O
doors	O
and	O
join	O
your	O
classmates	O
.	O
But	O
before	O
you	O
can	O
take	O
your	O
seats	O
,	O
you	O
must	O
be	O
sorted	O
into	O
your	O
houses	O
.	O
They	O
are	O
Gryffindor	O
,	O
Hufflepuff	O
,	O
Ravenclaw	O
,	O
and	O
Slytherin	O
.	O
Now	O
while	O
you	O
re	O
here	O
,	O
your	O
house	O
will	O
be	O
like	O
your	O
family	O
.	O
Your	O
triumphs	O
will	O
earn	O
you	O
house	O
points	O
.	O
Any	O
rule	O
breaking	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
lose	O
points	O
.	O
At	O
the	O
end	O
of	O
the	O
year	O
,	O
the	O
house	O
with	O
the	O
most	O
points	O
is	O
awarded	O
the	O
house	O
cup	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100236
# text = Trevor!  Sorry.
Trevor	B-PER
!	O
Sorry	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100237
# text = The sorting ceremony will begin momentarily.
The	O
sorting	O
ceremony	O
will	O
begin	O
momentarily	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100238
# text = It's true then, what they're saying on the train. Harry Potter has come to Hogwarts.  This is Crabbe and Goyle. And I'm Malfoy...Draco Malfoy.  Think my name's funny, do you? No need to ask yours. Red hair, and a hand-me-down robe? You must be a Weasley. Well, soon find that some wizarding families are better than others, Potter. Don t want to go making friends with the wrong sort. I can help you there.
It	O
's	O
true	O
then	O
,	O
what	O
they	O
're	O
saying	O
on	O
the	O
train	O
.	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
has	O
come	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O
This	O
is	O
Crabbe	B-PER
and	O
Goyle	B-PER
.	O
And	O
I	O
'm	O
Malfoy	B-PER
...	O
Draco	B-PER
Malfoy	I-PER
.	O
Think	O
my	O
name	O
's	O
funny	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
No	O
need	O
to	O
ask	O
yours	O
.	O
Red	O
hair	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
hand	O
me	O
down	O
robe	O
?	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
a	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O
Well	O
,	O
soon	O
find	O
that	O
some	O
wizarding	O
families	O
are	O
better	O
than	O
others	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
Don	O
t	O
want	O
to	O
go	O
making	O
friends	O
with	O
the	O
wrong	O
sort	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
help	O
you	O
there	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100239
# text = I think I can tell who the wrong sort are for myself, thanks.
I	O
think	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
who	O
the	O
wrong	O
sort	O
are	O
for	O
myself	O
,	O
thanks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100240
# text = We're ready for you now. Follow me.
We	O
're	O
ready	O
for	O
you	O
now	O
.	O
Follow	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100241
# text = It's not real, the ceiling. It's just bewitched to look like the night sky. I read about it in Hogwarts: A History.
It	O
's	O
not	O
real	O
,	O
the	O
ceiling	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
just	O
bewitched	O
to	O
look	O
like	O
the	O
night	O
sky	O
.	O
I	O
read	O
about	O
it	O
in	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
:	O
A	O
History	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100242
# text = Will you wait along here, please? Now, before we begin, Professor Dumbledore would like to say a few words.
Will	O
you	O
wait	O
along	O
here	O
,	O
please	O
?	O
Now	O
,	O
before	O
we	O
begin	O
,	O
Professor	O
Dumbledore	B-PER
would	O
like	O
to	O
say	O
a	O
few	O
words	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100243
# text = I have a few start of term notices I wish to announce. The first years please note that the dark forest is strictly forbidden to all students. Also, our caretaker, Mr. Filch  has asked me to remind you that the 3rd floor corridor on the right hand side is out of bounds to everyone who does not wish to die a most painful death. Thank you.
I	O
have	O
a	O
few	O
start	O
of	O
term	O
notices	O
I	O
wish	O
to	O
announce	O
.	O
The	O
first	O
years	O
please	O
note	O
that	O
the	O
dark	O
forest	O
is	O
strictly	O
forbidden	O
to	O
all	O
students	O
.	O
Also	O
,	O
our	O
caretaker	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Filch	B-PER
has	O
asked	O
me	O
to	O
remind	O
you	O
that	O
the	O
3rd	O
floor	O
corridor	O
on	O
the	O
right	O
hand	O
side	O
is	O
out	O
of	O
bounds	O
to	O
everyone	O
who	O
does	O
not	O
wish	O
to	O
die	O
a	O
most	O
painful	O
death	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100244
# text = When I call your name, you will come forth, I shall place the sorting hat on your head, and you will be sorted into your houses. Hermione Granger.
When	O
I	O
call	O
your	O
name	O
,	O
you	O
will	O
come	O
forth	O
,	O
I	O
shall	O
place	O
the	O
sorting	O
hat	O
on	O
your	O
head	O
,	O
and	O
you	O
will	O
be	O
sorted	O
into	O
your	O
houses	O
.	O
Hermione	B-PER
Granger	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100245
# text = Oh, no. Okay, relax.
Oh	O
,	O
no	O
.	O
Okay	O
,	O
relax	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100246
# text = Mental that one, I'm telling you.
Mental	O
that	O
one	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
telling	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100247
# text = Ah, right then...hmm...right. Okay...Gryffindor!!
Ah	O
,	O
right	O
then	O
...	O
hmm	O
...	O
right	O
.	O
Okay	O
...	O
Gryffindor	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100248
# text = Draco Malfoy.
Draco	B-PER
Malfoy	I-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100249
# text = SLYTHERIN!
SLYTHERIN	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100250
# text = There isn't a witch or wizard who went bad who wasn t in Slytherin.
There	O
is	O
n't	O
a	O
witch	O
or	O
wizard	O
who	O
went	O
bad	O
who	O
wasn	O
t	O
in	O
Slytherin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100251
# text = Susan Bones.
Susan	B-PER
Bones	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100252
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100253
# text = Harry, what is it?
Harry	B-PER
,	O
what	O
is	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100254
# text = Nothing... nothing, I'm fine.
Nothing	O
...	O
nothing	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
fine	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100255
# text = Let's see...I know...Hufflepuff!
Let	O
's	O
see	O
...	O
I	O
know	O
...	O
Hufflepuff	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100256
# text = Ronald Weasley.
Ronald	B-PER
Weasley	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100257
# text = Ha! Another Weasley. I know just what to do with you... Gryffindor!!
Ha	O
!	O
Another	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O
I	O
know	O
just	O
what	O
to	O
do	O
with	O
you	O
...	O
Gryffindor	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100258
# text = Harry Potter.
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100259
# text = Hmm...difficult, very difficult. Plenty of courage I see, not a bad mind, either. There's talent, oh yes, and a thirst to prove yourself. But where to put you?
Hmm	O
...	O
difficult	O
,	O
very	O
difficult	O
.	O
Plenty	O
of	O
courage	O
I	O
see	O
,	O
not	O
a	O
bad	O
mind	O
,	O
either	O
.	O
There	O
's	O
talent	O
,	O
oh	O
yes	O
,	O
and	O
a	O
thirst	O
to	O
prove	O
yourself	O
.	O
But	O
where	O
to	O
put	O
you	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100260
# text = Not Slytherin. Not Slytherin.
Not	O
Slytherin	O
.	O
Not	O
Slytherin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100261
# text = Not Slytherin, eh? Are you sure? You could be great, you know. It s all here in your head. And Slytherin will help you on the way to greatness! There's no doubt about that. No?
Not	O
Slytherin	O
,	O
eh	O
?	O
Are	O
you	O
sure	O
?	O
You	O
could	O
be	O
great	O
,	O
you	O
know	O
.	O
It	O
s	O
all	O
here	O
in	O
your	O
head	O
.	O
And	O
Slytherin	O
will	O
help	O
you	O
on	O
the	O
way	O
to	O
greatness	O
!	O
There	O
's	O
no	O
doubt	O
about	O
that	O
.	O
No	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100262
# text = Not Slytherin...anything but Slytherin.
Not	O
Slytherin	O
...	O
anything	O
but	O
Slytherin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100263
# text = Well, if you're sure... better be... GRYFFINDOR!!
Well	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
're	O
sure	O
...	O
better	O
be	O
...	O
GRYFFINDOR	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100264
# text = We got Potter! We got Potter!
We	O
got	O
Potter	B-PER
!	O
We	O
got	O
Potter	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100265
# text = We got Potter! We got Potter!
We	O
got	O
Potter	B-PER
!	O
We	O
got	O
Potter	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100266
# text = Your attention, please.
Your	O
attention	O
,	O
please	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100267
# text = Let the feast...begin.
Let	O
the	O
feast	O
...	O
begin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100268
# text = Wow.
Wow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100269
# text = I'm half and half. Me dad's a Muggle. Mam's a witch. Bit of a nasty shock for him when he found out.
I	O
'm	O
half	O
and	O
half	O
.	O
Me	O
dad	O
's	O
a	O
Muggle	O
.	O
Mam	O
's	O
a	O
witch	O
.	O
Bit	O
of	O
a	O
nasty	O
shock	O
for	O
him	O
when	O
he	O
found	O
out	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100270
# text = Say, Percy, who's that teacher talking to Professor Quirrell?
Say	O
,	O
Percy	B-PER
,	O
who	O
's	O
that	O
teacher	O
talking	O
to	O
Professor	O
Quirrell	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100271
# text = Oh, that's Professor Snape, head of Slytherin house.
Oh	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
Professor	O
Snape	B-PER
,	O
head	O
of	O
Slytherin	O
house	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100272
# text = What's he teach?
What	O
's	O
he	O
teach	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100273
# text = Potions. But everyone knows it's the Dark Arts he fancies. He's been after Quirrell s job for years.
Potions	O
.	O
But	O
everyone	O
knows	O
it	O
's	O
the	O
Dark	O
Arts	O
he	O
fancies	O
.	O
He	O
's	O
been	O
after	O
Quirrell	B-PER
s	O
job	O
for	O
years	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100274
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100275
# text = Hello! How are you? Welcome to Gryffindor.
Hello	O
!	O
How	O
are	O
you	O
?	O
Welcome	O
to	O
Gryffindor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100276
# text = Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo	O
hoo	O
hoo	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100277
# text = Look, it s the Bloody Baron!
Look	O
,	O
it	O
s	O
the	O
Bloody	B-PER
Baron	I-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100278
# text = Hello, Sir Nicholas. Have a nice summer?
Hello	O
,	O
Sir	O
Nicholas	B-PER
.	O
Have	O
a	O
nice	O
summer	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100279
# text = Dismal. Once again, my request to join the headless hunt has been denied.
Dismal	O
.	O
Once	O
again	O
,	O
my	O
request	O
to	O
join	O
the	O
headless	B-ORG
hunt	I-ORG
has	O
been	O
denied	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100280
# text = I know you! You're Nearly Headless Nick!
I	O
know	O
you	O
!	O
You	O
're	O
Nearly	B-PER
Headless	I-PER
Nick	I-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100281
# text = I prefer Sir Nicholas if you don't mind.
I	O
prefer	O
Sir	O
Nicholas	B-PER
if	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100282
# text = Nearly headless? How can you be nearly headless?
Nearly	O
headless	O
?	O
How	O
can	O
you	O
be	O
nearly	O
headless	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100283
# text = Like this.
Like	O
this	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100284
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100285
# text = Gryffindors, follow me, please. Keep up. Thank you.
Gryffindors	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
,	O
please	O
.	O
Keep	O
up	O
.	O
Thank	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100286
# text = Ravenclaws, follow me. This way.
Ravenclaws	O
,	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
This	O
way	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100287
# text = This is the most direct path to the dormitories. Oh, and keep an eye on the staircases...they like to change.
This	O
is	O
the	O
most	O
direct	O
path	O
to	O
the	O
dormitories	O
.	O
Oh	O
,	O
and	O
keep	O
an	O
eye	O
on	O
the	O
staircases	O
...	O
they	O
like	O
to	O
change	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100288
# text = Keep up, please, and follow me. Quickly now, come on. Come on.
Keep	O
up	O
,	O
please	O
,	O
and	O
follow	O
me	O
.	O
Quickly	O
now	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100289
# text = Seamus, that picture's moving!
Seamus	B-PER
,	O
that	O
picture	O
's	O
moving	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100290
# text = Look at that one, Harry!
Look	O
at	O
that	O
one	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100291
# text = I think she fancies you.
I	O
think	O
she	O
fancies	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100292
# text = Oh, look! Look! Who's that girl?
Oh	O
,	O
look	O
!	O
Look	O
!	O
Who	O
's	O
that	O
girl	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100293
# text = Welcome to Hogwarts.
Welcome	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
.	O

# sent_id = 100294
# text = Who's that?
Who	O
's	O
that	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100295
# text = Password?
Password	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100296
# text = Caput Draconis.  Follow me, everyone. Keep up, quickly, come on.
Caput	O
Draconis	O
.	O
Follow	O
me	O
,	O
everyone	O
.	O
Keep	O
up	O
,	O
quickly	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100297
# text = Oh, wow.
Oh	O
,	O
wow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100298
# text = Gather 'round here. Welcome to the Gryffindor Common Room. Boy's dormitories, upstairs and down to your left. Girls, the same on your right. You'll find that your belongings have already been brought up.
Gather	O
'	O
round	O
here	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
the	O
Gryffindor	O
Common	O
Room	O
.	O
Boy	O
's	O
dormitories	O
,	O
upstairs	O
and	O
down	O
to	O
your	O
left	O
.	O
Girls	O
,	O
the	O
same	O
on	O
your	O
right	O
.	O
You	O
'll	O
find	O
that	O
your	O
belongings	O
have	O
already	O
been	O
brought	O
up	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100299
# text = Whew, we made it. Can you imagine the look on McGonagall's face if we were late?
Whew	O
,	O
we	O
made	O
it	O
.	O
Can	O
you	O
imagine	O
the	O
look	O
on	O
McGonagall	B-PER
's	O
face	O
if	O
we	O
were	O
late	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100300
# text = That was bloody brilliant.
That	O
was	O
bloody	O
brilliant	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100301
# text = Thank you for that assessment, Mr. Weasley. Perhaps if I were to transfigure Mr. Potter and yourself into a pocketwatch, that way one of you might be on time.
Thank	O
you	O
for	O
that	O
assessment	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Weasley	B-PER
.	O
Perhaps	O
if	O
I	O
were	O
to	O
transfigure	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
and	O
yourself	O
into	O
a	O
pocketwatch	O
,	O
that	O
way	O
one	O
of	O
you	O
might	O
be	O
on	O
time	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100302
# text = We got lost.
We	O
got	O
lost	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100303
# text = Then perhaps a map? I trust you don't need one to find your seats.
Then	O
perhaps	O
a	O
map	O
?	O
I	O
trust	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
need	O
one	O
to	O
find	O
your	O
seats	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100304
# text = There will be no foolish wand waving or silly incantations in this class. As such, I don't expect many of you to appreciate the subtle science and exact art that is potion making. However, for those select few...  who possess the predisposition, I can teach you how to bewitch the mind and ensnare the senses. I can tell you how to bottle fame, brew glory and even put a stopper...  in death.  Then again, maybe some of you have come to Hogwarts in possession of abilities so formidable that you feel confidant enough to not...pay...attention.  Mr. Potter. Our...new...celebrity. Tell me, what would I get if I added powdered root of asphodel to an infusion of wormwood?  You don't know? Well, let's try again. Where, Mr. Potter, would you look if I asked you to find me a bezoar?
There	O
will	O
be	O
no	O
foolish	O
wand	O
waving	O
or	O
silly	O
incantations	O
in	O
this	O
class	O
.	O
As	O
such	O
,	O
I	O
do	O
n't	O
expect	O
many	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
appreciate	O
the	O
subtle	O
science	O
and	O
exact	O
art	O
that	O
is	O
potion	O
making	O
.	O
However	O
,	O
for	O
those	O
select	O
few	O
...	O
who	O
possess	O
the	O
predisposition	O
,	O
I	O
can	O
teach	O
you	O
how	O
to	O
bewitch	O
the	O
mind	O
and	O
ensnare	O
the	O
senses	O
.	O
I	O
can	O
tell	O
you	O
how	O
to	O
bottle	O
fame	O
,	O
brew	O
glory	O
and	O
even	O
put	O
a	O
stopper	O
...	O
in	O
death	O
.	O
Then	O
again	O
,	O
maybe	O
some	O
of	O
you	O
have	O
come	O
to	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
in	O
possession	O
of	O
abilities	O
so	O
formidable	O
that	O
you	O
feel	O
confidant	O
enough	O
to	O
not	O
...	O
pay	O
...	O
attention	O
.	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
Our	O
...	O
new	O
...	O
celebrity	O
.	O
Tell	O
me	O
,	O
what	O
would	O
I	O
get	O
if	O
I	O
added	O
powdered	O
root	O
of	O
asphodel	O
to	O
an	O
infusion	O
of	O
wormwood	O
?	O
You	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
?	O
Well	O
,	O
let	O
's	O
try	O
again	O
.	O
Where	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
,	O
would	O
you	O
look	O
if	O
I	O
asked	O
you	O
to	O
find	O
me	O
a	O
bezoar	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100305
# text = I don't know, sir.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100306
# text = And what is the difference between monkshood and wolfbane?
And	O
what	O
is	O
the	O
difference	O
between	O
monkshood	O
and	O
wolfbane	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100307
# text = I don't know, sir.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
know	O
,	O
sir	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100308
# text = Pity. Clearly, fame isn't everything...  is it, Mr. Potter?
Pity	O
.	O
Clearly	O
,	O
fame	O
is	O
n't	O
everything	O
...	O
is	O
it	O
,	O
Mr.	O
Potter	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100309
# text = Clearly, Hermione knows. Since it's a pity not to ask her.
Clearly	O
,	O
Hermione	B-PER
knows	O
.	O
Since	O
it	O
's	O
a	O
pity	O
not	O
to	O
ask	O
her	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100310
# text = Silence.  And put her hand down, you silly girl.  For your information, Potter... asphodel and wormwood make a sleeping potion so powerful, it is known as the Draught of Living Death. A bezoar is a stone taken from the stomach of a goat and it will save you from most poisons. As for monkshood and wolfsbane, they are the same plant, which also goes by the name of aconite.  Well?  Why aren't you all copying this down?  And Gryffindors, note that five points, will be taken from your house... for your classmate's cheek.
Silence	O
.	O
And	O
put	O
her	O
hand	O
down	O
,	O
you	O
silly	O
girl	O
.	O
For	O
your	O
information	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
...	O
asphodel	O
and	O
wormwood	O
make	O
a	O
sleeping	O
potion	O
so	O
powerful	O
,	O
it	O
is	O
known	O
as	O
the	O
Draught	O
of	O
Living	O
Death	O
.	O
A	O
bezoar	O
is	O
a	O
stone	O
taken	O
from	O
the	O
stomach	O
of	O
a	O
goat	O
and	O
it	O
will	O
save	O
you	O
from	O
most	O
poisons	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
monkshood	O
and	O
wolfsbane	O
,	O
they	O
are	O
the	O
same	O
plant	O
,	O
which	O
also	O
goes	O
by	O
the	O
name	O
of	O
aconite	O
.	O
Well	O
?	O
Why	O
are	O
n't	O
you	O
all	O
copying	O
this	O
down	O
?	O
And	O
Gryffindors	O
,	O
note	O
that	O
five	O
points	O
,	O
will	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
your	O
house	O
...	O
for	O
your	O
classmate	O
's	O
cheek	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100311
# text = Eye of rabbit, harp string hum. Turn this water, into rum.  Eye of rabbit, harp string hum...
Eye	O
of	O
rabbit	O
,	O
harp	O
string	O
hum	O
.	O
Turn	O
this	O
water	O
,	O
into	O
rum	O
.	O
Eye	O
of	O
rabbit	O
,	O
harp	O
string	O
hum	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100312
# text = What's Seamus trying to do to that glass of water?
What	O
's	O
Seamus	B-PER
trying	O
to	O
do	O
to	O
that	O
glass	O
of	O
water	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100313
# text = Turn it into rum. Actually managed a weak tea yesterday, before-
Turn	O
it	O
into	O
rum	O
.	O
Actually	O
managed	O
a	O
weak	O
tea	O
yesterday	O
,	O
before	O

# sent_id = 100314
# text = Ah. Mail's here!
Ah	O
.	O
Mail	O
's	O
here	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100315
# text = Can I borrow this?  Thanks.
Can	O
I	O
borrow	O
this	O
?	O
Thanks	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100316
# text = Hey, look! Neville's got a Remembrall!
Hey	O
,	O
look	O
!	O
Neville	B-PER
's	O
got	O
a	O
Remembrall	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100317
# text = I've read about those. When the smoke turns red,  it means you've forgotten something.
I	O
've	O
read	O
about	O
those	O
.	O
When	O
the	O
smoke	O
turns	O
red	O
,	O
it	O
means	O
you	O
've	O
forgotten	O
something	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100318
# text = The only problem is, I can't remember what I've forgotten.
The	O
only	O
problem	O
is	O
,	O
I	O
ca	O
n't	O
remember	O
what	O
I	O
've	O
forgotten	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100319
# text = Hey, Ron, somebody broke into Gringotts, listen.  Believed to be the work of dark witches or wizards unknown, Gringotts goblins, while acknowledging the breach, insist that nothing was taken. The vault in question, number 713, had in fact been emptied earlier that same day. That's odd. That's the vault Hagrid and I went to.
Hey	O
,	O
Ron	B-PER
,	O
somebody	O
broke	O
into	O
Gringotts	B-ORG
,	O
listen	O
.	O
Believed	O
to	O
be	O
the	O
work	O
of	O
dark	O
witches	O
or	O
wizards	O
unknown	O
,	O
Gringotts	B-ORG
goblins	O
,	O
while	O
acknowledging	O
the	O
breach	O
,	O
insist	O
that	O
nothing	O
was	O
taken	O
.	O
The	O
vault	O
in	O
question	O
,	O
number	O
713	O
,	O
had	O
in	O
fact	O
been	O
emptied	O
earlier	O
that	O
same	O
day	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
odd	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
the	O
vault	O
Hagrid	B-PER
and	O
I	O
went	O
to	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100320
# text = Good afternoon, class.
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
class	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100321
# text = Good afternoon, Madam Hooch.
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Madam	O
Hooch	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100322
# text = Good afternoon, Amanda, good afternoon.  Welcome to your first flying lesson. Well, what are you waiting for? Everyone step up to the left side of their broomstick. Come on now, hurry up. Stick your right hand over the broom and say, up!
Good	O
afternoon	O
,	O
Amanda	B-PER
,	O
good	O
afternoon	O
.	O
Welcome	O
to	O
your	O
first	O
flying	O
lesson	O
.	O
Well	O
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
waiting	O
for	O
?	O
Everyone	O
step	O
up	O
to	O
the	O
left	O
side	O
of	O
their	O
broomstick	O
.	O
Come	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
hurry	O
up	O
.	O
Stick	O
your	O
right	O
hand	O
over	O
the	O
broom	O
and	O
say	O
,	O
up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100323
# text = Up!
Up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100324
# text = Wow.
Wow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100325
# text = Up!
Up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100326
# text = With feeling!
With	O
feeling	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100327
# text = Up. Up. Up. Up.
Up	O
.	O
Up	O
.	O
Up	O
.	O
Up	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100328
# text = Up!!  Ooh!  Shut up, Harry.
Up	O
!	O
!	O
Ooh	O
!	O
Shut	O
up	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100329
# text = Now, once you've got hold of your broom, I want you to mount it. And grip it tight, you don't want to be sliding off the end.  When I blow my whistle, I want each of you to kick off from the ground, hard. Keep your broom steady, hover for a moment, and then lean forward slightly and touch back down. On my whistle...3...2...
Now	O
,	O
once	O
you	O
've	O
got	O
hold	O
of	O
your	O
broom	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
mount	O
it	O
.	O
And	O
grip	O
it	O
tight	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
want	O
to	O
be	O
sliding	O
off	O
the	O
end	O
.	O
When	O
I	O
blow	O
my	O
whistle	O
,	O
I	O
want	O
each	O
of	O
you	O
to	O
kick	O
off	O
from	O
the	O
ground	O
,	O
hard	O
.	O
Keep	O
your	O
broom	O
steady	O
,	O
hover	O
for	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
and	O
then	O
lean	O
forward	O
slightly	O
and	O
touch	O
back	O
down	O
.	O
On	O
my	O
whistle	O
...	O
3	O
...	O
2	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100330
# text = Oh...
Oh	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100331
# text = Mr. Longbottom.
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100332
# text = Neville, what are you doing?
Neville	B-PER
,	O
what	O
are	O
you	O
doing	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100333
# text = Neville...Neville...
Neville	B-PER
...	O
Neville	B-PER
...	O

# sent_id = 100334
# text = We're not supposed to take off, yet.
We	O
're	O
not	O
supposed	O
to	O
take	O
off	O
,	O
yet	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100335
# text = M-M-Mr. Longbottom! Mr. Longbottom!
M	O
M	O
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
!	O
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100336
# text = AHH!
AHH	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100337
# text = Mr. Longbottom!
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100338
# text = Down! Down! Ahhhh!
Down	O
!	O
Down	O
!	O
Ahhhh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100339
# text = Neville!
Neville	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100340
# text = Help!!!
Help	O
!	O
!	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100341
# text = Come back down this instant!
Come	O
back	O
down	O
this	O
instant	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100342
# text = AHH!
AHH	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100343
# text = Help!
Help	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100344
# text = Mr. Longbottom-!
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100345
# text = Ahhhh! Whoa! Ahhh!  Oh. Ah...help!  Ahh!
Ahhhh	O
!	O
Whoa	O
!	O
Ahhh	O
!	O
Oh	O
.	O
Ah	O
...	O
help	O
!	O
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100346
# text = Everyone out of the way!  Come on, get up.
Everyone	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
way	O
!	O
Come	O
on	O
,	O
get	O
up	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100347
# text = Is he alright?
Is	O
he	O
alright	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100348
# text = Owowowow.
Owowowow	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100349
# text = Oh, oh, oh, oh dear. It's a broken wrist. Tch, tch, tch. Good boy, come on now, up you get.  Everyone's to keep their feet firmly on the ground while I take Mr. Longbottom to the hospital wing. Understand? If I see a single broom in the air, the one riding it will find themselves out of Hogwarts before they can say, Quidditch.
Oh	O
,	O
oh	O
,	O
oh	O
,	O
oh	O
dear	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
a	O
broken	O
wrist	O
.	O
Tch	O
,	O
tch	O
,	O
tch	O
.	O
Good	O
boy	O
,	O
come	O
on	O
now	O
,	O
up	O
you	O
get	O
.	O
Everyone	O
's	O
to	O
keep	O
their	O
feet	O
firmly	O
on	O
the	O
ground	O
while	O
I	O
take	O
Mr.	O
Longbottom	B-PER
to	O
the	O
hospital	O
wing	O
.	O
Understand	O
?	O
If	O
I	O
see	O
a	O
single	O
broom	O
in	O
the	O
air	O
,	O
the	O
one	O
riding	O
it	O
will	O
find	O
themselves	O
out	O
of	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
before	O
they	O
can	O
say	O
,	O
Quidditch	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100350
# text = Did you see his face? Maybe if the fat lump had given this a squeeze, he'd have remembered to fall on his fat arse.
Did	O
you	O
see	O
his	O
face	O
?	O
Maybe	O
if	O
the	O
fat	O
lump	O
had	O
given	O
this	O
a	O
squeeze	O
,	O
he	O
'd	O
have	O
remembered	O
to	O
fall	O
on	O
his	O
fat	O
arse	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100351
# text = Give it here, Malfoy.
Give	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100352
# text = No. I think I'll leave it somewhere for Longbottom to find.  How 'bout up on the roof?  What's the matter, Potter? Bit beyond your reach?
No	O
.	O
I	O
think	O
I	O
'll	O
leave	O
it	O
somewhere	O
for	O
Longbottom	B-PER
to	O
find	O
.	O
How	O
'	O
bout	O
up	O
on	O
the	O
roof	O
?	O
What	O
's	O
the	O
matter	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
?	O
Bit	O
beyond	O
your	O
reach	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100353
# text = Harry, no way! You heard what Madam Hooch said! Besides, you don't even know how to fly.  What an idiot.
Harry	B-PER
,	O
no	O
way	O
!	O
You	O
heard	O
what	O
Madam	O
Hooch	B-PER
said	O
!	O
Besides	O
,	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
even	O
know	O
how	O
to	O
fly	O
.	O
What	O
an	O
idiot	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100354
# text = Give it here, Malfoy, or I'll knock you off your broom!
Give	O
it	O
here	O
,	O
Malfoy	B-PER
,	O
or	O
I	O
'll	O
knock	O
you	O
off	O
your	O
broom	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100355
# text = Is that so?  Have it your way, then!
Is	O
that	O
so	O
?	O
Have	O
it	O
your	O
way	O
,	O
then	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100356
# text = Good job, Harry!
Good	O
job	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
!	O

# sent_id = 100357
# text = Oh, that was wicked, Harry.
Oh	O
,	O
that	O
was	O
wicked	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100358
# text = Harry Potter?  Follow me.
Harry	B-PER
Potter	I-PER
?	O
Follow	O
me	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100359
# text = An iguana s-such as this is...
An	O
iguana	O
s	O
such	O
as	O
this	O
is	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100360
# text = You wait here.
You	O
wait	O
here	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100361
# text = ... an essential in-gredient.
...	O
an	O
essential	O
in	O
gredient	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100362
# text = Professor Quirrell, excuse me, excuse me. Could I borrow Wood for a moment, please?
Professor	O
Quirrell	B-PER
,	O
excuse	O
me	O
,	O
excuse	O
me	O
.	O
Could	O
I	O
borrow	O
Wood	B-PER
for	O
a	O
moment	O
,	O
please	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100363
# text = Oh. Y-yes, of course.  And the vampire b-bat...
Oh	O
.	O
Y	O
yes	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
And	O
the	O
vampire	O
b	O
bat	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100364
# text = Potter, this is Oliver Wood. Wood, I have found you a Seeker!
Potter	B-PER
,	O
this	O
is	O
Oliver	B-PER
Wood	I-PER
.	O
Wood	B-PER
,	O
I	O
have	O
found	O
you	O
a	O
Seeker	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100365
# text = Have you heard? Harry Potter's the new Gryffindor Seeker. I always knew he'd do well.
Have	O
you	O
heard	O
?	O
Harry	B-PER
Potter	B-PER
's	O
the	O
new	O
Gryffindor	O
Seeker	O
.	O
I	O
always	O
knew	O
he	O
'd	O
do	O
well	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100366
# text = Seeker? But first years never make their house teams! You must be the youngest Quidditch player in...
Seeker	O
?	O
But	O
first	O
years	O
never	O
make	O
their	O
house	O
teams	O
!	O
You	O
must	O
be	O
the	O
youngest	O
Quidditch	O
player	O
in	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100367
# text = A century, according to McGonagall.
A	O
century	O
,	O
according	O
to	O
McGonagall	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100368
# text = Hey, well done, Harry, Wood's just told us!
Hey	O
,	O
well	O
done	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
Wood	B-PER
's	O
just	O
told	O
us	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100369
# text = Fred and George are on the team, too. Beaters.
Fred	B-PER
and	O
George	B-PER
are	O
on	O
the	O
team	O
,	O
too	O
.	O
Beaters	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100370
# text = Our job is to make sure that you don't get bloodied up too bad. Can't make any promises, of course. Rough game, Quidditch.
Our	O
job	O
is	O
to	O
make	O
sure	O
that	O
you	O
do	O
n't	O
get	O
bloodied	O
up	O
too	O
bad	O
.	O
Ca	O
n't	O
make	O
any	O
promises	O
,	O
of	O
course	O
.	O
Rough	O
game	O
,	O
Quidditch	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100371
# text = Brutal. But no one's died in years. Someone will vanish occasionally...
Brutal	B-PER
.	O
But	O
no	O
one	O
's	O
died	O
in	O
years	O
.	O
Someone	O
will	O
vanish	O
occasionally	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100372
# text = But they'll turn up in a month or two!
But	O
they	O
'll	O
turn	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
month	O
or	O
two	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100373
# text = Oh, go on, Harry, Quidditch is great. Best game there is! And you'll be great, too!
Oh	O
,	O
go	O
on	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
Quidditch	O
is	O
great	O
.	O
Best	O
game	O
there	O
is	O
!	O
And	O
you	O
'll	O
be	O
great	O
,	O
too	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100374
# text = But I've never even played Quidditch. What if I make a fool of myself?
But	O
I	O
've	O
never	O
even	O
played	O
Quidditch	O
.	O
What	O
if	O
I	O
make	O
a	O
fool	O
of	O
myself	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100375
# text = You won't make a fool of yourself. It's in your blood.
You	O
wo	O
n't	O
make	O
a	O
fool	O
of	O
yourself	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
in	O
your	O
blood	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100376
# text = Whoa. Harry, you never told me your father was a Seeker, too.
Whoa	O
.	O
Harry	B-PER
,	O
you	O
never	O
told	O
me	O
your	O
father	O
was	O
a	O
Seeker	O
,	O
too	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100377
# text = I-I didn't know.
I	O
I	O
did	O
n't	O
know	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100378
# text = I'm telling you, it's spooky. She knows more about you than you do.
I	O
'm	O
telling	O
you	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
spooky	O
.	O
She	O
knows	O
more	O
about	O
you	O
than	O
you	O
do	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100379
# text = Who doesn't?
Who	O
does	O
n't	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100380
# text = Ahh!
Ahh	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100381
# text = What's happening?
What	O
's	O
happening	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100382
# text = The staircases change, remember?
The	O
staircases	O
change	O
,	O
remember	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100383
# text = Let's go this way.
Let	O
's	O
go	O
this	O
way	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100384
# text = Before the staircase moves again.
Before	O
the	O
staircase	O
moves	O
again	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100385
# text = Does anyone feel like...we shouldn't be here?
Does	O
anyone	O
feel	O
like	O
...	O
we	O
should	O
n't	O
be	O
here	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100386
# text = We're not supposed to be here. This is the 3rd floor. It's forbidden.
We	O
're	O
not	O
supposed	O
to	O
be	O
here	O
.	O
This	O
is	O
the	O
3rd	O
floor	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
forbidden	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100387
# text = Let's go.
Let	O
's	O
go	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100388
# text = It's Filch's cat!
It	O
's	O
Filch	B-PER
's	O
cat	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100389
# text = Run!
Run	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100390
# text = Quick! Let s hide though that door!
Quick	O
!	O
Let	O
s	O
hide	O
though	O
that	O
door	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100391
# text = It's locked!
It	O
's	O
locked	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100392
# text = That's it, we're done for!
That	O
's	O
it	O
,	O
we	O
're	O
done	O
for	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100393
# text = Oh, move over!  Alohomora.  Get in.
Oh	O
,	O
move	O
over	O
!	O
Alohomora	O
.	O
Get	O
in	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100394
# text = Alohomora?
Alohomora	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100395
# text = Standard book of spells, Chapter 7.
Standard	B-MISC
book	O
of	O
spells	O
,	O
Chapter	O
7	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100396
# text = Anyone here, my sweet?  Come on.
Anyone	O
here	O
,	O
my	O
sweet	O
?	O
Come	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100397
# text = Filch is gone.
Filch	O
is	O
gone	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100398
# text = Probably thinks this door's locked.
Probably	O
thinks	O
this	O
door	O
's	O
locked	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100399
# text = It was locked.
It	O
was	O
locked	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100400
# text = And for good reason.
And	O
for	O
good	O
reason	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100401
# text = AHHHHHHH!
AHHHHHHH	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100402
# text = What do they think they're doing?? Keeping a thing like that locked up in a school.
What	O
do	O
they	O
think	O
they	O
're	O
doing	O
?	O
?	O
Keeping	O
a	O
thing	O
like	O
that	O
locked	O
up	O
in	O
a	O
school	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100403
# text = You don't use your eyes, do you? Didn't you see what it was standing on?
You	O
do	O
n't	O
use	O
your	O
eyes	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
?	O
Did	O
n't	O
you	O
see	O
what	O
it	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100404
# text = I wasn't looking at its feet! I was a bit preoccupied with its heads. Or maybe you didn't notice, there were three!
I	O
was	O
n't	O
looking	O
at	O
its	O
feet	O
!	O
I	O
was	O
a	O
bit	O
preoccupied	O
with	O
its	O
heads	O
.	O
Or	O
maybe	O
you	O
did	O
n't	O
notice	O
,	O
there	O
were	O
three	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100405
# text = It was standing on a trap door. Which means it wasn't there by accident. It's guarding something.
It	O
was	O
standing	O
on	O
a	O
trap	O
door	O
.	O
Which	O
means	O
it	O
was	O
n't	O
there	O
by	O
accident	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
guarding	O
something	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100406
# text = Guarding something?
Guarding	O
something	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100407
# text = That's right. Now, if you two don't mind, I'm going to bed before either of you come up with another clever idea to get us killed... or worse, expelled!
That	O
's	O
right	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
if	O
you	O
two	O
do	O
n't	O
mind	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
going	O
to	O
bed	O
before	O
either	O
of	O
you	O
come	O
up	O
with	O
another	O
clever	O
idea	O
to	O
get	O
us	O
killed	O
...	O
or	O
worse	O
,	O
expelled	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100408
# text = She needs to sort out her priorities!
She	O
needs	O
to	O
sort	O
out	O
her	O
priorities	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100409
# text = Quidditch is easy enough to understand. Each time has seven players, 3 chasers, 2 beaters, 1 keeper and a seeker. That's you. There are three kinds of balls.  This one's called the Quaffle. Now, the chasers handle the Quaffle and try to put it through one of those three hoops.  The keeper, that's me, defends the hoops.  With me so far?
Quidditch	O
is	O
easy	O
enough	O
to	O
understand	O
.	O
Each	O
time	O
has	O
seven	O
players	O
,	O
3	O
chasers	O
,	O
2	O
beaters	O
,	O
1	O
keeper	O
and	O
a	O
seeker	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
you	O
.	O
There	O
are	O
three	O
kinds	O
of	O
balls	O
.	O
This	O
one	O
's	O
called	O
the	O
Quaffle	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
the	O
chasers	O
handle	O
the	O
Quaffle	O
and	O
try	O
to	O
put	O
it	O
through	O
one	O
of	O
those	O
three	O
hoops	O
.	O
The	O
keeper	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
me	O
,	O
defends	O
the	O
hoops	O
.	O
With	O
me	O
so	O
far	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100410
# text = I think so. What are those?
I	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
What	O
are	O
those	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100411
# text = You better take this.  Careful now, it's comin' back.  Eh, not bad, Potter, you'd make a fair beater... Uh-oh.
You	O
better	O
take	O
this	O
.	O
Careful	O
now	O
,	O
it	O
's	O
comin	O
'	O
back	O
.	O
Eh	O
,	O
not	O
bad	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
,	O
you	O
'd	O
make	O
a	O
fair	O
beater	O
...	O
Uh	O
oh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100412
# text = What is that?
What	O
is	O
that	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100413
# text = Bludger. Nasty little buggers. But you are the seeker, and the only thing I want you to worry about is this... the Golden Snitch.
Bludger	O
.	O
Nasty	O
little	O
buggers	O
.	O
But	O
you	O
are	O
the	O
seeker	O
,	O
and	O
the	O
only	O
thing	O
I	O
want	O
you	O
to	O
worry	O
about	O
is	O
this	O
...	O
the	O
Golden	O
Snitch	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100414
# text = I like this ball.
I	O
like	O
this	O
ball	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100415
# text = Ah, you like it now. Just wait. It's wicked fast and damn near impossible to see.
Ah	O
,	O
you	O
like	O
it	O
now	O
.	O
Just	O
wait	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
wicked	O
fast	O
and	O
damn	O
near	O
impossible	O
to	O
see	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100416
# text = What do I do with it?
What	O
do	O
I	O
do	O
with	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100417
# text = You catch it... before the other team's seeker. You catch this, the game is over. You catch this, Potter, and we win.
You	O
catch	O
it	O
...	O
before	O
the	O
other	O
team	O
's	O
seeker	O
.	O
You	O
catch	O
this	O
,	O
the	O
game	O
is	O
over	O
.	O
You	O
catch	O
this	O
,	O
Potter	O
,	O
and	O
we	O
win	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100418
# text = Whoa.
Whoa	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100419
# text = One of a wizard's most rudimentary skills is levitation the ability to make objects fly. Uh, do you all have your feathers?  Good. Now, uh, don't forget the nice wrist movement we've been practicing, hmm? The swish and flick. Everyone.
One	O
of	O
a	O
wizard	O
's	O
most	O
rudimentary	O
skills	O
is	O
levitation	O
the	O
ability	O
to	O
make	O
objects	O
fly	O
.	O
Uh	O
,	O
do	O
you	O
all	O
have	O
your	O
feathers	O
?	O
Good	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
uh	O
,	O
do	O
n't	O
forget	O
the	O
nice	O
wrist	O
movement	O
we	O
've	O
been	O
practicing	O
,	O
hmm	O
?	O
The	O
swish	O
and	O
flick	O
.	O
Everyone	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100420
# text = The swish and flick.
The	O
swish	O
and	O
flick	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100421
# text = Good. And enunciate. Wingardium Leviosa. Off you go then.
Good	O
.	O
And	O
enunciate	O
.	O
Wingardium	O
Leviosa	O
.	O
Off	O
you	O
go	O
then	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100422
# text = Wingardium Levio-saaa.
Wingardium	O
Levio	O
saaa	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100423
# text = Wingardrium Leviosar!
Wingardrium	O
Leviosar	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100424
# text = Stop, stop, stop. You're going to take someone's eye out. Besides, you're saying it wrong. It's Levi-o-sa, not Leviosar.
Stop	O
,	O
stop	O
,	O
stop	O
.	O
You	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
take	O
someone	O
's	O
eye	O
out	O
.	O
Besides	O
,	O
you	O
're	O
saying	O
it	O
wrong	O
.	O
It	O
's	O
Levi	O
o	O
sa	O
,	O
not	O
Leviosar	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100425
# text = You do it then if you're so clever. Go on, go on.
You	O
do	O
it	O
then	O
if	O
you	O
're	O
so	O
clever	O
.	O
Go	O
on	O
,	O
go	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100426
# text = Wingardium Leviosa.
Wingardium	O
Leviosa	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100427
# text = Oh, well done! See here, everyone! Ms. Granger's done it! Oh, splendid!
Oh	O
,	O
well	O
done	O
!	O
See	O
here	O
,	O
everyone	O
!	O
Ms	O
.	O
Granger	B-PER
's	O
done	O
it	O
!	O
Oh	O
,	O
splendid	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100428
# text = Wingard Levosa.
Wingard	O
Levosa	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100429
# text = Well done, dear.
Well	O
done	O
,	O
dear	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100430
# text = Whooaaa! Ooh.
Whooaaa	O
!	O
Ooh	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100431
# text = I think we're going to need another feather over here, Professor.
I	O
think	O
we	O
're	O
going	O
to	O
need	O
another	O
feather	O
over	O
here	O
,	O
Professor	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100432
# text = It's Levioooosa, not Leviosaaaar.  She's a nightmare, honestly. No wonder she hasn't got any friends!
It	O
's	O
Levioooosa	O
,	O
not	O
Leviosaaaar	B-PER
.	O
She	O
's	O
a	O
nightmare	O
,	O
honestly	O
.	O
No	O
wonder	O
she	O
has	O
n't	O
got	O
any	O
friends	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100433
# text = I think she heard you.
I	O
think	O
she	O
heard	O
you	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100434
# text = Where's Hermione?
Where	O
's	O
Hermione	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100435
# text = Parvati Patil said that she wouldn't come out of the girl's bathroom. She said that she'd been in there all afternoon...crying.
Parvati	B-PER
Patil	I-PER
said	O
that	O
she	O
would	O
n't	O
come	O
out	O
of	O
the	O
girl	O
's	O
bathroom	O
.	O
She	O
said	O
that	O
she	O
'd	O
been	O
in	O
there	O
all	O
afternoon	O
...	O
crying	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100436
# text = TROLL! IN THE DUNGEON! T-TROOLLL IN THE DUNGEON!!  Thought you ought to know.
TROLL	O
!	O
IN	O
THE	O
DUNGEON	O
!	O
T	O
TROOLLL	O
IN	O
THE	O
DUNGEON	O
!	O
!	O
Thought	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
know	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100437
# text = SILLLLLEEENNNNCEEEEE!  Everyone will please, not panic. Now, Prefects will lead their houses back to the dormitories. Teachers will follow me to the dungeons.
SILLLLLEEENNNNCEEEEE	O
!	O
Everyone	O
will	O
please	O
,	O
not	O
panic	O
.	O
Now	O
,	O
Prefects	O
will	O
lead	O
their	O
houses	O
back	O
to	O
the	O
dormitories	O
.	O
Teachers	O
will	O
follow	O
me	O
to	O
the	O
dungeons	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100438
# text = Hufflepuff, this way!
Hufflepuff	O
,	O
this	O
way	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100439
# text = Stay together!
Stay	O
together	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100440
# text = Gryffindors, keep up please. And stay alert!
Gryffindors	O
,	O
keep	O
up	O
please	O
.	O
And	O
stay	O
alert	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100441
# text = How could a troll get in?
How	O
could	O
a	O
troll	O
get	O
in	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100442
# text = Not by itself. Trolls are really stupid. Probably people playing jokes.  What?
Not	O
by	O
itself	O
.	O
Trolls	O
are	O
really	O
stupid	O
.	O
Probably	O
people	O
playing	O
jokes	O
.	O
What	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100443
# text = Hermione! She doesn't know!
Hermione	B-PER
!	O
She	O
does	O
n't	O
know	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100444
# text = I think the troll's left the dungeon!
I	O
think	O
the	O
troll	O
's	O
left	O
the	O
dungeon	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100445
# text = It s going into the Girl's Bathroom!
It	O
s	O
going	O
into	O
the	O
Girl	O
's	O
Bathroom	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100446
# text = Hermione, move!
Hermione	B-PER
,	O
move	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100447
# text = Help! Help!
Help	O
!	O
Help	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100448
# text = Hey, pea brain!
Hey	O
,	O
pea	O
brain	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100449
# text = Ahhh! Help!
Ahhh	O
!	O
Help	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100450
# text = Whooa! Whoa, whoa!
Whooa	O
!	O
Whoa	O
,	O
whoa	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100451
# text = Ew.
Ew	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100452
# text = Whoa, whoa whoa!
Whoa	O
,	O
whoa	O
whoa	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100453
# text = Do something!
Do	O
something	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100454
# text = What?
What	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100455
# text = Anything! Hurry up!
Anything	O
!	O
Hurry	O
up	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100456
# text = Swish and flick!
Swish	O
and	O
flick	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100457
# text = Wingardium Leviosa!  Cool.
Wingardium	O
Leviosa	O
!	O
Cool	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100458
# text = Is it...dead?
Is	O
it	O
...	O
dead	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100459
# text = I don't think so. Just knocked out.  Ew. Troll bogies.
I	O
do	O
n't	O
think	O
so	O
.	O
Just	O
knocked	O
out	O
.	O
Ew	O
.	O
Troll	O
bogies	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100460
# text = Oh! Oh, my goodness! E-Explain yourselves, both of you!
Oh	O
!	O
Oh	O
,	O
my	O
goodness	O
!	O
E	O
Explain	O
yourselves	O
,	O
both	O
of	O
you	O
!	O

# sent_id = 100461
# text = Well, what it is...
Well	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100462
# text = Well, what it is...
Well	O
,	O
what	O
it	O
is	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100463
# text = It's my fault, Professor McGonagall.
It	O
's	O
my	O
fault	O
,	O
Professor	O
McGonagall	B-PER
.	O

# sent_id = 100464
# text = Miss Granger?
Miss	O
Granger	B-PER
?	O

# sent_id = 100465
# text = I went looking for the troll. I'd read about them and thought I could handle it. But I was wrong. If Harry and Ron hadn't come and found me...I'd probably be dead.
I	O
went	O
looking	O
for	O
the	O
troll	O
.	O
I	O
'd	O
read	O
about	O
them	O
and	O
thought	O
I	O
could	O
handle	O
it	O
.	O
But	O
I	O
was	O
wrong	O
.	O
If	O
Harry	B-PER
and	O
Ron	B-PER
had	O
n't	O
come	O
and	O
found	O
me	O
...	O
I	O
'd	O
probably	O
be	O
dead	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100466
# text = Be that as it may be...it was an extremely foolish thing to do.  I would have expected more rational behavior on your part, Miss Granger. Five points will be taken from Gryffindor for your serious lack of judgment.  As for you two gentlemen I just hope you realize how fortunate you are. Not many students could take on a fully grown mountain troll and live to tell the tale. Five points...will be awarded to each of you.  For sheer dumb luck.
Be	O
that	O
as	O
it	O
may	O
be	O
...	O
it	O
was	O
an	O
extremely	O
foolish	O
thing	O
to	O
do	O
.	O
I	O
would	O
have	O
expected	O
more	O
rational	O
behavior	O
on	O
your	O
part	O
,	O
Miss	O
Granger	B-PER
.	O
Five	O
points	O
will	O
be	O
taken	O
from	O
Gryffindor	O
for	O
your	O
serious	O
lack	O
of	O
judgment	O
.	O
As	O
for	O
you	O
two	O
gentlemen	O
I	O
just	O
hope	O
you	O
realize	O
how	O
fortunate	O
you	O
are	O
.	O
Not	O
many	O
students	O
could	O
take	O
on	O
a	O
fully	O
grown	O
mountain	O
troll	O
and	O
live	O
to	O
tell	O
the	O
tale	O
.	O
Five	O
points	O
...	O
will	O
be	O
awarded	O
to	O
each	O
of	O
you	O
.	O
For	O
sheer	O
dumb	O
luck	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100467
# text = Perhaps you ought to go...M-might wake up...heh.  Ahh! Hehe....
Perhaps	O
you	O
ought	O
to	O
go	O
...	O
M	O
might	O
wake	O
up	O
...	O
heh	O
.	O
Ahh	O
!	O
Hehe	O
...	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100468
# text = Good for you to get us out of trouble like that.
Good	O
for	O
you	O
to	O
get	O
us	O
out	O
of	O
trouble	O
like	O
that	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100469
# text = Mind you, I mean, we did save her life.
Mind	O
you	O
,	O
I	O
mean	O
,	O
we	O
did	O
save	O
her	O
life	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100470
# text = Mind you, she didn't need saving if you hadn't insulted her.
Mind	O
you	O
,	O
she	O
did	O
n't	O
need	O
saving	O
if	O
you	O
had	O
n't	O
insulted	O
her	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100471
# text = What are friends for?
What	O
are	O
friends	O
for	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100472
# text = Take a bit of toast, mate, go on.
Take	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
toast	O
,	O
mate	O
,	O
go	O
on	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100473
# text = Ron's right, Harry. You're gonna need your strength today.
Ron	B-PER
's	O
right	O
,	O
Harry	B-PER
.	O
You	O
're	O
gonna	O
need	O
your	O
strength	O
today	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100474
# text = I'm not hungry.
I	O
'm	O
not	O
hungry	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100475
# text = Good luck today, Potter. Then again, now that you've proven yourself against a troll, a little game of Quidditch should be easy work for you...even if it is against Slytherin.
Good	O
luck	O
today	O
,	O
Potter	B-PER
.	O
Then	O
again	O
,	O
now	O
that	O
you	O
've	O
proven	O
yourself	O
against	O
a	O
troll	O
,	O
a	O
little	O
game	O
of	O
Quidditch	O
should	O
be	O
easy	O
work	O
for	O
you	O
...	O
even	O
if	O
it	O
is	O
against	O
Slytherin	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100476
# text = That explains the blood.
That	O
explains	O
the	O
blood	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100477
# text = Blood?
Blood	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100478
# text = Listen, last night, I'm guessing Snape let the troll in as a diversion so he could try and get past that 3 headed dog. But, he got himself bitten, that's why he's limping.
Listen	O
,	O
last	O
night	O
,	O
I	O
'm	O
guessing	O
Snape	B-PER
let	O
the	O
troll	O
in	O
as	O
a	O
diversion	O
so	O
he	O
could	O
try	O
and	O
get	O
past	O
that	O
3	O
headed	O
dog	O
.	O
But	O
,	O
he	O
got	O
himself	O
bitten	O
,	O
that	O
's	O
why	O
he	O
's	O
limping	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100479
# text = But why would anyone go near that dog?
But	O
why	O
would	O
anyone	O
go	O
near	O
that	O
dog	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100480
# text = The day I was at Gringotts, Hagrid took something out of one of the vaults. He said it was Hogwarts' business, very secret.
The	O
day	O
I	O
was	O
at	O
Gringotts	B-ORG
,	O
Hagrid	B-PER
took	O
something	O
out	O
of	O
one	O
of	O
the	O
vaults	O
.	O
He	O
said	O
it	O
was	O
Hogwarts	B-ORG
'	O
business	O
,	O
very	O
secret	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100481
# text = So you're saying...
So	O
you	O
're	O
saying	O
...	O

# sent_id = 100482
# text = That's what the dog's guarding. That's what Snape wants.
That	O
's	O
what	O
the	O
dog	O
's	O
guarding	O
.	O
That	O
's	O
what	O
Snape	B-PER
wants	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100483
# text = Bit early for mail, isn't it?
Bit	O
early	O
for	O
mail	O
,	O
is	O
n't	O
it	O
?	O

# sent_id = 100484
# text = But I-I never get mail.
But	O
I	O
I	O
never	O
get	O
mail	O
.	O

# sent_id = 100485
# text = Let's open it.
Let	O
's	O
open	O
it	O
.	O