# newdoc id = hp7diolog.csv
# sent_id = 700001
# text = These are dark times, there is no denying.  Our world has perhaps faced no greater threat than it does today.  But I say this to our citizenry:  we, ever your servants, continue to defend your liberty and repel the forces that would seek to take it from you. Your Ministry remains strong...
1	These	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	dark	O	-	-
4	times	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	there	O	-	-
7	is	O	-	-
8	no	O	-	-
9	denying	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Our	O	-	-
12	world	O	-	-
13	has	O	-	-
14	perhaps	O	-	-
15	faced	O	-	-
16	no	O	-	-
17	greater	O	-	-
18	threat	O	-	-
19	than	O	-	-
20	it	O	-	-
21	does	O	-	-
22	today	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	But	O	-	-
25	I	O	-	-
26	say	O	-	-
27	this	O	-	-
28	to	O	-	-
29	our	O	-	-
30	citizenry	O	-	-
31	:	O	-	-
32	we	O	-	-
33	,	O	-	-
34	ever	O	-	-
35	your	O	-	-
36	servants	O	-	-
37	,	O	-	-
38	continue	O	-	-
39	to	O	-	-
40	defend	O	-	-
41	your	O	-	-
42	liberty	O	-	-
43	and	O	-	-
44	repel	O	-	-
45	the	O	-	-
46	forces	O	-	-
47	that	O	-	-
48	would	O	-	-
49	seek	O	-	-
50	to	O	-	-
51	take	O	-	-
52	it	O	-	-
53	from	O	-	-
54	you	O	-	-
55	.	O	-	-
56	Your	O	-	-
57	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
58	remains	O	-	-
59	strong	O	-	-
60	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700002
# text = Hermione.  Your tea is ready, dear.
1	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Your	O	-	-
4	tea	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	ready	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	dear	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700003
# text = Coming, Mum.
1	Coming	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Mum	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700004
# text = Don't you look lovely.  All packed?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	look	O	-	-
5	lovely	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	All	O	-	-
8	packed	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700005
# text = Are you sure these biscuits are sugar-free?
1	Are	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	sure	O	-	-
4	these	O	-	-
5	biscuits	O	-	-
6	are	O	-	-
7	sugar	O	-	-
8	free	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700006
# text = Quite sure, dear.  See the big bold letters that say 'Sugar Free'?  Dead giveaway.
1	Quite	O	-	-
2	sure	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	dear	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	See	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	big	O	-	-
9	bold	O	-	-
10	letters	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	say	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-
14	Sugar	O	-	-
15	Free	O	-	-
16	'	O	-	-
17	?	O	-	-
18	Dead	O	-	-
19	giveaway	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700007
# text = Mm.  Yes. Hello, kitten.  Don't you look lovely.
1	Mm	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Yes	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Hello	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	kitten	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Do	O	-	-
10	n't	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	look	O	-	-
13	lovely	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700008
# text = Darling, don't be suspicious the biscuits taste so good, be grateful the company's so clever...
1	Darling	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	n't	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	suspicious	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	biscuits	O	-	-
9	taste	O	-	-
10	so	O	-	-
11	good	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	grateful	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	company	O	-	-
17	's	O	-	-
18	so	O	-	-
19	clever	O	-	-
20	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700009
# text = Obliviate.
1	Obliviate	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700010
# text = Goodbye.
1	Goodbye	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700011
# text = What are those?
1	What	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	those	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700012
# text = Close the door.
1	Close	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	door	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700013
# text = These are for the Order.  So many are on the run now, it helps them to stay connected with the rest of us.  Know they're not alone...
1	These	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	for	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Order	B-ORG	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	So	O	-	-
8	many	O	-	-
9	are	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	run	O	-	-
13	now	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	it	O	-	-
16	helps	O	-	-
17	them	O	-	-
18	to	O	-	-
19	stay	O	-	-
20	connected	O	-	-
21	with	O	-	-
22	the	O	-	-
23	rest	O	-	-
24	of	O	-	-
25	us	O	-	-
26	.	O	-	-
27	Know	O	-	-
28	they	O	-	-
29	're	O	-	-
30	not	O	-	-
31	alone	O	-	-
32	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700014
# text = C'mon.  Mum's got dinner ready.
1	C	O	-	-
2	'm	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Mum	O	-	-
6	's	O	-	-
7	got	O	-	-
8	dinner	O	-	-
9	ready	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700015
# text = Severus.  I was beginning to worry you'd lost your way.  Come.  I've saved you a seat.
1	Severus	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	beginning	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	worry	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	'd	O	-	-
10	lost	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	way	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	Come	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	've	O	-	-
18	saved	O	-	-
19	you	O	-	-
20	a	O	-	-
21	seat	O	-	-
22	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700016
# text = You know our hosts, of course, Severus.  Narcissa in particular has been most hospitable.  Lucius, on the other hand, is, I fear, burdened by my presence.  Are you, Lucius?
1	You	O	-	-
2	know	O	-	-
3	our	O	-	-
4	hosts	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	course	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Severus	B-PER	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Narcissa	B-PER	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	particular	O	-	-
14	has	O	-	-
15	been	O	-	-
16	most	O	-	-
17	hospitable	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-
19	Lucius	B-PER	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	on	O	-	-
22	the	O	-	-
23	other	O	-	-
24	hand	O	-	-
25	,	O	-	-
26	is	O	-	-
27	,	O	-	-
28	I	O	-	-
29	fear	O	-	-
30	,	O	-	-
31	burdened	O	-	-
32	by	O	-	-
33	my	O	-	-
34	presence	O	-	-
35	.	O	-	-
36	Are	O	-	-
37	you	O	-	-
38	,	O	-	-
39	Lucius	B-PER	-	-
40	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700017
# text = My lord?
1	My	O	-	-
2	lord	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700018
# text = Are you burdened?
1	Are	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	burdened	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700019
# text = My lord is always welcome here.
1	My	O	-	-
2	lord	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	always	O	-	-
5	welcome	O	-	-
6	here	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700020
# text = You bring news I trust, Severus?
1	You	O	-	-
2	bring	O	-	-
3	news	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	trust	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Severus	B-PER	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700021
# text = It will happen Saturday next.  At nightfall.
1	It	O	-	-
2	will	O	-	-
3	happen	O	-	-
4	Saturday	O	-	-
5	next	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	At	O	-	-
8	nightfall	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700022
# text = And this information comes --
1	And	O	-	-
2	this	O	-	-
3	information	O	-	-
4	comes	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700023
# text = -- from the source we discussed.
1	from	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	source	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	discussed	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700024
# text = I have heard differently, my lord. Dawlish, the Auror, let slip that the Potter boy will not be moved until the thirtieth of this month, the night before he turns seventeen.
1	I	O	-	-
2	have	O	-	-
3	heard	O	-	-
4	differently	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	lord	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Dawlish	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Auror	B-TTL	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	let	O	-	-
15	slip	O	-	-
16	that	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	Potter	B-PER	-	-
19	boy	O	-	-
20	will	O	-	-
21	not	O	-	-
22	be	O	-	-
23	moved	O	-	-
24	until	O	-	-
25	the	O	-	-
26	thirtieth	O	-	-
27	of	O	-	-
28	this	O	-	-
29	month	O	-	-
30	,	O	-	-
31	the	O	-	-
32	night	O	-	-
33	before	O	-	-
34	he	O	-	-
35	turns	O	-	-
36	seventeen	O	-	-
37	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700025
# text = This is a false trail.  The Auror Office no longer plays any part in the protection of Harry Potter. Those closest to him believe we have infiltrated the Ministry.
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	false	O	-	-
5	trail	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	The	O	-	-
8	Auror	B-ORG	-	-
9	Office	I-ORG	-	-
10	no	O	-	-
11	longer	O	-	-
12	plays	O	-	-
13	any	O	-	-
14	part	O	-	-
15	in	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	protection	O	-	-
18	of	O	-	-
19	Harry	B-PER	-	-
20	Potter	I-PER	-	-
21	.	O	-	-
22	Those	O	-	-
23	closest	O	-	-
24	to	O	-	-
25	him	O	-	-
26	believe	O	-	-
27	we	O	-	-
28	have	O	-	-
29	infiltrated	O	-	-
30	the	O	-	-
31	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
32	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700026
# text = Well, they've got that right, then, 'aven't they?
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	they	O	-	-
4	've	O	-	-
5	got	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	right	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	then	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	'	O	-	-
12	ave	O	-	-
13	n't	O	-	-
14	they	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700027
# text = Pius, what say you?
1	Pius	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	what	O	-	-
4	say	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700028
# text = One hears many things, my lord. Whether the truth is among them is not clear.
1	One	O	-	-
2	hears	O	-	-
3	many	O	-	-
4	things	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	lord	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Whether	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	truth	O	-	-
12	is	O	-	-
13	among	O	-	-
14	them	O	-	-
15	is	O	-	-
16	not	O	-	-
17	clear	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700029
# text = Spoken like a true politician. You will, I think, prove most useful, Pius.  Where will he be taken?  The boy?
1	Spoken	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	true	O	-	-
5	politician	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	You	O	-	-
8	will	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	think	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	prove	O	-	-
14	most	O	-	-
15	useful	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	Pius	B-PER	-	-
18	.	O	-	-
19	Where	O	-	-
20	will	O	-	-
21	he	O	-	-
22	be	O	-	-
23	taken	O	-	-
24	?	O	-	-
25	The	O	-	-
26	boy	O	-	-
27	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700030
# text = To a safehouse.  Likely the home of someone in the Order.  I'm told it has been given every manner of protection possible. Once there, it will be impractical to attack him.  We may have compromised the Ministry, but there are those who remain loyal to him.  As long as the Ministry stands, his allies within will have the means at their disposal to insure his safety.
1	To	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	safehouse	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Likely	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	home	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	someone	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Order	B-ORG	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	'm	O	-	-
16	told	O	-	-
17	it	O	-	-
18	has	O	-	-
19	been	O	-	-
20	given	O	-	-
21	every	O	-	-
22	manner	O	-	-
23	of	O	-	-
24	protection	O	-	-
25	possible	O	-	-
26	.	O	-	-
27	Once	O	-	-
28	there	O	-	-
29	,	O	-	-
30	it	O	-	-
31	will	O	-	-
32	be	O	-	-
33	impractical	O	-	-
34	to	O	-	-
35	attack	O	-	-
36	him	O	-	-
37	.	O	-	-
38	We	O	-	-
39	may	O	-	-
40	have	O	-	-
41	compromised	O	-	-
42	the	O	-	-
43	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
44	,	O	-	-
45	but	O	-	-
46	there	O	-	-
47	are	O	-	-
48	those	O	-	-
49	who	O	-	-
50	remain	O	-	-
51	loyal	O	-	-
52	to	O	-	-
53	him	O	-	-
54	.	O	-	-
55	As	O	-	-
56	long	O	-	-
57	as	O	-	-
58	the	O	-	-
59	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
60	stands	O	-	-
61	,	O	-	-
62	his	O	-	-
63	allies	O	-	-
64	within	O	-	-
65	will	O	-	-
66	have	O	-	-
67	the	O	-	-
68	means	O	-	-
69	at	O	-	-
70	their	O	-	-
71	disposal	O	-	-
72	to	O	-	-
73	insure	O	-	-
74	his	O	-	-
75	safety	O	-	-
76	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700031
# text = My lord, if I might, I'd like to volunteer myself for this task. I'd like to kill the boy.
1	My	O	-	-
2	lord	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	if	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	might	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	'd	O	-	-
10	like	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	volunteer	O	-	-
13	myself	O	-	-
14	for	O	-	-
15	this	O	-	-
16	task	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	I	O	-	-
19	'd	O	-	-
20	like	O	-	-
21	to	O	-	-
22	kill	O	-	-
23	the	O	-	-
24	boy	O	-	-
25	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700032
# text = Wormtail!  Have I not spoken to you about keeping our guest quiet?
1	Wormtail	B-ORG	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Have	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	not	O	-	-
6	spoken	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	about	O	-	-
10	keeping	O	-	-
11	our	O	-	-
12	guest	O	-	-
13	quiet	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700033
# text = Yes, m-my lord.  Right away, my lord.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	m	O	-	-
4	my	O	-	-
5	lord	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	Right	O	-	-
8	away	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	lord	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700034
# text = As inspiring as I find your bloodlust, Bellatrix, I must be the one to kill Harry Potter.  But I face an unfortunate complication.  It has recently come to my attention that my wand and Potter's share the same core. They are, in some ways, twins.  We can wound but not fatally harm one another.  Which means, if I am to kill him... I will have to do it with another's wand.
1	As	O	-	-
2	inspiring	O	-	-
3	as	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	find	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	bloodlust	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Bellatrix	B-ORG	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	must	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	one	O	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	kill	O	-	-
18	Harry	B-PERS	-	-
19	Potter	I-PERS	-	-
20	.	O	-	-
21	But	O	-	-
22	I	O	-	-
23	face	O	-	-
24	an	O	-	-
25	unfortunate	O	-	-
26	complication	O	-	-
27	.	O	-	-
28	It	O	-	-
29	has	O	-	-
30	recently	O	-	-
31	come	O	-	-
32	to	O	-	-
33	my	O	-	-
34	attention	O	-	-
35	that	O	-	-
36	my	O	-	-
37	wand	O	-	-
38	and	O	-	-
39	Potter	B-PERS	-	-
40	's	O	-	-
41	share	O	-	-
42	the	O	-	-
43	same	O	-	-
44	core	O	-	-
45	.	O	-	-
46	They	O	-	-
47	are	O	-	-
48	,	O	-	-
49	in	O	-	-
50	some	O	-	-
51	ways	O	-	-
52	,	O	-	-
53	twins	O	-	-
54	.	O	-	-
55	We	O	-	-
56	can	O	-	-
57	wound	O	-	-
58	but	O	-	-
59	not	O	-	-
60	fatally	O	-	-
61	harm	O	-	-
62	one	O	-	-
63	another	O	-	-
64	.	O	-	-
65	Which	O	-	-
66	means	O	-	-
67	,	O	-	-
68	if	O	-	-
69	I	O	-	-
70	am	O	-	-
71	to	O	-	-
72	kill	O	-	-
73	him	O	-	-
74	...	O	-	-
75	I	O	-	-
76	will	O	-	-
77	have	O	-	-
78	to	O	-	-
79	do	O	-	-
80	it	O	-	-
81	with	O	-	-
82	another	O	-	-
83	's	O	-	-
84	wand	O	-	-
85	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700035
# text = Come now.  Surely one of you would like the honor?  What about... you, Lucius?
1	Come	O	-	-
2	now	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Surely	O	-	-
5	one	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	would	O	-	-
9	like	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	honor	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	What	O	-	-
14	about	O	-	-
15	...	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	Lucius	B-PER	-	-
19	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700036
# text = I require your wand.
1	I	O	-	-
2	require	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	wand	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700037
# text = Do I detect elm?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	detect	O	-	-
4	elm	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700038
# text = Yes, my lord.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	lord	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700039
# text = And the core?
1	And	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	core	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700040
# text = Dragon -- dragon heartstring.
1	Dragon	O	-	-
2	dragon	O	-	-
3	heartstring	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700041
# text = My wand?  You can't possibly think I would give you my wand.
1	My	O	-	-
2	wand	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	ca	O	-	-
6	n't	O	-	-
7	possibly	O	-	-
8	think	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	would	O	-	-
11	give	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	wand	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700042
# text = No, my lord.
1	No	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	my	O	-	-
4	lord	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700043
# text = For those of you who do not know, we are joined tonight by Miss Charity Burbage who until recently taught at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry.  Her specialty was Muggle studies. It is Miss Burbage's belief that Muggles are not so different from us.
1	For	O	-	-
2	those	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	who	O	-	-
6	do	O	-	-
7	not	O	-	-
8	know	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	we	O	-	-
11	are	O	-	-
12	joined	O	-	-
13	tonight	O	-	-
14	by	O	-	-
15	Miss	B-TTL	-	-
16	Charity	B-PER	-	-
17	Burbage	I-PER	-	-
18	who	O	-	-
19	until	O	-	-
20	recently	O	-	-
21	taught	O	-	-
22	at	O	-	-
23	Hogwarts	B-ORG	-	-
24	School	I-ORG	-	-
25	of	I-ORG	-	-
26	Witchcraft	I-ORG	-	-
27	and	I-ORG	-	-
28	Wizardry	I-ORG	-	-
29	.	O	-	-
30	Her	O	-	-
31	specialty	O	-	-
32	was	O	-	-
33	Muggle	O	-	-
34	studies	O	-	-
35	.	O	-	-
36	It	O	-	-
37	is	O	-	-
38	Miss	B-TTL	-	-
39	Burbage	B-PER	-	-
40	's	O	-	-
41	belief	O	-	-
42	that	O	-	-
43	Muggles	O	-	-
44	are	O	-	-
45	not	O	-	-
46	so	O	-	-
47	different	O	-	-
48	from	O	-	-
49	us	O	-	-
50	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700044
# text = She would, given her way, have us mate with them.  To her, the mixture of magical and Muggle blood is not an abomination but something to be encouraged.  I, of course, take a contrary view.  But we're all civilized here.  All adults.  We can agree to disagree.
1	She	O	-	-
2	would	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	given	O	-	-
5	her	O	-	-
6	way	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	have	O	-	-
9	us	O	-	-
10	mate	O	-	-
11	with	O	-	-
12	them	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	To	O	-	-
15	her	O	-	-
16	,	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	mixture	O	-	-
19	of	O	-	-
20	magical	O	-	-
21	and	O	-	-
22	Muggle	O	-	-
23	blood	O	-	-
24	is	O	-	-
25	not	O	-	-
26	an	O	-	-
27	abomination	O	-	-
28	but	O	-	-
29	something	O	-	-
30	to	O	-	-
31	be	O	-	-
32	encouraged	O	-	-
33	.	O	-	-
34	I	O	-	-
35	,	O	-	-
36	of	O	-	-
37	course	O	-	-
38	,	O	-	-
39	take	O	-	-
40	a	O	-	-
41	contrary	O	-	-
42	view	O	-	-
43	.	O	-	-
44	But	O	-	-
45	we	O	-	-
46	're	O	-	-
47	all	O	-	-
48	civilized	O	-	-
49	here	O	-	-
50	.	O	-	-
51	All	O	-	-
52	adults	O	-	-
53	.	O	-	-
54	We	O	-	-
55	can	O	-	-
56	agree	O	-	-
57	to	O	-	-
58	disagree	O	-	-
59	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700045
# text = Severus, please.  We're friends...
1	Severus	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	please	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	We	O	-	-
6	're	O	-	-
7	friends	O	-	-
8	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700046
# text = Avada Kedavra!
1	Avada	O	-	-
2	Kedavra	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700047
# text = Nagini... Dinner.
1	Nagini	B-PER	-	-
2	...	O	-	-
3	Dinner	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700048
# text = Come now, Dudley.  Hurry up!
1	Come	O	-	-
2	now	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Dudley	B-PER	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Hurry	O	-	-
7	up	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700049
# text = Time for the teary farewell.
1	Time	O	-	-
2	for	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	teary	O	-	-
5	farewell	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700050
# text = I've lived in this house twenty years.  And now -- in a single night -- I'm expected to leave.
1	I	O	-	-
2	've	O	-	-
3	lived	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	this	O	-	-
6	house	O	-	-
7	twenty	O	-	-
8	years	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	And	O	-	-
11	now	O	-	-
12	in	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	single	O	-	-
15	night	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	'm	O	-	-
18	expected	O	-	-
19	to	O	-	-
20	leave	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700051
# text = They'll torture you.  Even Dudley. If they think you know where I'm going, they'll stop at noth--
1	They	O	-	-
2	'll	O	-	-
3	torture	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Even	O	-	-
7	Dudley	B-PER	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	If	O	-	-
10	they	O	-	-
11	think	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	know	O	-	-
14	where	O	-	-
15	I	O	-	-
16	'm	O	-	-
17	going	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	they	O	-	-
20	'll	O	-	-
21	stop	O	-	-
22	at	O	-	-
23	noth	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700052
# text = You think I don't know that?  You think I don't know what they're capable of?
1	You	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	do	O	-	-
5	n't	O	-	-
6	know	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	You	O	-	-
10	think	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	do	O	-	-
13	n't	O	-	-
14	know	O	-	-
15	what	O	-	-
16	they	O	-	-
17	're	O	-	-
18	capable	O	-	-
19	of	O	-	-
20	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700053
# text = You didn't just lose a mother that night in Godric's Hollow, you know.  I lost a sister.
1	You	O	-	-
2	did	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	just	O	-	-
5	lose	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	mother	O	-	-
8	that	O	-	-
9	night	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	Godric	B-LOC	-	-
12	's	I-LOC	-	-
13	Hollow	I-LOC	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-
16	know	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	I	O	-	-
19	lost	O	-	-
20	a	O	-	-
21	sister	O	-	-
22	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700054
# text = Do you have any?  Magic?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	have	O	-	-
4	any	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	Magic	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700055
# text = What a cruel thing to ask.
1	What	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	cruel	O	-	-
4	thing	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	ask	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700056
# text = Well, this is goodbye then, boy.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	goodbye	O	-	-
6	then	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	boy	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700057
# text = I don't understand.  Isn't he coming with us?
1	I	O	-	-
2	do	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	understand	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Is	O	-	-
7	n't	O	-	-
8	he	O	-	-
9	coming	O	-	-
10	with	O	-	-
11	us	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700058
# text = Who?
1	Who	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700059
# text = Harry.
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700060
# text = Absolutely not.
1	Absolutely	O	-	-
2	not	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700061
# text = Why?
1	Why	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700062
# text = Well, because -- he doesn't want to, do you, boy?
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	because	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	does	O	-	-
6	n't	O	-	-
7	want	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	do	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	boy	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700063
# text = Absolutely not.  Besides, I'm just a waste of space.  Isn't that right, Vernon?
1	Absolutely	O	-	-
2	not	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Besides	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'm	O	-	-
8	just	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	waste	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	space	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	Is	O	-	-
15	n't	O	-	-
16	that	O	-	-
17	right	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	Vernon	B-PER	-	-
20	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700064
# text = Come on, Dudley, we're off.
1	Come	O	-	-
2	on	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Dudley	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	're	O	-	-
8	off	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700065
# text = I don't think you're a waste of space.
1	I	O	-	-
2	do	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	think	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	're	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	waste	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	space	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700066
# text = Well... thanks.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	...	O	-	-
3	thanks	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700067
# text = See you, Big D.
1	See	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Big	B-PER	-	-
5	D	I-PER	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700068
# text = Good riddance.
1	Good	O	-	-
2	riddance	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700069
# text = All righ', 'arry?  Yeh look fit.
1	All	O	-	-
2	righ	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	'	B-PER	-	-
6	arry	I-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-
8	Yeh	O	-	-
9	look	O	-	-
10	fit	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700070
# text = Yeah, he's ruddy gorgeous.  What say we get undercover before someone murders him.
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	's	O	-	-
5	ruddy	O	-	-
6	gorgeous	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	What	O	-	-
9	say	O	-	-
10	we	O	-	-
11	get	O	-	-
12	undercover	O	-	-
13	before	O	-	-
14	someone	O	-	-
15	murders	O	-	-
16	him	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700071
# text = I thought you were looking after the Prime Minister, Kingsley.
1	I	O	-	-
2	thought	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	were	O	-	-
5	looking	O	-	-
6	after	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Prime	B-TTL	-	-
9	Minister	I-TTL	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Kingsley	B-PER	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700072
# text = You're more important.
1	You	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	more	O	-	-
4	important	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700073
# text = Hello, Harry.  Bill Weasley.
1	Hello	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Harry	B-PER	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Bill	B-PER	-	-
6	Weasley	I-PER	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700074
# text = Wasn't always this handsome.
1	Was	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	always	O	-	-
4	this	O	-	-
5	handsome	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700075
# text = Dead ugly.
1	Dead	O	-	-
2	ugly	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700076
# text = True enough.  Owe it all to a werewolf by name of Greyback. Hope to repay the favor one day.
1	True	O	-	-
2	enough	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Owe	O	-	-
5	it	O	-	-
6	all	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	werewolf	O	-	-
10	by	O	-	-
11	name	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	Greyback	B-PER	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	Hope	O	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	repay	O	-	-
18	the	O	-	-
19	favor	O	-	-
20	one	O	-	-
21	day	O	-	-
22	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700077
# text = You are still beautiful to me, William.
1	You	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	still	O	-	-
4	beautiful	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	William	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700078
# text = Just remember, Fleur, once you're married:  Bill takes his steaks on the raw side now.
1	Just	O	-	-
2	remember	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Fleur	B-PER	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	once	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	're	O	-	-
9	married	O	-	-
10	:	O	-	-
11	Bill	B-PER	-	-
12	takes	O	-	-
13	his	O	-	-
14	steaks	O	-	-
15	on	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	raw	O	-	-
18	side	O	-	-
19	now	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700079
# text = My husband, the joker.  By the way, wait until you hear the news! Remus and I are --
1	My	O	-	-
2	husband	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	joker	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	By	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	way	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	wait	O	-	-
12	until	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	hear	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	news	O	-	-
17	!	O	-	-
18	Remus	B-PER	-	-
19	and	O	-	-
20	I	O	-	-
21	are	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700080
# text = All right, all right!  You'll all have time for a cozy catch-up later!  We've got to get the hell out of here and soon!
1	All	O	-	-
2	right	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	right	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	You	O	-	-
8	'll	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	have	O	-	-
11	time	O	-	-
12	for	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	cozy	O	-	-
15	catch	O	-	-
16	up	O	-	-
17	later	O	-	-
18	!	O	-	-
19	We	O	-	-
20	've	O	-	-
21	got	O	-	-
22	to	O	-	-
23	get	O	-	-
24	the	O	-	-
25	hell	O	-	-
26	out	O	-	-
27	of	O	-	-
28	here	O	-	-
29	and	O	-	-
30	soon	O	-	-
31	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700081
# text = Potter, you're underage, which means you've still got the Trace on you.
1	Potter	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	're	O	-	-
5	underage	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	which	O	-	-
8	means	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	've	O	-	-
11	still	O	-	-
12	got	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	Trace	O	-	-
15	on	O	-	-
16	you	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700082
# text = The Trace?
1	The	O	-	-
2	Trace	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700083
# text = You sneeze and the Ministry will know who wipes your nose.  Point is, we have to use those means of transport the Trace can't detect: brooms, thestrals and the like. We'll go in pairs.  That way if anyone's out there waiting for us -- and I reckon there will be -- they won't know which Harry Potter is the real one.
1	You	O	-	-
2	sneeze	O	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
6	will	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	who	O	-	-
9	wipes	O	-	-
10	your	O	-	-
11	nose	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	Point	O	-	-
14	is	O	-	-
15	,	O	-	-
16	we	O	-	-
17	have	O	-	-
18	to	O	-	-
19	use	O	-	-
20	those	O	-	-
21	means	O	-	-
22	of	O	-	-
23	transport	O	-	-
24	the	O	-	-
25	Trace	O	-	-
26	ca	O	-	-
27	n't	O	-	-
28	detect	O	-	-
29	:	O	-	-
30	brooms	O	-	-
31	,	O	-	-
32	thestrals	O	-	-
33	and	O	-	-
34	the	O	-	-
35	like	O	-	-
36	.	O	-	-
37	We	O	-	-
38	'll	O	-	-
39	go	O	-	-
40	in	O	-	-
41	pairs	O	-	-
42	.	O	-	-
43	That	O	-	-
44	way	O	-	-
45	if	O	-	-
46	anyone	O	-	-
47	's	O	-	-
48	out	O	-	-
49	there	O	-	-
50	waiting	O	-	-
51	for	O	-	-
52	us	O	-	-
53	and	O	-	-
54	I	O	-	-
55	reckon	O	-	-
56	there	O	-	-
57	will	O	-	-
58	be	O	-	-
59	they	O	-	-
60	wo	O	-	-
61	n't	O	-	-
62	know	O	-	-
63	which	O	-	-
64	Harry	B-PER	-	-
65	Potter	I-PER	-	-
66	is	O	-	-
67	the	O	-	-
68	real	O	-	-
69	one	O	-	-
70	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700084
# text = The real one...?
1	The	O	-	-
2	real	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	...	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700085
# text = I believe you're familiar with this particular brew.
1	I	O	-	-
2	believe	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	're	O	-	-
5	familiar	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	this	O	-	-
8	particular	O	-	-
9	brew	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700086
# text = No!  Absolutely not!
1	No	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Absolutely	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700087
# text = I told you he'd take it well.
1	I	O	-	-
2	told	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	'd	O	-	-
6	take	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-
8	well	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700088
# text = If you think I'm going to let people risk their lives for me --
1	If	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	think	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	'm	O	-	-
6	going	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	let	O	-	-
9	people	O	-	-
10	risk	O	-	-
11	their	O	-	-
12	lives	O	-	-
13	for	O	-	-
14	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700089
# text = Never done that before, have we?
1	Never	O	-	-
2	done	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	before	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700090
# text = This is different.  Taking that. Becoming me -- no.
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	different	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Taking	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	Becoming	O	-	-
9	me	O	-	-
10	no	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700091
# text = Well, none of us really fancy it, mate.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	none	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	us	O	-	-
6	really	O	-	-
7	fancy	O	-	-
8	it	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	mate	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700092
# text = Yeah, imagine if something went wrong and we were stuck as scrawny, specky gits forever.
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	imagine	O	-	-
4	if	O	-	-
5	something	O	-	-
6	went	O	-	-
7	wrong	O	-	-
8	and	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	were	O	-	-
11	stuck	O	-	-
12	as	O	-	-
13	scrawny	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	specky	O	-	-
16	gits	O	-	-
17	forever	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700093
# text = Everyone here's of age, Potter, and they've all agreed to take the risk.
1	Everyone	O	-	-
2	here	O	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	age	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Potter	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	they	O	-	-
11	've	O	-	-
12	all	O	-	-
13	agreed	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	take	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	risk	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700094
# text = Technically, I've been coerced. Mundungus Fletcher, Mr. Potter. I've always been a huge admirer.
1	Technically	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	've	O	-	-
5	been	O	-	-
6	coerced	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	Mundungus	B-PER	-	-
9	Fletcher	I-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Mr.	O	B-TTL	-
12	Potter	O	B-PER	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	've	O	-	-
16	always	O	-	-
17	been	O	-	-
18	a	O	-	-
19	huge	O	-	-
20	admirer	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700095
# text = Nip it, Mundungus!  All right, Granger, as discussed.
1	Nip	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Mundungus	B-PER	-	-
5	!	O	-	-
6	All	O	-	-
7	right	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Granger	B-PER	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	as	O	-	-
12	discussed	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700096
# text = Blimey, Hermione!
1	Blimey	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700097
# text = Straight in here, if you please.
1	Straight	O	-	-
2	in	O	-	-
3	here	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	if	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	please	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700098
# text = For those of you who haven't taken Polyjuice Potion before, fair warning.  It tastes like goblin piss.
1	For	O	-	-
2	those	O	-	-
3	of	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	who	O	-	-
6	have	O	-	-
7	n't	O	-	-
8	taken	O	-	-
9	Polyjuice	O	-	-
10	Potion	O	-	-
11	before	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	fair	O	-	-
14	warning	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	It	O	-	-
17	tastes	O	-	-
18	like	O	-	-
19	goblin	O	-	-
20	piss	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700099
# text = Have a lot of experience with that, do you, Mad-Eye?
1	Have	O	-	-
2	a	O	-	-
3	lot	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	experience	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Mad	B-PER	-	-
13	Eye	I-PER	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700100
# text = Just trying to defuse the tension.
1	Just	O	-	-
2	trying	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	defuse	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	tension	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700101
# text = Wow -- we're identical!
1	Wow	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	're	O	-	-
4	identical	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700102
# text = Wow -- we're identical!
1	Wow	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	're	O	-	-
4	identical	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700103
# text = Not yet you aren't.
1	Not	O	-	-
2	yet	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	are	O	-	-
5	n't	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700104
# text = Don't have something a bit more sporty, do you?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	have	O	-	-
4	something	O	-	-
5	a	O	-	-
6	bit	O	-	-
7	more	O	-	-
8	sporty	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	do	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700105
# text = Yes, don't fancy this color at all.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	n't	O	-	-
5	fancy	O	-	-
6	this	O	-	-
7	color	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	all	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700106
# text = Fancy this:  You're not you, so shut it and strip. You'll need to change too, Potter.
1	Fancy	O	-	-
2	this	O	-	-
3	:	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	're	O	-	-
6	not	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	so	O	-	-
10	shut	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	and	O	-	-
13	strip	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	You	O	-	-
16	'll	O	-	-
17	need	O	-	-
18	to	O	-	-
19	change	O	-	-
20	too	O	-	-
21	,	O	-	-
22	Potter	B-PER	-	-
23	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700107
# text = Bill, look away -- I'm 'ideous.
1	Bill	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	look	O	-	-
4	away	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	'm	O	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	ideous	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700108
# text = I knew Ginny was lying about that tattoo.
1	I	O	-	-
2	knew	O	-	-
3	Ginny	B-PER	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	lying	O	-	-
6	about	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	tattoo	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700109
# text = Harry, your eyesight really is awful.
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	eyesight	O	-	-
5	really	O	-	-
6	is	O	-	-
7	awful	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700110
# text = Blimey.  I almost forgot.
1	Blimey	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	almost	O	-	-
5	forgot	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700111
# text = Right then.  We'll be pairing off. Each Potter will have a protector. As for you, Harry...
1	Right	O	-	-
2	then	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	We	O	-	-
5	'll	O	-	-
6	be	O	-	-
7	pairing	O	-	-
8	off	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Each	O	-	-
11	Potter	B-PER	-	-
12	will	O	-	-
13	have	O	-	-
14	a	O	-	-
15	protector	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	As	O	-	-
18	for	O	-	-
19	you	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	Harry	B-PER	-	-
22	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700112
# text = Yes?
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700113
# text = The real Harry!  Where the devil are you, anyway?
1	The	O	-	-
2	real	O	-	-
3	Harry	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	Where	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	devil	O	-	-
8	are	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	anyway	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700114
# text = Here.
1	Here	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700115
# text = You'll ride with Hagrid.
1	You	O	-	-
2	'll	O	-	-
3	ride	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	Hagrid	B-PER	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700116
# text = Brought yeh here sixteen years ago when you were barely bigger than a Bowtruckle. Seems only righ' I should be the one ter take yeh away.
1	Brought	O	-	-
2	yeh	O	-	-
3	here	O	-	-
4	sixteen	O	-	-
5	years	O	-	-
6	ago	O	-	-
7	when	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	were	O	-	-
10	barely	O	-	-
11	bigger	O	-	-
12	than	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	Bowtruckle	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	Seems	O	-	-
17	only	O	-	-
18	righ	O	-	-
19	'	O	-	-
20	I	O	-	-
21	should	O	-	-
22	be	O	-	-
23	the	O	-	-
24	one	O	-	-
25	ter	O	-	-
26	take	O	-	-
27	yeh	O	-	-
28	away	O	-	-
29	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700117
# text = Yeah, it's all very touching. Let's go.
1	Yeah	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	's	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	very	O	-	-
7	touching	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Let	O	-	-
10	's	O	-	-
11	go	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700118
# text = Good luck, everyone.  On the count of three.  One... two --
1	Good	O	-	-
2	luck	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	everyone	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	On	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	count	O	-	-
9	of	O	-	-
10	three	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	One	O	-	-
13	...	O	-	-
14	two	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700119
# text = Hagrid!  We've got to help the others!
1	Hagrid	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	We	O	-	-
4	've	O	-	-
5	got	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	help	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	others	O	-	-
10	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700120
# text = Can't do it, 'arry.  My job's ter get you where we're goin' safe 'n sound -- Mad-Eye's orders!
1	Ca	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	it	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	'	B-PER	-	-
7	arry	I-PER	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	My	O	-	-
10	job	O	-	-
11	's	O	-	-
12	ter	O	-	-
13	get	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	where	O	-	-
16	we	O	-	-
17	're	O	-	-
18	goin	O	-	-
19	'	O	-	-
20	safe	O	-	-
21	'	O	-	-
22	n	O	-	-
23	sound	O	-	-
24	Mad	B-PER	-	-
25	Eye	I-PER	-	-
26	's	O	-	-
27	orders	O	-	-
28	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700121
# text = What was that?
1	What	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700122
# text = Dragon fire!
1	Dragon	O	-	-
2	fire	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700123
# text = That's him!  The real one!
1	That	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	him	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	The	O	-	-
6	real	O	-	-
7	one	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700124
# text = Hol' tight, 'arry!  We've got ter get yeh out of here!
1	Hol	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	tight	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	'	B-PER	-	-
6	arry	I-PER	-	-
7	!	O	-	-
8	We	O	-	-
9	've	O	-	-
10	got	O	-	-
11	ter	O	-	-
12	get	O	-	-
13	yeh	O	-	-
14	out	O	-	-
15	of	O	-	-
16	here	O	-	-
17	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700125
# text = Hagrid... HAGRID...!
1	Hagrid	B-PER	-	-
2	...	O	-	-
3	HAGRID	B-PER	-	-
4	...	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700126
# text = Avada...
1	Avada	O	-	-
2	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700127
# text = Harry!  Hagrid!  What happened?! Have you seen the others?
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Hagrid	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	What	O	-	-
6	happened	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	Have	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	seen	O	-	-
12	the	O	-	-
13	others	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700128
# text = Is no one back yet?
1	Is	O	-	-
2	no	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	yet	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700129
# text = They were on us from the star', Molly -- the Death Eaters.  And You-Know-Who as well.
1	They	O	-	-
2	were	O	-	-
3	on	O	-	-
4	us	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	star	O	-	-
8	'	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	Molly	B-PER	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Death	B-ORG	-	-
13	Eaters	I-ORG	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	And	O	-	-
16	You	B-PER	-	-
17	Know	I-PER	-	-
18	Who	I-PER	-	-
19	as	O	-	-
20	well	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700130
# text = Well, thank goodness you two are all right.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	thank	O	-	-
4	goodness	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	two	O	-	-
7	are	O	-	-
8	all	O	-	-
9	right	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700131
# text = Haven't go' any brandy, have yeh, Molly?  Fer medicinal purposes?
1	Have	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	go	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	any	O	-	-
6	brandy	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	have	O	-	-
9	yeh	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Molly	B-PER	-	-
12	?	O	-	-
13	Fer	O	-	-
14	medicinal	O	-	-
15	purposes	O	-	-
16	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700132
# text = Ron and Tonks should've already been back.  Dad and Fred as well.
1	Ron	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Tonks	B-PER	-	-
4	should	O	-	-
5	've	O	-	-
6	already	O	-	-
7	been	O	-	-
8	back	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Dad	O	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	Fred	B-PER	-	-
13	as	O	-	-
14	well	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700133
# text = Oh my God!  George!
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	my	O	-	-
3	God	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	George	B-PER	-	-
6	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700134
# text = The house!  Quickly!
1	The	O	-	-
2	house	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	Quickly	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700135
# text = My boy!  My darling boy!  What've they done to you?!
1	My	O	-	-
2	boy	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	My	O	-	-
5	darling	O	-	-
6	boy	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-
8	What	O	-	-
9	've	O	-	-
10	they	O	-	-
11	done	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-
15	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700136
# text = Remus!  What're you doing!
1	Remus	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	What	O	-	-
4	're	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	doing	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700137
# text = What creature sat in the corner the first time that Harry Potter visited my office at Hogwarts!
1	What	O	-	-
2	creature	O	-	-
3	sat	O	-	-
4	in	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	corner	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	first	O	-	-
9	time	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	Harry	B-PER	-	-
12	Potter	I-PER	-	-
13	visited	O	-	-
14	my	O	-	-
15	office	O	-	-
16	at	O	-	-
17	Hogwarts	B-ORG	-	-
18	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700138
# text = Are you mad...?
1	Are	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	mad	O	-	-
4	...	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700139
# text = What Creature!
1	What	O	-	-
2	Creature	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700140
# text = A grindylow!
1	A	O	-	-
2	grindylow	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700141
# text = We've been betrayed.  Voldemort knew you were being moved tonight. I had to make sure you weren't an imposter.
1	We	O	-	-
2	've	O	-	-
3	been	O	-	-
4	betrayed	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Voldemort	B-PER	-	-
7	knew	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	were	O	-	-
10	being	O	-	-
11	moved	O	-	-
12	tonight	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	had	O	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	make	O	-	-
18	sure	O	-	-
19	you	O	-	-
20	were	O	-	-
21	n't	O	-	-
22	an	O	-	-
23	imposter	O	-	-
24	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700142
# text = Who did this to him?
1	Who	O	-	-
2	did	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	him	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700143
# text = Snape. He'll be fine, Molly.  But that's Dark Magic.  The damage is done.
1	Snape	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	He	O	-	-
4	'll	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	fine	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Molly	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	But	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	's	O	-	-
13	Dark	O	-	-
14	Magic	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	The	O	-	-
17	damage	O	-	-
18	is	O	-	-
19	done	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700144
# text = Someone else is back.
1	Someone	O	-	-
2	else	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	back	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700145
# text = The last words Albus Dumbledore spoke to the pair of us?
1	The	O	-	-
2	last	O	-	-
3	words	O	-	-
4	Albus	B-PER	-	-
5	Dumbledore	I-PER	-	-
6	spoke	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	pair	O	-	-
10	of	O	-	-
11	us	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700146
# text = 'Harry is the best hope we have. Trust him.'
1	'	O	-	-
2	Harry	B-PER	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	best	O	-	-
6	hope	O	-	-
7	we	O	-	-
8	have	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Trust	O	-	-
11	him	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700147
# text = What gave you away?
1	What	O	-	-
2	gave	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	away	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700148
# text = Hedwig -- I think.  She was trying to protect me --
1	Hedwig	B-PER	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	think	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	She	O	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	trying	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	protect	O	-	-
10	me	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700149
# text = Hey ya -- Well... thanks.
1	Hey	O	-	-
2	ya	O	-	-
3	Well	O	-	-
4	...	O	-	-
5	thanks	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700150
# text = Deserves that.  Brilliant, he was. Wouldn't be standing here without him.
1	Deserves	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Brilliant	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	he	O	-	-
7	was	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Would	O	-	-
10	n't	O	-	-
11	be	O	-	-
12	standing	O	-	-
13	here	O	-	-
14	without	O	-	-
15	him	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700151
# text = Really?
1	Really	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700152
# text = Always the tone of surprise.
1	Always	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	tone	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	surprise	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700153
# text = Are we the last?  Where's George?
1	Are	O	-	-
2	we	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	last	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	Where	O	-	-
7	's	O	-	-
8	George	B-PER	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700154
# text = Remus.  Where's my son?
1	Remus	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Where	O	-	-
4	's	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	son	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700155
# text = How do you feel, Georgie?
1	How	O	-	-
2	do	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	feel	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Georgie	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700156
# text = Saint-like.
1	Saint	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700157
# text = Come again?
1	Come	O	-	-
2	again	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700158
# text = Saint-like... You see, I'm holy. Holey, Fred, geddit?
1	Saint	O	-	-
2	like	O	-	-
3	...	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	see	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'm	O	-	-
9	holy	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Holey	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	Fred	B-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	geddit	O	-	-
16	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700159
# text = With the whole wide world of ear- related humor at your disposal, you go for holey?  Pathetic.
1	With	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	whole	O	-	-
4	wide	O	-	-
5	world	O	-	-
6	of	O	-	-
7	ear	O	-	-
8	related	O	-	-
9	humor	O	-	-
10	at	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	disposal	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	you	O	-	-
15	go	O	-	-
16	for	O	-	-
17	holey	O	-	-
18	?	O	-	-
19	Pathetic	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700160
# text = Reckon I'm still better-looking than you.  Better-looking than Bill, that's for sure.
1	Reckon	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'm	O	-	-
4	still	O	-	-
5	better	O	-	-
6	looking	O	-	-
7	than	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Better	O	-	-
11	looking	O	-	-
12	than	O	-	-
13	Bill	B-PER	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	that	O	-	-
16	's	O	-	-
17	for	O	-	-
18	sure	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700161
# text = Mad-Eye's dead.
1	Mad	B-PER	-	-
2	Eye	I-PER	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	dead	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700162
# text = Mundungus took one look at Voldemort and Disapparated.
1	Mundungus	B-PER	-	-
2	took	O	-	-
3	one	O	-	-
4	look	O	-	-
5	at	O	-	-
6	Voldemort	B-PER	-	-
7	and	O	-	-
8	Disapparated	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700163
# text = Mad-Eye reckoned You-Know-Who would expect the real Harry to be with the most skilled Auror.  He knew he'd be in the most danger.
1	Mad	B-PER	-	-
2	Eye	I-PER	-	-
3	reckoned	O	-	-
4	You	B-PER	-	-
5	Know	I-PER	-	-
6	Who	I-PER	-	-
7	would	O	-	-
8	expect	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	real	O	-	-
11	Harry	B-PER	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	be	O	-	-
14	with	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	most	O	-	-
17	skilled	O	-	-
18	Auror	B-TTL	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	He	O	-	-
21	knew	O	-	-
22	he	O	-	-
23	'd	O	-	-
24	be	O	-	-
25	in	O	-	-
26	the	O	-	-
27	most	O	-	-
28	danger	O	-	-
29	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700164
# text = It doesn't explain how they knew we were moving Harry tonight.
1	It	O	-	-
2	does	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	explain	O	-	-
5	how	O	-	-
6	they	O	-	-
7	knew	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	were	O	-	-
10	moving	O	-	-
11	Harry	B-PER	-	-
12	tonight	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700165
# text = Wha'?  One of us?  Tha's mad.  I'd wager me life it wasn' none of you lot.  An' if it was me I'd kno', wouldn' I?  Talk in me sleep on occasion, I'll admit, but there's only Fang aroun' ter hear an' mostly it's gibberish an' besides I'd cut me tongue out 'fore 'd betray 'arry e'en in me dreams --
1	Wha	O	-	-
2	'	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-
4	One	O	-	-
5	of	O	-	-
6	us	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-
8	Tha	O	-	-
9	's	O	-	-
10	mad	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	'd	O	-	-
14	wager	O	-	-
15	me	O	-	-
16	life	O	-	-
17	it	O	-	-
18	wasn	O	-	-
19	'	O	-	-
20	none	O	-	-
21	of	O	-	-
22	you	O	-	-
23	lot	O	-	-
24	.	O	-	-
25	An	O	-	-
26	'	O	-	-
27	if	O	-	-
28	it	O	-	-
29	was	O	-	-
30	me	O	-	-
31	I	O	-	-
32	'd	O	-	-
33	kno	O	-	-
34	'	O	-	-
35	,	O	-	-
36	wouldn	O	-	-
37	'	O	-	-
38	I	O	-	-
39	?	O	-	-
40	Talk	O	-	-
41	in	O	-	-
42	me	O	-	-
43	sleep	O	-	-
44	on	O	-	-
45	occasion	O	-	-
46	,	O	-	-
47	I	O	-	-
48	'll	O	-	-
49	admit	O	-	-
50	,	O	-	-
51	but	O	-	-
52	there	O	-	-
53	's	O	-	-
54	only	O	-	-
55	Fang	B-PER	-	-
56	aroun	O	-	-
57	'	O	-	-
58	ter	O	-	-
59	hear	O	-	-
60	an	O	-	-
61	'	O	-	-
62	mostly	O	-	-
63	it	O	-	-
64	's	O	-	-
65	gibberish	O	-	-
66	an	O	-	-
67	'	O	-	-
68	besides	O	-	-
69	I	O	-	-
70	'd	O	-	-
71	cut	O	-	-
72	me	O	-	-
73	tongue	O	-	-
74	out	O	-	-
75	'	O	-	-
76	fore	O	-	-
77	'd	O	-	-
78	betray	O	-	-
79	'	O	-	-
80	arry	O	-	-
81	e	O	-	-
82	'	O	-	-
83	en	O	-	-
84	in	O	-	-
85	me	O	-	-
86	dreams	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700166
# text = Wha's so funny!
1	Wha	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	funny	O	-	-
5	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700167
# text = I trust you with my life, Hagrid. I trust everyone in this room. Understood?
1	I	O	-	-
2	trust	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	with	O	-	-
5	my	O	-	-
6	life	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Hagrid	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	trust	O	-	-
12	everyone	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	this	O	-	-
15	room	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	Understood	O	-	-
18	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700168
# text = 'Ear, 'ear.
1	'	O	-	-
2	Ear	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	'	O	-	-
5	ear	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700169
# text = Better.
1	Better	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700170
# text = No!  No!  I believed a different wand would work, I swear!
1	No	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	No	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	believed	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	different	O	-	-
9	wand	O	-	-
10	would	O	-	-
11	work	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	swear	O	-	-
15	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700171
# text = Then explain this!
1	Then	O	-	-
2	explain	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700172
# text = But it makes no sense...
1	But	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	makes	O	-	-
4	no	O	-	-
5	sense	O	-	-
6	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700173
# text = Perhaps our friend's loyalties lie elsewhere, Wormtail.
1	Perhaps	O	-	-
2	our	O	-	-
3	friend	O	-	-
4	's	O	-	-
5	loyalties	O	-	-
6	lie	O	-	-
7	elsewhere	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Wormtail	B-PER	-	-
10	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700174
# text = No!  There must be a way!  I'll think of something else!
1	No	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	There	O	-	-
4	must	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	way	O	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	'll	O	-	-
11	think	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	something	O	-	-
14	else	O	-	-
15	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700175
# text = I hope so, Ollivander, for your sake.  I won't be so forgiving next time...
1	I	O	-	-
2	hope	O	-	-
3	so	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Ollivander	B-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	your	O	-	-
9	sake	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	wo	O	-	-
13	n't	O	-	-
14	be	O	-	-
15	so	O	-	-
16	forgiving	O	-	-
17	next	O	-	-
18	time	O	-	-
19	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700176
# text = Going somewhere?
1	Going	O	-	-
2	somewhere	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700177
# text = No one else is going to die.  Not for me.
1	No	O	-	-
2	one	O	-	-
3	else	O	-	-
4	is	O	-	-
5	going	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	die	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Not	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	me	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700178
# text = For you?  You think Madeye died for you?  You think George took that curse for you?  You may be the Chosen One, mate, but this is a whole lot bigger than that.
1	For	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	think	O	-	-
6	Madeye	B-PER	-	-
7	died	O	-	-
8	for	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	You	O	-	-
12	think	O	-	-
13	George	B-PER	-	-
14	took	O	-	-
15	that	O	-	-
16	curse	O	-	-
17	for	O	-	-
18	you	O	-	-
19	?	O	-	-
20	You	O	-	-
21	may	O	-	-
22	be	O	-	-
23	the	O	-	-
24	Chosen	B-PER	-	-
25	One	I-PER	-	-
26	,	O	-	-
27	mate	O	-	-
28	,	O	-	-
29	but	O	-	-
30	this	O	-	-
31	is	O	-	-
32	a	O	-	-
33	whole	O	-	-
34	lot	O	-	-
35	bigger	O	-	-
36	than	O	-	-
37	that	O	-	-
38	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700179
# text = Come with me.  Now.
1	Come	O	-	-
2	with	O	-	-
3	me	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Now	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700180
# text = And leave Hermione?  Are you mad? We wouldn't last two days without her.
1	And	O	-	-
2	leave	O	-	-
3	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
4	?	O	-	-
5	Are	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	mad	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	We	O	-	-
10	would	O	-	-
11	n't	O	-	-
12	last	O	-	-
13	two	O	-	-
14	days	O	-	-
15	without	O	-	-
16	her	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700181
# text = Don't tell her I said that. Besides, you've still got the Trace on you.  And there's the wedding...
1	Do	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	her	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	said	O	-	-
7	that	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Besides	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	you	O	-	-
12	've	O	-	-
13	still	O	-	-
14	got	O	-	-
15	the	O	-	-
16	Trace	O	-	-
17	on	O	-	-
18	you	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	And	O	-	-
21	there	O	-	-
22	's	O	-	-
23	the	O	-	-
24	wedding	O	-	-
25	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700182
# text = Wedding?
1	Wedding	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700183
# text = Bill and Fleur.  Mum's been planning it for months.  Only thing that's kept her sane, I reckon.  She'll kill me if I miss it.  Kill you too.  Rather go face to face with You-Know-Who if I'm honest.
1	Bill	B-PER	-	-
2	and	O	-	-
3	Fleur	B-PER	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Mum	O	-	-
6	's	O	-	-
7	been	O	-	-
8	planning	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	for	O	-	-
11	months	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	Only	O	-	-
14	thing	O	-	-
15	that	O	-	-
16	's	O	-	-
17	kept	O	-	-
18	her	O	-	-
19	sane	O	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	I	O	-	-
22	reckon	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	She	O	-	-
25	'll	O	-	-
26	kill	O	-	-
27	me	O	-	-
28	if	O	-	-
29	I	O	-	-
30	miss	O	-	-
31	it	O	-	-
32	.	O	-	-
33	Kill	O	-	-
34	you	O	-	-
35	too	O	-	-
36	.	O	-	-
37	Rather	O	-	-
38	go	O	-	-
39	face	O	-	-
40	to	O	-	-
41	face	O	-	-
42	with	O	-	-
43	You	B-PER	-	-
44	Know	I-PER	-	-
45	Who	I-PER	-	-
46	if	O	-	-
47	I	O	-	-
48	'm	O	-	-
49	honest	O	-	-
50	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700184
# text = I don't care about a bloody wedding -- no matter whose it is. I have to start searching for the Horcruxes.  It's the only chance we have to beat him.  And the longer we wait the stronger he gets.
1	I	O	-	-
2	do	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	care	O	-	-
5	about	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	bloody	O	-	-
8	wedding	O	-	-
9	no	O	-	-
10	matter	O	-	-
11	whose	O	-	-
12	it	O	-	-
13	is	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	I	O	-	-
16	have	O	-	-
17	to	O	-	-
18	start	O	-	-
19	searching	O	-	-
20	for	O	-	-
21	the	O	-	-
22	Horcruxes	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	It	O	-	-
25	's	O	-	-
26	the	O	-	-
27	only	O	-	-
28	chance	O	-	-
29	we	O	-	-
30	have	O	-	-
31	to	O	-	-
32	beat	O	-	-
33	him	O	-	-
34	.	O	-	-
35	And	O	-	-
36	the	O	-	-
37	longer	O	-	-
38	we	O	-	-
39	wait	O	-	-
40	the	O	-	-
41	stronger	O	-	-
42	he	O	-	-
43	gets	O	-	-
44	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700185
# text = Tonight's not the night, mate. You'd only be doing him a favor.
1	Tonight	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	not	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	night	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	mate	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	You	O	-	-
10	'd	O	-	-
11	only	O	-	-
12	be	O	-	-
13	doing	O	-	-
14	him	O	-	-
15	a	O	-	-
16	favor	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700186
# text = Do you think he knows?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	think	O	-	-
4	he	O	-	-
5	knows	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700187
# text = I mean, they're bits of his soul, the Horcruxes.  Bits of him.  When Dumbledore destroyed the ring and you destroyed Tom Riddle's diary all those years ago -- he must've felt something right?
1	I	O	-	-
2	mean	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	're	O	-	-
6	bits	O	-	-
7	of	O	-	-
8	his	O	-	-
9	soul	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Horcruxes	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	Bits	O	-	-
15	of	O	-	-
16	him	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	When	O	-	-
19	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
20	destroyed	O	-	-
21	the	O	-	-
22	ring	O	-	-
23	and	O	-	-
24	you	O	-	-
25	destroyed	O	-	-
26	Tom	B-PER	-	-
27	Riddle	I-PER	-	-
28	's	O	-	-
29	diary	O	-	-
30	all	O	-	-
31	those	O	-	-
32	years	O	-	-
33	ago	O	-	-
34	he	O	-	-
35	must	O	-	-
36	've	O	-	-
37	felt	O	-	-
38	something	O	-	-
39	right	O	-	-
40	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700188
# text = What I'm saying is, if we do this thing right, if we find the Horcruxes and begin to destroy them one by one...
1	What	O	-	-
2	I	O	-	-
3	'm	O	-	-
4	saying	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	if	O	-	-
8	we	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	this	O	-	-
11	thing	O	-	-
12	right	O	-	-
13	,	O	-	-
14	if	O	-	-
15	we	O	-	-
16	find	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	Horcruxes	O	-	-
19	and	O	-	-
20	begin	O	-	-
21	to	O	-	-
22	destroy	O	-	-
23	them	O	-	-
24	one	O	-	-
25	by	O	-	-
26	one	O	-	-
27	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700189
# text = Won't he know he's being hunted?
1	Wo	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	's	O	-	-
7	being	O	-	-
8	hunted	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700190
# text = All together now!
1	All	O	-	-
2	together	O	-	-
3	now	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700191
# text = One.  Two.  Three!
1	One	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Two	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Three	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700192
# text = Were you going to tell me?
1	Were	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	going	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	tell	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700193
# text = Yes.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700194
# text = And Ron and Hermione.  They'll not be going back to Hogwarts either?
1	And	O	-	-
2	Ron	B-PER	-	-
3	and	O	-	-
4	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	They	O	-	-
7	'll	O	-	-
8	not	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	going	O	-	-
11	back	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	Hogwarts	B-ORG	-	-
14	either	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700195
# text = I see.
1	I	O	-	-
2	see	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700196
# text = Dumbledore didn't want anyone to know what it is we're doing.  If I tell you, I'd be betraying him.
1	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
2	did	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	want	O	-	-
5	anyone	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	know	O	-	-
8	what	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	we	O	-	-
12	're	O	-	-
13	doing	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	If	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	tell	O	-	-
18	you	O	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	I	O	-	-
21	'd	O	-	-
22	be	O	-	-
23	betraying	O	-	-
24	him	O	-	-
25	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700197
# text = Zip me up, will you.
1	Zip	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	up	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	will	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700198
# text = Seems silly, doesn't it?  A wedding.  Given everything that's going on.
1	Seems	O	-	-
2	silly	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	does	O	-	-
5	n't	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-
8	A	O	-	-
9	wedding	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Given	O	-	-
12	everything	O	-	-
13	that	O	-	-
14	's	O	-	-
15	going	O	-	-
16	on	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700199
# text = Maybe that's the best reason to have it.  Because of everything that's going on.
1	Maybe	O	-	-
2	that	O	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	best	O	-	-
6	reason	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	have	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Because	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	everything	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	's	O	-	-
16	going	O	-	-
17	on	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700200
# text = Morning.
1	Morning	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700201
# text = How's it look on your end, boys?
1	How	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	look	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	your	O	-	-
7	end	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	boys	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700202
# text = Brilliant!
1	Brilliant	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700203
# text = Bloody hell, what's the Minister of Magic doing here?
1	Bloody	O	-	-
2	hell	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	what	O	-	-
5	's	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Minister	B-TTL	-	-
8	of	I-TTL	-	-
9	Magic	I-TTL	-	-
10	doing	O	-	-
11	here	O	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700204
# text = Dunno.  But something tells me he didn't come to give away the bride.
1	Dunno	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	But	O	-	-
4	something	O	-	-
5	tells	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	did	O	-	-
9	n't	O	-	-
10	come	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	give	O	-	-
13	away	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	bride	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700205
# text = To what do we owe the pleasure, Minister?
1	To	O	-	-
2	what	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	owe	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	pleasure	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	Minister	B-TTL	-	-
10	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700206
# text = I think we both know the answer to that question, Mr. Potter.
1	I	O	-	-
2	think	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	both	O	-	-
5	know	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	answer	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	question	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
13	Potter	B-PER	-	-
14	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700207
# text = And this would be...?
1	And	O	-	-
2	this	O	-	-
3	would	O	-	-
4	be	O	-	-
5	...	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700208
# text = Don't be coy, Mr. Potter.  Mr. Weasley.  Would you say you were close to your former Headmaster?
1	Do	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	coy	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
7	Potter	B-PER	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
10	Weasley	B-PER	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	Would	O	-	-
13	you	O	-	-
14	say	O	-	-
15	you	O	-	-
16	were	O	-	-
17	close	O	-	-
18	to	O	-	-
19	your	O	-	-
20	former	O	-	-
21	Headmaster	B-TTL	-	-
22	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700209
# text = Dumbledore?  And me?  I dunno. I reckon I was just another Weasley to him.  He was always polite --
1	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
2	?	O	-	-
3	And	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	dunno	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	reckon	O	-	-
11	I	O	-	-
12	was	O	-	-
13	just	O	-	-
14	another	O	-	-
15	Weasley	B-PER	-	-
16	to	O	-	-
17	him	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-
19	He	O	-	-
20	was	O	-	-
21	always	O	-	-
22	polite	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700210
# text = And you, Miss Granger?  How would you characterize your relationship?
1	And	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	Miss	B-TTL	-	-
5	Granger	B-PER	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	How	O	-	-
8	would	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	characterize	O	-	-
11	your	O	-	-
12	relationship	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700211
# text = We were friendly, not close like Harry, but --
1	We	O	-	-
2	were	O	-	-
3	friendly	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	not	O	-	-
6	close	O	-	-
7	like	O	-	-
8	Harry	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	but	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700212
# text = What's this all about?
1	What	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	all	O	-	-
5	about	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700213
# text = This.  Despite the fact that neither of your friends appear to have been particularly close to their recently deceased Headmaster, he saw fit to remember them in his will.  Now why do you suppose that would be?
1	This	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Despite	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	fact	O	-	-
6	that	O	-	-
7	neither	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	your	O	-	-
10	friends	O	-	-
11	appear	O	-	-
12	to	O	-	-
13	have	O	-	-
14	been	O	-	-
15	particularly	O	-	-
16	close	O	-	-
17	to	O	-	-
18	their	O	-	-
19	recently	O	-	-
20	deceased	O	-	-
21	Headmaster	B-TTL	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	he	O	-	-
24	saw	O	-	-
25	fit	O	-	-
26	to	O	-	-
27	remember	O	-	-
28	them	O	-	-
29	in	O	-	-
30	his	O	-	-
31	will	O	-	-
32	.	O	-	-
33	Now	O	-	-
34	why	O	-	-
35	do	O	-	-
36	you	O	-	-
37	suppose	O	-	-
38	that	O	-	-
39	would	O	-	-
40	be	O	-	-
41	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700214
# text = No idea.
1	No	O	-	-
2	idea	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700215
# text = Come now, you don't expect me to believe...
1	Come	O	-	-
2	now	O	-	-
3	,	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	n't	O	-	-
7	expect	O	-	-
8	me	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	believe	O	-	-
11	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700216
# text = 'Herein is set forth the Last Will and Testament of Albus Percival Wulfric Brian Dumbledore.  First, to Ronald Bilius Weasley, I leave my Deluminator, a device of my own making, in the hope that -- when things seem most dark -- it will show him the light.'
1	'	O	-	-
2	Herein	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	set	O	-	-
5	forth	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	Last	O	-	-
8	Will	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	Testament	O	-	-
11	of	O	-	-
12	Albus	B-PER	-	-
13	Percival	I-PER	-	-
14	Wulfric	I-PER	-	-
15	Brian	I-PER	-	-
16	Dumbledore	I-PER	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	First	O	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	to	O	-	-
21	Ronald	B-PER	-	-
22	Bilius	I-PER	-	-
23	Weasley	I-PER	-	-
24	,	O	-	-
25	I	O	-	-
26	leave	O	-	-
27	my	O	-	-
28	Deluminator	O	-	-
29	,	O	-	-
30	a	O	-	-
31	device	O	-	-
32	of	O	-	-
33	my	O	-	-
34	own	O	-	-
35	making	O	-	-
36	,	O	-	-
37	in	O	-	-
38	the	O	-	-
39	hope	O	-	-
40	that	O	-	-
41	when	O	-	-
42	things	O	-	-
43	seem	O	-	-
44	most	O	-	-
45	dark	O	-	-
46	it	O	-	-
47	will	O	-	-
48	show	O	-	-
49	him	O	-	-
50	the	O	-	-
51	light	O	-	-
52	.	O	-	-
53	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700217
# text = Dumbledore left this?  For me? Brilliant.  Er -- what is it?
1	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
2	left	O	-	-
3	this	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-
5	For	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-
8	Brilliant	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Er	O	-	-
11	what	O	-	-
12	is	O	-	-
13	it	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700218
# text = Wicked.
1	Wicked	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700219
# text = 'To Miss Hermione Jean Granger, I leave my copy of The Tales of Beedle the Bard, in the hope that she will find it entertaining and instructive.'
1	'	O	-	-
2	To	O	-	-
3	Miss	B-TTL	-	-
4	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
5	Jean	I-PER	-	-
6	Granger	I-PER	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	I	O	-	-
9	leave	O	-	-
10	my	O	-	-
11	copy	O	-	-
12	of	O	-	-
13	The	O	-	-
14	Tales	O	-	-
15	of	O	-	-
16	Beedle	B-PER	-	-
17	the	I-PER	-	-
18	Bard	I-PER	-	-
19	,	O	-	-
20	in	O	-	-
21	the	O	-	-
22	hope	O	-	-
23	that	O	-	-
24	she	O	-	-
25	will	O	-	-
26	find	O	-	-
27	it	O	-	-
28	entertaining	O	-	-
29	and	O	-	-
30	instructive	O	-	-
31	.	O	-	-
32	'	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700220
# text = Mum used to read me those!  The Wizard and the Hopping Pot, Babbitty Rabbity and her Cackling Stump...
1	Mum	O	-	-
2	used	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	read	O	-	-
5	me	O	-	-
6	those	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-
8	The	O	-	-
9	Wizard	O	-	-
10	and	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Hopping	O	-	-
13	Pot	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Babbitty	O	-	-
16	Rabbity	O	-	-
17	and	O	-	-
18	her	O	-	-
19	Cackling	O	-	-
20	Stump	O	-	-
21	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700221
# text = Oh, c'mon!  Beedle's stories are famous!  Babbity Rabbitty? No...?
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	c	O	-	-
4	'm	O	-	-
5	on	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	Beedle	B-PER	-	-
8	's	O	-	-
9	stories	O	-	-
10	are	O	-	-
11	famous	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-
13	Babbity	O	-	-
14	Rabbitty	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-
16	No	O	-	-
17	...	O	-	-
18	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700222
# text = 'To Harry James Potter, I leave the Snitch he caught in his first Quidditch match at Hogwarts, as a reminder of the rewards of perseverance and skill.
1	'	O	-	-
2	To	O	-	-
3	Harry	B-PER	-	-
4	James	I-PER	-	-
5	Potter	I-PER	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	leave	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Snitch	O	-	-
11	he	O	-	-
12	caught	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	his	O	-	-
15	first	O	-	-
16	Quidditch	O	-	-
17	match	O	-	-
18	at	O	-	-
19	Hogwarts	B-ORG	-	-
20	,	O	-	-
21	as	O	-	-
22	a	O	-	-
23	reminder	O	-	-
24	of	O	-	-
25	the	O	-	-
26	rewards	O	-	-
27	of	O	-	-
28	perseverance	O	-	-
29	and	O	-	-
30	skill	O	-	-
31	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700223
# text = That's it then?
1	That	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	then	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700224
# text = Not quite.  Dumbledore left you a second bequest:  The Sword of Godric Gryffindor.  Unfortunately, the Sword of Gryffindor was not Dumbledore's to give away.  As an important historical artifact, it belongs...
1	Not	O	-	-
2	quite	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
5	left	O	-	-
6	you	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	second	O	-	-
9	bequest	O	-	-
10	:	O	-	-
11	The	O	-	-
12	Sword	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	Godric	O	-	-
15	Gryffindor	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	Unfortunately	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	the	O	-	-
20	Sword	O	-	-
21	of	O	-	-
22	Gryffindor	O	-	-
23	was	O	-	-
24	not	O	-	-
25	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
26	's	O	-	-
27	to	O	-	-
28	give	O	-	-
29	away	O	-	-
30	.	O	-	-
31	As	O	-	-
32	an	O	-	-
33	important	O	-	-
34	historical	O	-	-
35	artifact	O	-	-
36	,	O	-	-
37	it	O	-	-
38	belongs	O	-	-
39	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700225
# text = To Harry!  It belongs to Harry! It chose him!  It came to him in the Chamber of Secrets when he most needed it!
1	To	O	-	-
2	Harry	B-PER	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	It	O	-	-
5	belongs	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	Harry	B-PER	-	-
8	!	O	-	-
9	It	O	-	-
10	chose	O	-	-
11	him	O	-	-
12	!	O	-	-
13	It	O	-	-
14	came	O	-	-
15	to	O	-	-
16	him	O	-	-
17	in	O	-	-
18	the	O	-	-
19	Chamber	B-LOC	-	-
20	of	I-LOC	-	-
21	Secrets	I-LOC	-	-
22	when	O	-	-
23	he	O	-	-
24	most	O	-	-
25	needed	O	-	-
26	it	O	-	-
27	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700226
# text = The sword may present itself to any worthy Gryffindor, Miss Granger.  That does not make it that wizard's property.  And in any event the current whereabouts of the sword are unknown.
1	The	O	-	-
2	sword	O	-	-
3	may	O	-	-
4	present	O	-	-
5	itself	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	any	O	-	-
8	worthy	O	-	-
9	Gryffindor	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Miss	B-TTL	-	-
12	Granger	B-PER	-	-
13	.	O	-	-
14	That	O	-	-
15	does	O	-	-
16	not	O	-	-
17	make	O	-	-
18	it	O	-	-
19	that	O	-	-
20	wizard	O	-	-
21	's	O	-	-
22	property	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	And	O	-	-
25	in	O	-	-
26	any	O	-	-
27	event	O	-	-
28	the	O	-	-
29	current	O	-	-
30	whereabouts	O	-	-
31	of	O	-	-
32	the	O	-	-
33	sword	O	-	-
34	are	O	-	-
35	unknown	O	-	-
36	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700227
# text = Excuse me?
1	Excuse	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700228
# text = The sword is missing. I won't pretend to be your friend, Mr. Potter.  But I assure you I'm not your enemy.
1	The	O	-	-
2	sword	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	missing	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	wo	O	-	-
8	n't	O	-	-
9	pretend	O	-	-
10	to	O	-	-
11	be	O	-	-
12	your	O	-	-
13	friend	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
16	Potter	B-PER	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	But	O	-	-
19	I	O	-	-
20	assure	O	-	-
21	you	O	-	-
22	I	O	-	-
23	'm	O	-	-
24	not	O	-	-
25	your	O	-	-
26	enemy	O	-	-
27	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700229
# text = You'll forgive me, Minister.  But it's a little hard to tell the difference these days.
1	You	O	-	-
2	'll	O	-	-
3	forgive	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Minister	B-TTL	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	But	O	-	-
9	it	O	-	-
10	's	O	-	-
11	a	O	-	-
12	little	O	-	-
13	hard	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	tell	O	-	-
16	the	O	-	-
17	difference	O	-	-
18	these	O	-	-
19	days	O	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700230
# text = Dumbledore said something very similar the last time we spoke.
1	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
2	said	O	-	-
3	something	O	-	-
4	very	O	-	-
5	similar	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	last	O	-	-
8	time	O	-	-
9	we	O	-	-
10	spoke	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700231
# text = Where is your guard, sir?
1	Where	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	your	O	-	-
4	guard	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	sir	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700232
# text = I came alone.  I don't really need them anymore...
1	I	O	-	-
2	came	O	-	-
3	alone	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	do	O	-	-
7	n't	O	-	-
8	really	O	-	-
9	need	O	-	-
10	them	O	-	-
11	anymore	O	-	-
12	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700233
# text = We want you to be the godfather.
1	We	O	-	-
2	want	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	be	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	godfather	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700234
# text = You mean -- But that's brilliant -- I... don't know what to say.
1	You	O	-	-
2	mean	O	-	-
3	But	O	-	-
4	that	O	-	-
5	's	O	-	-
6	brilliant	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	...	O	-	-
9	do	O	-	-
10	n't	O	-	-
11	know	O	-	-
12	what	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	say	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700235
# text = Say yes.
1	Say	O	-	-
2	yes	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700236
# text = Hello, Harry!
1	Hello	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Harry	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700237
# text = Oh, I've interrupted a deep thought, haven't I?  I can see it growing smaller in your eyes.
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	've	O	-	-
5	interrupted	O	-	-
6	a	O	-	-
7	deep	O	-	-
8	thought	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	have	O	-	-
11	n't	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-
14	I	O	-	-
15	can	O	-	-
16	see	O	-	-
17	it	O	-	-
18	growing	O	-	-
19	smaller	O	-	-
20	in	O	-	-
21	your	O	-	-
22	eyes	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700238
# text = No, 'course not.  How are you, Luna?
1	No	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	'	O	-	-
4	course	O	-	-
5	not	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	How	O	-	-
8	are	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	Luna	B-PER	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700239
# text = Very well.  I was bitten by a garden gnome only moments ago.
1	Very	O	-	-
2	well	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	bitten	O	-	-
7	by	O	-	-
8	a	O	-	-
9	garden	O	-	-
10	gnome	O	-	-
11	only	O	-	-
12	moments	O	-	-
13	ago	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700240
# text = Gnome saliva is enormously beneficial!  Xenophilius Lovegood. We live just over the hill!
1	Gnome	O	-	-
2	saliva	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	enormously	O	-	-
5	beneficial	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-
7	Xenophilius	B-PER	-	-
8	Lovegood	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	We	O	-	-
11	live	O	-	-
12	just	O	-	-
13	over	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	hill	O	-	-
16	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700241
# text = Nice to meet you, sir.
1	Nice	O	-	-
2	to	O	-	-
3	meet	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	sir	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700242
# text = I trust you know, Mr. Potter, that we at The Quibbler, unlike those toadies at the Daily Prophet, fully supported Dumbledore during his lifetime and in his death support you just as fully.
1	I	O	-	-
2	trust	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	know	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
7	Potter	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	that	O	-	-
10	we	O	-	-
11	at	O	-	-
12	The	O	-	-
13	Quibbler	B-ORG	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	unlike	O	-	-
16	those	O	-	-
17	toadies	O	-	-
18	at	O	-	-
19	the	O	-	-
20	Daily	B-ORG	-	-
21	Prophet	I-ORG	-	-
22	,	O	-	-
23	fully	O	-	-
24	supported	O	-	-
25	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
26	during	O	-	-
27	his	O	-	-
28	lifetime	O	-	-
29	and	O	-	-
30	in	O	-	-
31	his	O	-	-
32	death	O	-	-
33	support	O	-	-
34	you	O	-	-
35	just	O	-	-
36	as	O	-	-
37	fully	O	-	-
38	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700243
# text = Come, Daddy.  Harry doesn't want to talk to us right now.  He's just too nice to say so.
1	Come	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	Daddy	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Harry	B-PER	-	-
6	does	O	-	-
7	n't	O	-	-
8	want	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	talk	O	-	-
11	to	O	-	-
12	us	O	-	-
13	right	O	-	-
14	now	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	He	O	-	-
17	's	O	-	-
18	just	O	-	-
19	too	O	-	-
20	nice	O	-	-
21	to	O	-	-
22	say	O	-	-
23	so	O	-	-
24	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700244
# text = Sir?  May I sit down?
1	Sir	B-TTL	-	-
2	?	O	-	-
3	May	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	sit	O	-	-
6	down	O	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700245
# text = Mr. Potter!  By all means!
1	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
2	Potter	B-PER	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	By	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	means	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700246
# text = I found what you wrote in the Daily Prophet very moving, sir.  I take it you knew Professor Dumbledore well?
1	I	O	-	-
2	found	O	-	-
3	what	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	wrote	O	-	-
6	in	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	Daily	B-ORG	-	-
9	Prophet	I-ORG	-	-
10	very	O	-	-
11	moving	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	sir	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-
15	I	O	-	-
16	take	O	-	-
17	it	O	-	-
18	you	O	-	-
19	knew	O	-	-
20	Professor	B-TTL	-	-
21	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
22	well	O	-	-
23	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700247
# text = I certainly knew him the longest, if you don't count his brother Aberforth -- and somehow, people never do seem to count Aberforth.
1	I	O	-	-
2	certainly	O	-	-
3	knew	O	-	-
4	him	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	longest	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	if	O	-	-
9	you	O	-	-
10	do	O	-	-
11	n't	O	-	-
12	count	O	-	-
13	his	O	-	-
14	brother	O	-	-
15	Aberforth	B-PER	-	-
16	and	O	-	-
17	somehow	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	people	O	-	-
20	never	O	-	-
21	do	O	-	-
22	seem	O	-	-
23	to	O	-	-
24	count	O	-	-
25	Aberforth	B-PER	-	-
26	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700248
# text = I never even knew he had a brother, sir.
1	I	O	-	-
2	never	O	-	-
3	even	O	-	-
4	knew	O	-	-
5	he	O	-	-
6	had	O	-	-
7	a	O	-	-
8	brother	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	sir	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700249
# text = Yes, well, Dumbledore was always very private.  Even as a boy.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	well	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
6	was	O	-	-
7	always	O	-	-
8	very	O	-	-
9	private	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Even	O	-	-
12	as	O	-	-
13	a	O	-	-
14	boy	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700250
# text = Sir, I was wondering if you'd had much contact with him before he died.
1	Sir	B-TTL	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	was	O	-	-
5	wondering	O	-	-
6	if	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	'd	O	-	-
9	had	O	-	-
10	much	O	-	-
11	contact	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	him	O	-	-
14	before	O	-	-
15	he	O	-	-
16	died	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700251
# text = The occasional owl.  Though it was strange...
1	The	O	-	-
2	occasional	O	-	-
3	owl	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Though	O	-	-
6	it	O	-	-
7	was	O	-	-
8	strange	O	-	-
9	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700252
# text = Strange, sir?
1	Strange	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	sir	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700253
# text = It was the owls themselves.  They often arrived in distress.  It was clear they'd traveled great distances in some cases.
1	It	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	owls	O	-	-
5	themselves	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	They	O	-	-
8	often	O	-	-
9	arrived	O	-	-
10	in	O	-	-
11	distress	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	It	O	-	-
14	was	O	-	-
15	clear	O	-	-
16	they	O	-	-
17	'd	O	-	-
18	traveled	O	-	-
19	great	O	-	-
20	distances	O	-	-
21	in	O	-	-
22	some	O	-	-
23	cases	O	-	-
24	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700254
# text = Could you tell me from where they'd come, sir?
1	Could	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	tell	O	-	-
4	me	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	where	O	-	-
7	they	O	-	-
8	'd	O	-	-
9	come	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	sir	B-TTL	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700255
# text = I'm afraid not.  Albus' messages mostly referenced our days together as schoolboys.  They were surprisingly intimate.  When he did speak of his current activities his words would turn elliptical.  Still, I sensed he was under great stress.  Why do you ask?
1	I	O	-	-
2	'm	O	-	-
3	afraid	O	-	-
4	not	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Albus	B-PER	-	-
7	'	O	-	-
8	messages	O	-	-
9	mostly	O	-	-
10	referenced	O	-	-
11	our	O	-	-
12	days	O	-	-
13	together	O	-	-
14	as	O	-	-
15	schoolboys	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	They	O	-	-
18	were	O	-	-
19	surprisingly	O	-	-
20	intimate	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-
22	When	O	-	-
23	he	O	-	-
24	did	O	-	-
25	speak	O	-	-
26	of	O	-	-
27	his	O	-	-
28	current	O	-	-
29	activities	O	-	-
30	his	O	-	-
31	words	O	-	-
32	would	O	-	-
33	turn	O	-	-
34	elliptical	O	-	-
35	.	O	-	-
36	Still	O	-	-
37	,	O	-	-
38	I	O	-	-
39	sensed	O	-	-
40	he	O	-	-
41	was	O	-	-
42	under	O	-	-
43	great	O	-	-
44	stress	O	-	-
45	.	O	-	-
46	Why	O	-	-
47	do	O	-	-
48	you	O	-	-
49	ask	O	-	-
50	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700256
# text = Just curious.  I was... close to Professor Dumbledore.
1	Just	O	-	-
2	curious	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	was	O	-	-
6	...	O	-	-
7	close	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	Professor	B-TTL	-	-
10	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
11	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700257
# text = Well, he treasured you, Mr. Potter, I can attest to that.  I can also tell you that when a person passes, it's only natural to rue the things left unsaid, to regret the question never asked. I knew Albus nigh on 100 years, but in many ways he will always remain a riddle even to me.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	treasured	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
8	Potter	B-PER	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	can	O	-	-
12	attest	O	-	-
13	to	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	I	O	-	-
17	can	O	-	-
18	also	O	-	-
19	tell	O	-	-
20	you	O	-	-
21	that	O	-	-
22	when	O	-	-
23	a	O	-	-
24	person	O	-	-
25	passes	O	-	-
26	,	O	-	-
27	it	O	-	-
28	's	O	-	-
29	only	O	-	-
30	natural	O	-	-
31	to	O	-	-
32	rue	O	-	-
33	the	O	-	-
34	things	O	-	-
35	left	O	-	-
36	unsaid	O	-	-
37	,	O	-	-
38	to	O	-	-
39	regret	O	-	-
40	the	O	-	-
41	question	O	-	-
42	never	O	-	-
43	asked	O	-	-
44	.	O	-	-
45	I	O	-	-
46	knew	O	-	-
47	Albus	B-PER	-	-
48	nigh	O	-	-
49	on	O	-	-
50	100	O	-	-
51	years	O	-	-
52	,	O	-	-
53	but	O	-	-
54	in	O	-	-
55	many	O	-	-
56	ways	O	-	-
57	he	O	-	-
58	will	O	-	-
59	always	O	-	-
60	remain	O	-	-
61	a	O	-	-
62	riddle	O	-	-
63	even	O	-	-
64	to	O	-	-
65	me	O	-	-
66	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700258
# text = Don't despair, Elphias.  I'm told he's been thoroughly unriddled by Rita Skeeter.  In 800 pages no less.
1	Do	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	despair	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Elphias	B-PER	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	I	O	-	-
8	'm	O	-	-
9	told	O	-	-
10	he	O	-	-
11	's	O	-	-
12	been	O	-	-
13	thoroughly	O	-	-
14	unriddled	O	-	-
15	by	O	-	-
16	Rita	B-PER	-	-
17	Skeeter	I-PER	-	-
18	.	O	-	-
19	In	O	-	-
20	800	O	-	-
21	pages	O	-	-
22	no	O	-	-
23	less	O	-	-
24	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700259
# text = That woman is a vulture, Muriel, and you well know it.
1	That	O	-	-
2	woman	O	-	-
3	is	O	-	-
4	a	O	-	-
5	vulture	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	Muriel	B-PER	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	and	O	-	-
10	you	O	-	-
11	well	O	-	-
12	know	O	-	-
13	it	O	-	-
14	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700260
# text = Someone has to pick the bones to get at the truth.  I read your obituary, Elphias.  Lovely.  But you did skate over some of the sticky patches in Dumbledore's life.
1	Someone	O	-	-
2	has	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	pick	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	bones	O	-	-
7	to	O	-	-
8	get	O	-	-
9	at	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	truth	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	read	O	-	-
15	your	O	-	-
16	obituary	O	-	-
17	,	O	-	-
18	Elphias	B-PER	-	-
19	.	O	-	-
20	Lovely	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-
22	But	O	-	-
23	you	O	-	-
24	did	O	-	-
25	skate	O	-	-
26	over	O	-	-
27	some	O	-	-
28	of	O	-	-
29	the	O	-	-
30	sticky	O	-	-
31	patches	O	-	-
32	in	O	-	-
33	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
34	's	O	-	-
35	life	O	-	-
36	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700261
# text = I'm sorry you think so, Muriel.  I assure you I was writing from the heart.
1	I	O	-	-
2	'm	O	-	-
3	sorry	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	think	O	-	-
6	so	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Muriel	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	I	O	-	-
11	assure	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	was	O	-	-
15	writing	O	-	-
16	from	O	-	-
17	the	O	-	-
18	heart	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700262
# text = Yes, well, Rita Skeeter hasn't made that mistake, I'm sure.  Word has it someone talked to her, someone who knew the Dumbledore family well.  You and I both know who that is, Elphias.
1	Yes	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	well	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Rita	B-PER	-	-
6	Skeeter	I-PER	-	-
7	has	O	-	-
8	n't	O	-	-
9	made	O	-	-
10	that	O	-	-
11	mistake	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	I	O	-	-
14	'm	O	-	-
15	sure	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	Word	O	-	-
18	has	O	-	-
19	it	O	-	-
20	someone	O	-	-
21	talked	O	-	-
22	to	O	-	-
23	her	O	-	-
24	,	O	-	-
25	someone	O	-	-
26	who	O	-	-
27	knew	O	-	-
28	the	O	-	-
29	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
30	family	O	-	-
31	well	O	-	-
32	.	O	-	-
33	You	O	-	-
34	and	O	-	-
35	I	O	-	-
36	both	O	-	-
37	know	O	-	-
38	who	O	-	-
39	that	O	-	-
40	is	O	-	-
41	,	O	-	-
42	Elphias	B-PER	-	-
43	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700263
# text = A monstrous betrayal.  I can only conclude the rumors are true and that she has become untethered.
1	A	O	-	-
2	monstrous	O	-	-
3	betrayal	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	can	O	-	-
7	only	O	-	-
8	conclude	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	rumors	O	-	-
11	are	O	-	-
12	true	O	-	-
13	and	O	-	-
14	that	O	-	-
15	she	O	-	-
16	has	O	-	-
17	become	O	-	-
18	untethered	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700264
# text = Who are you talking about?
1	Who	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	talking	O	-	-
5	about	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700265
# text = Well, I don't suppose it'll be a secret once the book comes out. Bathilda Bagshot.
1	Well	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	do	O	-	-
5	n't	O	-	-
6	suppose	O	-	-
7	it	O	-	-
8	'll	O	-	-
9	be	O	-	-
10	a	O	-	-
11	secret	O	-	-
12	once	O	-	-
13	the	O	-	-
14	book	O	-	-
15	comes	O	-	-
16	out	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
19	Bagshot	I-PER	-	-
20	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700266
# text = Who?
1	Who	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700267
# text = Who? Bathilda Bagshot!  My god, boy, she's only the most celebrated magical historian of the last century.  Don't they read History of Magic at Hogwarts anymore?
1	Who	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-
3	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
4	Bagshot	I-PER	-	-
5	!	O	-	-
6	My	O	-	-
7	god	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	boy	O	-	-
10	,	O	-	-
11	she	O	-	-
12	's	O	-	-
13	only	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	most	O	-	-
16	celebrated	O	-	-
17	magical	O	-	-
18	historian	O	-	-
19	of	O	-	-
20	the	O	-	-
21	last	O	-	-
22	century	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	Do	O	-	-
25	n't	O	-	-
26	they	O	-	-
27	read	O	-	-
28	History	O	-	-
29	of	O	-	-
30	Magic	O	-	-
31	at	O	-	-
32	Hogwarts	B-ORG	-	-
33	anymore	O	-	-
34	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700268
# text = Oh, right.  Slipped my mind...
1	Oh	O	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	right	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Slipped	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	mind	O	-	-
8	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700269
# text = She knew the Dumbledores as well as anyone.  She'd have letters, perhaps an interesting photograph or two.  I'm sure Rita Skeeter would have thought it well worth a trip to Godric's Hollow to take a peek into that old bird's rattled cage.
1	She	O	-	-
2	knew	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	Dumbledores	B-PER	-	-
5	as	O	-	-
6	well	O	-	-
7	as	O	-	-
8	anyone	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	She	O	-	-
11	'd	O	-	-
12	have	O	-	-
13	letters	O	-	-
14	,	O	-	-
15	perhaps	O	-	-
16	an	O	-	-
17	interesting	O	-	-
18	photograph	O	-	-
19	or	O	-	-
20	two	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-
22	I	O	-	-
23	'm	O	-	-
24	sure	O	-	-
25	Rita	B-PER	-	-
26	Skeeter	I-PER	-	-
27	would	O	-	-
28	have	O	-	-
29	thought	O	-	-
30	it	O	-	-
31	well	O	-	-
32	worth	O	-	-
33	a	O	-	-
34	trip	O	-	-
35	to	O	-	-
36	Godric	B-LOC	-	-
37	's	I-LOC	-	-
38	Hollow	I-LOC	-	-
39	to	O	-	-
40	take	O	-	-
41	a	O	-	-
42	peek	O	-	-
43	into	O	-	-
44	that	O	-	-
45	old	O	-	-
46	bird	O	-	-
47	's	O	-	-
48	rattled	O	-	-
49	cage	O	-	-
50	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700270
# text = Godric's Hollow?  Bathilda Bagshot lives in Godric's Hollow?
1	Godric	B-LOC	-	-
2	's	I-LOC	-	-
3	Hollow	I-LOC	-	-
4	?	O	-	-
5	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
6	Bagshot	I-PER	-	-
7	lives	O	-	-
8	in	O	-	-
9	Godric	B-LOC	-	-
10	's	I-LOC	-	-
11	Hollow	I-LOC	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700271
# text = For years now.  That's where she first met Dumbledore.
1	For	O	-	-
2	years	O	-	-
3	now	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	That	O	-	-
6	's	O	-	-
7	where	O	-	-
8	she	O	-	-
9	first	O	-	-
10	met	O	-	-
11	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700272
# text = Excuse me?  You don't mean to say Dumbledore lived there too?
1	Excuse	O	-	-
2	me	O	-	-
3	?	O	-	-
4	You	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	n't	O	-	-
7	mean	O	-	-
8	to	O	-	-
9	say	O	-	-
10	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
11	lived	O	-	-
12	there	O	-	-
13	too	O	-	-
14	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700273
# text = Of course.  The family moved there after his father killed those three Muggles.  It was quite the scandal. Honestly, my boy, are you sure you knew him at all?
1	Of	O	-	-
2	course	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	The	O	-	-
5	family	O	-	-
6	moved	O	-	-
7	there	O	-	-
8	after	O	-	-
9	his	O	-	-
10	father	O	-	-
11	killed	O	-	-
12	those	O	-	-
13	three	O	-	-
14	Muggles	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-
16	It	O	-	-
17	was	O	-	-
18	quite	O	-	-
19	the	O	-	-
20	scandal	O	-	-
21	.	O	-	-
22	Honestly	O	-	-
23	,	O	-	-
24	my	O	-	-
25	boy	O	-	-
26	,	O	-	-
27	are	O	-	-
28	you	O	-	-
29	sure	O	-	-
30	you	O	-	-
31	knew	O	-	-
32	him	O	-	-
33	at	O	-	-
34	all	O	-	-
35	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700274
# text = The Ministry has fallen.  The Minister of Magic is dead.  They are coming...
1	The	O	-	-
2	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
3	has	O	-	-
4	fallen	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	The	O	-	-
7	Minister	B-TTL	-	-
8	of	I-TTL	-	-
9	Magic	I-TTL	-	-
10	is	O	-	-
11	dead	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-
13	They	O	-	-
14	are	O	-	-
15	coming	O	-	-
16	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700275
# text = Nice meeting you, Mr. Potter!
1	Nice	O	-	-
2	meeting	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	Mr.	B-TTL	-	-
6	Potter	B-PER	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700276
# text = Ron!  Ron!
1	Ron	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Ron	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700277
# text = Harry!  Go!  Go!
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Go	O	-	-
4	!	O	-	-
5	Go	O	-	-
6	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700278
# text = Where are we?
1	Where	O	-	-
2	are	O	-	-
3	we	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700279
# text = Shaftesbury Avenue.  I used to come here to the theater with my mum and dad.  Just popped into my head.  I don't know why...
1	Shaftesbury	B-LOC	-	-
2	Avenue	I-LOC	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	I	O	-	-
5	used	O	-	-
6	to	O	-	-
7	come	O	-	-
8	here	O	-	-
9	to	O	-	-
10	the	O	-	-
11	theater	O	-	-
12	with	O	-	-
13	my	O	-	-
14	mum	O	-	-
15	and	O	-	-
16	dad	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-
18	Just	O	-	-
19	popped	O	-	-
20	into	O	-	-
21	my	O	-	-
22	head	O	-	-
23	.	O	-	-
24	I	O	-	-
25	do	O	-	-
26	n't	O	-	-
27	know	O	-	-
28	why	O	-	-
29	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700280
# text = This way!
1	This	O	-	-
2	way	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700281
# text = We need to change.
1	We	O	-	-
2	need	O	-	-
3	to	O	-	-
4	change	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700282
# text = How the ruddy --
1	How	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	ruddy	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700283
# text = Undetectable Extension Charm.
1	Undetectable	O	-	-
2	Extension	O	-	-
3	Charm	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700284
# text = You're amazing, you are.
1	You	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	amazing	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	are	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700285
# text = Always the tone of surprise.
1	Always	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	tone	O	-	-
4	of	O	-	-
5	surprise	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700286
# text = That'll be the books.
1	That	O	-	-
2	'll	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	books	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700287
# text = Do you reckon everyone's alright at the wedding?  Maybe we should --
1	Do	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	reckon	O	-	-
4	everyone	O	-	-
5	's	O	-	-
6	alright	O	-	-
7	at	O	-	-
8	the	O	-	-
9	wedding	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Maybe	O	-	-
12	we	O	-	-
13	should	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700288
# text = They were after you, mate.  We'd just put everyone in danger going back.
1	They	O	-	-
2	were	O	-	-
3	after	O	-	-
4	you	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	mate	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	We	O	-	-
9	'd	O	-	-
10	just	O	-	-
11	put	O	-	-
12	everyone	O	-	-
13	in	O	-	-
14	danger	O	-	-
15	going	O	-	-
16	back	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700289
# text = Ron's right.  Cappuccino, please.
1	Ron	B-PER	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	right	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	Cappuccino	O	-	-
6	,	O	-	-
7	please	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700290
# text = What she said.
1	What	O	-	-
2	she	O	-	-
3	said	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700291
# text = Same.
1	Same	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700292
# text = Wicked scar.
1	Wicked	O	-	-
2	scar	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700293
# text = So where do we go from here?  The Leaky Cauldron?
1	So	O	-	-
2	where	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	go	O	-	-
6	from	O	-	-
7	here	O	-	-
8	?	O	-	-
9	The	O	-	-
10	Leaky	B-LOC	-	-
11	Cauldron	I-LOC	-	-
12	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700294
# text = Too dangerous.  If Voldemort's taken over the Ministry, none of the old places are safe.
1	Too	O	-	-
2	dangerous	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	If	O	-	-
5	Voldemort	B-PER	-	-
6	's	O	-	-
7	taken	O	-	-
8	over	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	Ministry	B-ORG	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	none	O	-	-
13	of	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	old	O	-	-
16	places	O	-	-
17	are	O	-	-
18	safe	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700295
# text = My rucksack.  With all my things. I left it back at the Burrow --
1	My	O	-	-
2	rucksack	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	With	O	-	-
5	all	O	-	-
6	my	O	-	-
7	things	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	I	O	-	-
10	left	O	-	-
11	it	O	-	-
12	back	O	-	-
13	at	O	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	Burrow	B-LOC	-	-

# sent_id = 700296
# text = You're joking.
1	You	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	joking	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700297
# text = I've had the essentials packed for days.  Just in case.
1	I	O	-	-
2	've	O	-	-
3	had	O	-	-
4	the	O	-	-
5	essentials	O	-	-
6	packed	O	-	-
7	for	O	-	-
8	days	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Just	O	-	-
11	in	O	-	-
12	case	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700298
# text = By the way -- these jeans?  Not my favorite.  Bit tight.
1	By	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	way	O	-	-
4	these	O	-	-
5	jeans	O	-	-
6	?	O	-	-
7	Not	O	-	-
8	my	O	-	-
9	favorite	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	Bit	O	-	-
12	tight	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700299
# text = Down!
1	Down	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700300
# text = Stupefy!
1	Stupefy	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700301
# text = Petrificus Totalus! Go.
1	Petrificus	O	-	-
2	Totalus	O	-	-
3	!	O	-	-
4	Go	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700302
# text = She doesn't argue.
1	She	O	-	-
2	does	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	argue	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700303
# text = Lock the door, get the lights.
1	Lock	O	-	-
2	the	O	-	-
3	door	O	-	-
4	,	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	lights	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700304
# text = This one's name is Rowle.  He was on the Astronomy Tower the night Snape killed Dumbledore.
1	This	O	-	-
2	one	O	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	name	O	-	-
5	is	O	-	-
6	Rowle	B-PER	-	-
7	.	O	-	-
8	He	O	-	-
9	was	O	-	-
10	on	O	-	-
11	the	O	-	-
12	Astronomy	B-LOC	-	-
13	Tower	I-LOC	-	-
14	the	O	-	-
15	night	O	-	-
16	Snape	B-PER	-	-
17	killed	O	-	-
18	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700305
# text = This is Dolohov.  I recognize him from the wanted posters.
1	This	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	Dolohov	B-PER	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	I	O	-	-
6	recognize	O	-	-
7	him	O	-	-
8	from	O	-	-
9	the	O	-	-
10	wanted	O	-	-
11	posters	O	-	-
12	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700306
# text = So what do we do with you, huh? Kill us if it was turned round, wouldn't you?
1	So	O	-	-
2	what	O	-	-
3	do	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	do	O	-	-
6	with	O	-	-
7	you	O	-	-
8	,	O	-	-
9	huh	O	-	-
10	?	O	-	-
11	Kill	O	-	-
12	us	O	-	-
13	if	O	-	-
14	it	O	-	-
15	was	O	-	-
16	turned	O	-	-
17	round	O	-	-
18	,	O	-	-
19	would	O	-	-
20	n't	O	-	-
21	you	O	-	-
22	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700307
# text = Suppose it's him that did Mad-Eye. How would you feel then?
1	Suppose	O	-	-
2	it	O	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	him	O	-	-
5	that	O	-	-
6	did	O	-	-
7	Mad	B-PER	-	-
8	Eye	I-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	How	O	-	-
11	would	O	-	-
12	you	O	-	-
13	feel	O	-	-
14	then	O	-	-
15	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700308
# text = It's better we wipe their memories.  We kill them, they'll know we were here.
1	It	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	better	O	-	-
4	we	O	-	-
5	wipe	O	-	-
6	their	O	-	-
7	memories	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	We	O	-	-
10	kill	O	-	-
11	them	O	-	-
12	,	O	-	-
13	they	O	-	-
14	'll	O	-	-
15	know	O	-	-
16	we	O	-	-
17	were	O	-	-
18	here	O	-	-
19	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700309
# text = You're the boss. Hermione?
1	You	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	boss	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-
6	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
7	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700310
# text = You're the best with spells.
1	You	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	the	O	-	-
4	best	O	-	-
5	with	O	-	-
6	spells	O	-	-
7	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700311
# text = Obliviate.
1	Obliviate	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700312
# text = How is it they knew we were there?
1	How	O	-	-
2	is	O	-	-
3	it	O	-	-
4	they	O	-	-
5	knew	O	-	-
6	we	O	-	-
7	were	O	-	-
8	there	O	-	-
9	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700313
# text = Maybe you still have the Trace on you.
1	Maybe	O	-	-
2	you	O	-	-
3	still	O	-	-
4	have	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	Trace	O	-	-
7	on	O	-	-
8	you	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700314
# text = Can't be. The Trace breaks at seventeen. It's Wizarding law.
1	Ca	O	-	-
2	n't	O	-	-
3	be	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-
5	The	O	-	-
6	Trace	O	-	-
7	breaks	O	-	-
8	at	O	-	-
9	seventeen	O	-	-
10	.	O	-	-
11	It	O	-	-
12	's	O	-	-
13	Wizarding	O	-	-
14	law	O	-	-
15	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700315
# text = What?
1	What	O	-	-
2	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700316
# text = We didn't celebrate your birthday, Harry.  Ginny and I -- we'd prepared a cake.  We were going to bring it out at the end of the wedding...
1	We	O	-	-
2	did	O	-	-
3	n't	O	-	-
4	celebrate	O	-	-
5	your	O	-	-
6	birthday	O	-	-
7	,	O	-	-
8	Harry	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Ginny	B-PER	-	-
11	and	O	-	-
12	I	O	-	-
13	we	O	-	-
14	'd	O	-	-
15	prepared	O	-	-
16	a	O	-	-
17	cake	O	-	-
18	.	O	-	-
19	We	O	-	-
20	were	O	-	-
21	going	O	-	-
22	to	O	-	-
23	bring	O	-	-
24	it	O	-	-
25	out	O	-	-
26	at	O	-	-
27	the	O	-	-
28	end	O	-	-
29	of	O	-	-
30	the	O	-	-
31	wedding	O	-	-
32	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700317
# text = Hermione.  I appreciate the thought -- honestly.  But given that we were almost killed by a couple of Death Eaters a few minutes ago...
1	Hermione	B-PER	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	appreciate	O	-	-
5	the	O	-	-
6	thought	O	-	-
7	honestly	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	But	O	-	-
10	given	O	-	-
11	that	O	-	-
12	we	O	-	-
13	were	O	-	-
14	almost	O	-	-
15	killed	O	-	-
16	by	O	-	-
17	a	O	-	-
18	couple	O	-	-
19	of	O	-	-
20	Death	B-ORG	-	-
21	Eaters	I-ORG	-	-
22	a	O	-	-
23	few	O	-	-
24	minutes	O	-	-
25	ago	O	-	-
26	...	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700318
# text = Right.  Perspective.
1	Right	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-
3	Perspective	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700319
# text = We've got to get off the streets, get somewhere safe.
1	We	O	-	-
2	've	O	-	-
3	got	O	-	-
4	to	O	-	-
5	get	O	-	-
6	off	O	-	-
7	the	O	-	-
8	streets	O	-	-
9	,	O	-	-
10	get	O	-	-
11	somewhere	O	-	-
12	safe	O	-	-
13	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700320
# text = I have an idea.
1	I	O	-	-
2	have	O	-	-
3	an	O	-	-
4	idea	O	-	-
5	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700321
# text = Severus Snape?
1	Severus	B-PER	-	-
2	Snape	I-PER	-	-
3	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700322
# text = Mad-Eye...?
1	Mad	B-PER	-	-
2	Eye	I-PER	-	-
3	...	O	-	-
4	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700323
# text = What was that about?
1	What	O	-	-
2	was	O	-	-
3	that	O	-	-
4	about	O	-	-
5	?	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700324
# text = Mad-eye's doing, I'd guess.  In case Snape decided to come snooping.
1	Mad	B-PER	-	-
2	eye	I-PER	-	-
3	's	O	-	-
4	doing	O	-	-
5	,	O	-	-
6	I	O	-	-
7	'd	O	-	-
8	guess	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	In	O	-	-
11	case	O	-	-
12	Snape	B-PER	-	-
13	decided	O	-	-
14	to	O	-	-
15	come	O	-	-
16	snooping	O	-	-
17	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700325
# text = Homenum revelio.
1	Homenum	O	-	-
2	revelio	O	-	-
3	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700326
# text = It's a spell to reveal human presence.
1	It	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	a	O	-	-
4	spell	O	-	-
5	to	O	-	-
6	reveal	O	-	-
7	human	O	-	-
8	presence	O	-	-
9	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700327
# text = We're alone.
1	We	O	-	-
2	're	O	-	-
3	alone	O	-	-
4	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700328
# text = Lumos.
1	Lumos	O	-	-
2	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700329
# text = Dear Sirius.  Thank you for Harry's birthday present.  You'd think he'd been born on a broom.
1	Dear	O	-	-
2	Sirius	B-PER	-	-
3	.	O	-	-
4	Thank	O	-	-
5	you	O	-	-
6	for	O	-	-
7	Harry	B-PER	-	-
8	's	O	-	-
9	birthday	O	-	-
10	present	O	-	-
11	.	O	-	-
12	You	O	-	-
13	'd	O	-	-
14	think	O	-	-
15	he	O	-	-
16	'd	O	-	-
17	been	O	-	-
18	born	O	-	-
19	on	O	-	-
20	a	O	-	-
21	broom	O	-	-
22	.	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700330
# text = James says he's got the look of a Seeker, but then James would.  We had a very quiet birthday tea, just us and old Bathilda, who dotes on Harry.  Wormy dropped by late in the day, but seemed down and didn't stay long.  James is frustrated being shut up here, but Dumbledore's still got his Invisibility Cloak, so he doesn't have much choice.  By the way, Bathilda tells the most amazing stories about our old Headmaster. I don't know how much to believe. Can it really be true that Dumbledore --
1	James	B-PER	-	-
2	says	O	-	-
3	he	O	-	-
4	's	O	-	-
5	got	O	-	-
6	the	O	-	-
7	look	O	-	-
8	of	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	Seeker	O	-	-
11	,	O	-	-
12	but	O	-	-
13	then	O	-	-
14	James	B-PER	-	-
15	would	O	-	-
16	.	O	-	-
17	We	O	-	-
18	had	O	-	-
19	a	O	-	-
20	very	O	-	-
21	quiet	O	-	-
22	birthday	O	-	-
23	tea	O	-	-
24	,	O	-	-
25	just	O	-	-
26	us	O	-	-
27	and	O	-	-
28	old	O	-	-
29	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
30	,	O	-	-
31	who	O	-	-
32	dotes	O	-	-
33	on	O	-	-
34	Harry	B-PER	-	-
35	.	O	-	-
36	Wormy	B-PER	-	-
37	dropped	O	-	-
38	by	O	-	-
39	late	O	-	-
40	in	O	-	-
41	the	O	-	-
42	day	O	-	-
43	,	O	-	-
44	but	O	-	-
45	seemed	O	-	-
46	down	O	-	-
47	and	O	-	-
48	did	O	-	-
49	n't	O	-	-
50	stay	O	-	-
51	long	O	-	-
52	.	O	-	-
53	James	B-PER	-	-
54	is	O	-	-
55	frustrated	O	-	-
56	being	O	-	-
57	shut	O	-	-
58	up	O	-	-
59	here	O	-	-
60	,	O	-	-
61	but	O	-	-
62	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-
63	's	O	-	-
64	still	O	-	-
65	got	O	-	-
66	his	O	-	-
67	Invisibility	O	-	-
68	Cloak	O	-	-
69	,	O	-	-
70	so	O	-	-
71	he	O	-	-
72	does	O	-	-
73	n't	O	-	-
74	have	O	-	-
75	much	O	-	-
76	choice	O	-	-
77	.	O	-	-
78	By	O	-	-
79	the	O	-	-
80	way	O	-	-
81	,	O	-	-
82	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
83	tells	O	-	-
84	the	O	-	-
85	most	O	-	-
86	amazing	O	-	-
87	stories	O	-	-
88	about	O	-	-
89	our	O	-	-
90	old	O	-	-
91	Headmaster	B-TTL	-	-
92	.	O	-	-
93	I	O	-	-
94	do	O	-	-
95	n't	O	-	-
96	know	O	-	-
97	how	O	-	-
98	much	O	-	-
99	to	O	-	-
100	believe	O	-	-
101	.	O	-	-
102	Can	O	-	-
103	it	O	-	-
104	really	O	-	-
105	be	O	-	-
106	true	O	-	-
107	that	O	-	-
108	Dumbledore	B-PER	-	-

# sent_id = 700331
# text = Harry!  Harry!
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Harry	B-PER	-	-
4	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700332
# text = Ron!  I've found him!
1	Ron	B-PER	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	I	O	-	-
4	've	O	-	-
5	found	O	-	-
6	him	O	-	-
7	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700333
# text = Good!  Tell him from me he's a git!
1	Good	O	-	-
2	!	O	-	-
3	Tell	O	-	-
4	him	O	-	-
5	from	O	-	-
6	me	O	-	-
7	he	O	-	-
8	's	O	-	-
9	a	O	-	-
10	git	O	-	-
11	!	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700334
# text = Harry, you can't just disappear. We thought --
1	Harry	B-PER	-	-
2	,	O	-	-
3	you	O	-	-
4	ca	O	-	-
5	n't	O	-	-
6	just	O	-	-
7	disappear	O	-	-
8	.	O	-	-
9	We	O	-	-
10	thought	O	-	-

# sent_id = 700335
# text = It's from your Mum.  To Sirius. Bathilda Bagshot...?
1	It	O	-	-
2	's	O	-	-
3	from	O	-	-
4	your	O	-	-
5	Mum	O	-	-
6	.	O	-	-
7	To	O	-	-
8	Sirius	B-PER	-	-
9	.	O	-	-
10	Bathilda	B-PER	-	-
11	Bagshot	I-PER	-	-
12	...	O	-	-
13	?	O	-	-